The program is presented by me lawyer Marcus Lodin at the law firm
the crime agency are you suspected or exposed to crime
Didn't hesitate to beat me a
[Music]
Signal well then Klagen yes thank you I am. We present ourselves to the item
Outside so you know that my name is Per Erik Rinsell and I am a prosecutor and we have
JU BAST YOU COME HERE AND TELL OR YOU COME HERE BETT YOU COME HERE AND
Tell us about an event that was the 14th eh of September this year and I was thinking
really that I will ask pretty much open question to you there
I ask you first try thought back even if it is hard attempt intended
back what was it what happened this evening
My husband and I were home came from work and
eh and so i said yes but i go back and check in at SL what time will
The train to Djurbro I go back to the bedroom
And then I see the lamp the role curtain is reduced
eh from the bedroom so I see that the lamp lights out and then I hear something
eh some sounds so I looked a little behind
curtain and saw two two figures two children I experienced they
which had to go on it actually reminded me of when we have children as as
rings on the door when there is bus or candy they mumbled something and they were
A little high Judah so I thought yes v what is this
For something they had hoods I saw they from behind it was something strange who is
that is coming now so late thought of the daughter but no it can't
tune so i hold in my
phone and start walking from the bedroom and then I just hear that she
starting to knock so it was, after all, it was not
ordinary without i think they knocked with with
pistols i just squat in between at the frame between the bedroom and
the front door and so thought no it is something that is not right there
The hoods I thought they scared me the most and then I hear my husband Emir say
from the living room who is it he is used to we open but I thought it is
no one who comes home to us after nine without calling then and so
Does he come from the living room and I told him only we must not open
that is something sumt I thought and fortunately he did not open up because he
usually open and why should we not be able to open so we have lived in
the house for 23 years and in the same weave they start shooting
The door bursts and so we panic both I
goes against living room toward the bedroom he starts to pull me toward
The toilet yes
Mm then we call or he says to
me call the police i hold in and he serer that i hold the phone i
can't the number i start calling beat 114 14 he says
112 and then we are in the toilet then the police responded or they answered and so
where you
Eh I think like this eh you described that you were in
the bedroom and you saw that the light was lit eh so I understand you right where
somewhere the light comes on it is when you come in eh at the gate so is
it a lamp above and it feels yes then I understand and when you look out
And you say you see two children outside where do they stand when they stand by they pull
Just that was it maybe I forgot to mention that I heard that we have a
a glazed entrance and it is like all spirits and then I hear how they open etc.
But fortunately it was open as the daughter has not come home we
usually close it in the evening but it was open for her to come
had it been closed then they would not be able to open it because there is no one
handle and there are many who do not know that you should only pull the glass then
would probably start shooting and i lie in bed bed is hit mm
the bed mattress is damaged, so it is completely silk so it was clean
Lucky there that it was open m plus that
We were that we had unimaginable so it was after all
It was fortunate that we moved on my husband and I all the time had we been
In the bedroom then we would be shot so
that yeah i don't know we had real angel yes with us and i think like this
Then now you have described that the ones they had pulled away so they came in through this
the glass door when they knock on or I will ask later when you see them they stand
at your front door then or where do they stand somewhere eh they stand they stand
by when I heard or when I saw mm that when I felt that the lamp
light up when I looked then they were just off the window of the bedroom but it is
entrance to this entrance or to the entrance to the house so they first saw
the ones there while I panic or I go against I was going to go to against
against Emir living room etc. and then I heard that they came in mm into this entrance
The entrance changes the door yes and then they are inside and should I knock on the door etc. so
it is the door they knock on they knock on the door not on everything a door no and
you said you you perceived they knocked hard and you thought it might be
the guns they knocked out with it must be something it was not ordinary no ordinary
So sounds you also mentioned you said you perceive that they let them talk a little
neighbor if I understood it right and so that as they mumbled
no when they knock on they shout something or say they
Something then
ehm no no i remember don't you know i no i don't remember i don't remember if i
Thought I went into the bedroom completely and no it was so I was
was in shock state so I I I heard nothing to no
And then I have understood you right as you may confirm if I have taken
right that you were in the bedroom first but you go out of the bedroom out towards the hall
and emir he was in the living room and also comes out towards the hall M exactly when
They will start when the first shots come what or first shot comes
can you try to describe what you and emir as carefully as you can
from home I am I am at the frame yes there and Emir stands for that
The toilet door is just behind and he stands there
and yes you can say that it is a few meters apart you and yes we but that
maybe a meter a meter or one and one two meters max so not even so no that
must be one meter apart he came just yes and so they start
shoot mm and when when they start shooting comes
You remember how do you react when eh runs you put it down what do you
I was on my way then I know I was on my way to the bedroom because it is after all
the same it can say it is only the door that is away there eh I
know that I thought I will inhibit myself under the bed or and so in the same
With that, Emil pulls me mm against and so we say to the toilet he says
Mm mm i
understands and he lives you scream he he said after all
Yeah what are you doing and yeah so there idiots or i know i don't remember
exactly but I know he yes said something to them
mm I understand and you have already described a little neighbor you said you
Perceive it as there were two children and they had the main assigned etc. do you have if
you try to think there is something more you can describe them in appearance
Long -term clothing in terms of something they were, after all, they were not long
When when I serve they were short then I think of our son who is 193 mm
long and then I think yes they are short they were not so long no mm and what about
you try to put words into what it is that makes you perceive that they are children v
What is it that makes you think so length and figure thus and that
they put on each other for themselves
eh body language maybe or yes if I understood it correctly you saw them from behind
When you saw them etc. just m then have you been to it but you
described a little so you were shocked but if you try to describe a little more v what
did you feel when this when the shots
came yes I thought it was it was run
for us that now they will kill us so it was mm because yes no that
be no but it is reminiscent we come from the war ourselves we so
is a traumatic experience that you have experienced now etc. that you have needed
experienced now again etc. so it is, after all, it is terrible it is not possible to describe
cannot find words and describe how I feel it jabar, so that one should
have to escape again or thus is what I have lived in Sweden for 32 years and came
hit to be able to live normally now we feel that life has
stopped and why so what is it so worth no that you need to
experience this and it is
Terrible
you you were into it that your daughter should home lived at home normally and
your son Aldin he did not live at home then no he did not live at home since May no
And it was we like
so chose after all the help before we got it was not good but our daughter
lived at home and we have two dotters it says that Aling's family consists of
A sister he has two big sisters one sister eldest sister is 33 years old and she
Lives in his own apartment and the other sister Eh moved back home to
us last year or August 22 and so she was on her way too to move out etc.
But she lived and she is written on she was written on
address just so lucky she wasn't home then we don't know how because yes know
we not how we would have gone now no I have to ask you about it because we see after all
that there is a bedroom on the ground floor where balls have gone in
So there is a room upstairs too
where there had been a ball through the roof cup approximately mm is the daughter's room
then the daughter's room okay yes I just understand
mm and then so you've heard me say that there has been some worry around Alin
Before that you feel it is true or
Eh yes it was m that was according to eh yes according to police so it was a little
just exactly and Alin wasn't home for the last three years so he was after all
Eh yes he was not at home no and i have understood that he vase abroad eh no
From May he is abroad from May he is abroad yes but think so so
Was he placed eh according to social services and absolutely I thought from May so is
he abroad and you just thought was a good solution for exactly
just support him if you say so yes exactly
mm you I stay there thanks so much yes thank you for thanks so much gabriela
Malmborg would you like to ask questions yes thank you eh I was going to start by
Ask you later on what I said earlier today was something of what I said
that was incorrect in any way or so or was it correct it was correct mm and how
Does it feel to you now to be here
about that contact too but we still have that we have had
Contact D It took time before they heard but
eh we those according to them so we should not live at home so we fi but we got no help
So the ones we did not get they have not said you can live here or there but yes we
Don't think you should live at home We think you should go from
Sweden so they could not guarantee anyone
security for us no for you you have mentioned to me that there was a short -term and
A long -term plan can you tell us a little about what they asked if we had
thoughts to move abroad entirely permanent eh yes long -term plan
In short, we have the opportunity to go now and that we had
And we did then we went abroad etc. and you did pretty much
fast and eh additional occasions we have g in a receipt or a basis
for a trip but there have been other trips also precance just we went first
we went September 21 eh and then we went
in October
Again, so that was the terrible situation that, then, that
man after the shooting the police tell us that we should we should not remain in
The house then we went to our friends was where we haven't even slept in the morning so
All of us three are going to work so you are just shocked and we can't
accept that we cannot live normally and according to the police they said
Yes eventually so maybe that day they told us too yes but it is a house you
Can maybe come back since the day after so they say no no no you will
Absolutely not stay at home and no we didn't dare
at all prime.se
Yes and eh i understand that it was very dumb but right there in
beginning how was the job there you went to work or how did it see
Out yes I went to work but I
Eh I took vacation as well as I had I could take sick leave
me so I was not I could not concentrate or anything so I
Thought I had six weeks of vacation savings as I got sick after all
Last year and
operated and then I thought then I take vacation instead I took some
holiday days too but at work so it is
the rather demanding work as eh store manager and staff too as s i
was the reason for it yes it is because I thought then
May i get more paid if i take sick if i sick leave i dont get alike
much paid as I had my saved days
So I took out holiday days
mm just that and if we go into more on your feeling then you have you have gone through
a little now all the time when you have talked and so but can you describe more how exactly it
Here the event has influenced your
everyday it affected in the way that I don't live my life
longer that you feel insecure cannot sleep concentrate
me i'm still sick after my illness so it has only gotten worse now
does it feel
who know me terribly all so small
destroyed
As I said it is difficult to describe how one feels
So feel that I no that I am not the same person as me
Be yes I don't know etc. We can't spend time with our daughters in the same way they
cannot we cannot be in our house we cannot spend time with our friends and
relatives thus it is not the same life you have as one had really
not mm and i showed a medical certificate that you have received a sick leave certain
time and then it was under medical treatment so it stands soothing and then
Did you get a referral to a psychologist yes exactly I got to write a written
sedatives and and it mir and i got sleep agents too you also got sleep
Medicine etc. was something that you chose to take or what did it look like
with sedative medicine and as a means there was something yes you so it is
quite often i need both we both need to take and now you say in the presen so it is
still so you need to take yes just can still not sleep and no
So I yes it is a trauma thus that can not describe as Emil said after all
When you were in the war then you knew which side to be careful and
scared against but here you don't know that you don't really know so it is
After all, it is fear all the time so I am afraid of my daughters too and
So it's awful
Mm and then you met psychologist on three occasions exactly and it what touched
the
Contact sorry what did you say about eh the contact i guess it touched
This situation yes exactly and how to process maybe or yes
exactly eh you serve the only only way is to
You have to process it and then he gave me some tips and so on and but but
But it will be difficult it will be difficult to process indeed
So it felt like one day maybe being good but the next three days are
The horrible and
yes mm eh and then I know then that it is
You who really had contact with people who, although it became now then that
It ended up on EH EMIR's individual claim so it is you who had the contacts
simply ehm and eh there were things that were destroyed so might be able to start with
And and tell us what what did you look like at home and you after this event
Yes it was yes it was terrible it was holes everywhere
and yes so there was glass in the hall outside also all thander it was
the glass there and no it was awful to be in there and come we
came eh after three days four days and would pick up medicine emir's medicine and
some things and so we went in with the police and no but it was
horrible really mm and i have also written in my individual claim or
Our individual claims there that there were several things that broke, among other things
refrigerator and just doors and windows and alternative door outer door windows
eh bat mattress
The duvet cover pillowed even yes and the OP floor also h stm and and and
I said the thing about scaffolding illegal then that they did not want to
Ehm yes but come home to you to do this inspection and before that
They would have to grant you some compensation and then and then I got there too
a question about the difference where I too thought you can explain a little so
That it will not be wrong exactly what that contact looked exactly eh Folksam says
that eh in view of the circumstances so
Can't we send an entrepreneur to you and eh do inspection nose okay then
asked it have you changed the condition or no that is
The yes it is advice we have received and so there MHM okay then you can hire your own company
or something any company and we did and what the company has done
as a diet suggestions when it thought Folksam or officer at Folksam to
Eh, for example, establishment and that is to move on furniture
EH is a cost and that they also paid for extra security because it is
not many companies that wanted to come eh and inspect and take the job on and that
Contact eh and what did they say anything about to you then about eh emir's company
as he had his car company what did they say about it just eh he asked me can't
your husband lock in eh while he works and you can
not work with customers and lock in there are no customers coming and yes
to one a closed workshop so so to
end he had to put down his workshop after 21 21 years for it went
not especially when we were told later that someone had called Emir something
numbers that were strange too mm and when was it like it
The decision was made you can remember on October 24 he closed down the workshop etc.
prime.se and then he also terminated in connection with the then lease then
Exactly the agreement was until last December 2023
eh and then he would empty the workshop and he
was sick and it was not possible and then we had to extend a month eh at
the company and then we had to pay 25,000 or 23000 something rent for January
Month of January 2024 mm just that and eh can you tell us how
How have you experienced that Enem Mirr has been affected by it
Here yes
that he doesn't feel good he doesn't sleep on he sleeps we sleep
not both but he he can wake up in the middle of the night and cannot fall asleep
If he has had heart problems for 10 years he has had a heart attack then it
This has not given anyone better that he feels better but of course be
worse he could not he cannot concentrate as one serves lump in
stomach all the time terrible feeling
mm so it has taken
on him too of course and and I read from his
journal notes that there were suicidal thoughts and stuff like that
As you have noticed on something
So put
I I wont talk about it no eh but then have no more questions for you
Sending thank you very much Anton Sundberg would you like to ask questions no question please
no questions for the sig you have any question yes thank you any short question just so i
understand things right ehm you you have described this one
event I will not ask you to describe it again I will just say that I have
recorded some things correctly eh you you saw two kids outside and I record
that they mumble something and e put on each other these kids yes
just that is it on it is hard to explain but then it reminds me
about that when you hear that children run towards the eh entrance for example as when they
runs at Easter or at Hallowen or eh that was the way I experienced
that they were children they were short as I said eh but when I look short so they
may be 1 75 too and so I think they are understanding but you didn't hear what
as SAS but some kind of discussion was going on between them at least PR they
mumbled something mm mm and then it felt like they put in to that when
I checked eh when I removed the curtain it was maybe two three cm when I
checked so I saw I see them I see them and so I see
that, like that they are to come to mind who
are as to come to first in the door etc. there to the door or something like that in
all cases did you see who it was that knocked no
we can't see it because we have what is it called
The eh glass is shimmered so you don't see no you saw any weapon
No, then I thought about asking about these different costs that you have had only as
I understood right you flew away abroad I should not ask where or so eh without
I understand the right that you flew abroad on the request of the police to
The police thought you would fly except it would be best for us and escape and
Leave the country okay eh late in terms of this work as
Utv at your home for I understand the right that the insurance company thought that
This eh cost proposal that had been submitted from the company was not reasonable
Mm exactly they thought part of the cost was after all
eh too high as, for example, when there is an establishment, they were meant that you
should move on furniture etc. eh while you have to paint because you had to
repaint the walls what are we talking about for sum as
They thought was unreasonable you know that eh what we got what had the insurance company
Seemed to be reasonable you got any such explanation total costs you mean
Or yes they thought this was unreasonable yes 28,000 they thought it was
It was too much but then we got 200,000 so 48.00 is what they took
away that establishment and there is the security that companies have paid
because they take the risk as well and come home to us okay so
The insurance company made an assessment that the sum they pay out it is reasonable
It is a reasonable amount just okay as we did not get we have unlucky
Vall Insurance but Ollys
Fall Following this event because others did not want to eh they took that
is one that they say it is the security that they pay for as to extra
paid because of the risk or what to say mm
Okay you have any idea what this extra is that they took for this eh
How much extra they took for think it was maybe five
5000 including VAT I think it's a guess then that yes I think it etc. I
Can check there may be any cost proposal
left eh then i had a question i think prosecutor mentioned it
initially that your son's residence has been Utsö for
more landscaped fires earlier eh you don't have to mention any
addresses at all I just want to say my question is just that is meant
that then the depths of 317 eh our son has never had any other accommodation except
at home with us and I have reacted to the majority as well
Eh what are the numerous fires that we know we have received a police report
on it and it's shortly after this event and it's October 4th and I
asked Eh Frida yesterday also what is meant by
this eh she wondered too so no it was only once and it should have
Happened after this yes it is October 4 Okay mm
exactly that were my questions thank you so much questions i have no follow -up
Thank you I am satisfied Visel Abdalla do you want to set
Questions currently have no questions but there may be questions on
Monday thanks etc. Yes I have no questions but yes thought to do an enlightenment late
just yes but then we can end the hearing first if there are no more questions
Well and then the f complaint begins by asking questions or is it you who should
set yes, please hello hi eh senida has told us about this event but i
thought you would also be able to tell you what you remember about this and I was thinking
that you would be able to tell you then with your own words and then maybe I ask some questions
Tist so I walked up eh and walked toward the bedroom and through h I saw her eh in
at the eh door in the bedroom she sat down and waved that I did not open you know and
Then I noticed that to something came you know so I raw in to the fool you know and
Then I should first heard the glass on the door you know I did not hoe shots I just hde
like h throw stones or something i saw the glass she tried to go into the bedroom
and I pulled her toward
toilet ask them call you know the police you know she pressed the phone i said call
1002 you know s when she called it answered any woman i had to talk to her
During that time it was also you know you hde you know prime.se small stones throw on
roads know yes what we were shot know so I up plenty too during the war man
Don't have shot then when you are shot about if if any bullet comes nearby
One only gets the one you have not shot unfortunately
mm eh and I understood right that you were at
upstairs first no we were yes you were down all the time up know yes okay eh
and then when you hear these knocks were what you found then yes we were after all
her you know she tried to go into so the room then I pulled her toward toilet
mm I sat down you know pulled toilet okay and is this in the hall then so
do you understand
Okay I don't know what's its angel howing that we we haven't shot
When you check then know what did the fun went you
know it was miracle that we actually survived etc. so when you hear these sounds
As you described as pebbles it is in the hall all the time then yes and where
Sending somewhere we frame letters with it is just that is not that far from
The toilet to the bedroom it's just maybe meters etc. Okay and then you went in
to the restroom toilet okay eh and did you see some people eh under
this time no eh mins here what time no no
comment no no have you talked to him about this event
Yes i talked to you want to say what he has said then no no okay thanks then i have
No more questions no thanks so much Gabriella Malmborg
Eh yes thank you we have to share a bit on this microphone now m eh i think i
should ask about the same questions that I ask eh sinida around your
Feeling can you can describe partly in this particular moment when you pull her in on
toilet we might be able to start there how did it feel for
you v at the moment I thought what can you do best that you survive you know I
was perhaps more conscious than she because I was in such situation you know I
experienced such stuff not she and one try your best miga way
I think I have done right anyway etc. It turned out that was right mm
Yes it really did eh but so but know you you know when such happens you know
via becomes panic you know when you want to get out or something you know then you are
Open but it is important to react
you see
they easily have me in the lump but I interpreted as you anyway
tried to act rationally there on the spot and think out solutions and so
But how has it affected you after this then when it may have been in
what has happened to how has it affected you in your everyday life then
Yes it disappeared a security as he had joy
I don't know if will
back and then but the work you know I have had
vests 20 years you know I thought i have two three years left for retirement thought
drive on the last two three years since it has
Happened It is not possible to describe
feeling no you can try to describe how how did you come to that decision that you would
close again and how was it just
bitten sam tke you know that one should be lying down
Tr still i'm not cool it it is hard for me you know
After 20 years we've had pretty nice cone you
know working together now now you have to do if you know the borjan
from the beginning of the third time
Mm mm and
[Music] eh it also appears by your
medical certificate that you got some physical complaints because of this yes you know so
Säve my work so one cannot properly concentrate on work or
I want
not work with because of concentration I
don't want to do careless job you know it g I parry the car you know so that is too
risk to others if you do something wrong
Mm mm eh it also states that if I do not
still it a feeling man there is this cramp in the stomach that it I had late
it happens all
Time it disappears there when we go a little abroad after two days release
a little you know then if you intend to come back it will come back it
The feeling etc.
ehm and then so how would you describe the nights then after this
The event
Yes sleeping badly wakes up
often yes yes it says it says you fall asleep
But that you wake up and then cannot fall asleep if that task is true
stands in heal yes it is not true but sometimes it might be thought to reach so you can
Put a little neighbor when you wake up [music]
Mm just the mm mm I have no more questions to
Digir etc. is any of the defenders who want to ask questions a single question yes
please eh in the same way just so I have
understood it right it as stated before you
can confirm a task in terms of your company I understand that right that
were the police who urged you not to go back to the company and work no
I have to lock myself in company h
And you know it can't be locking up and work you know no no I understand but
I I I interpreted a task that is left before they may have the wood to on the police
prompt so you do not return to the company it was the police who gave the council to
not that is correct yes yes should no security all mine
Location yes that was that question thank you very much Visel Abdalla would you like to
any question yes thank you mm hey i also thought of the same subject
Around your business you can say anything about what the result looked like for your
business
thus eh you have to talk to my fro she takes care of v with economy etc. I think a
Individual company so it is your finances too yes what I with my wife
take care of the economic part and eh paper accountant so there okay so you mean
that you have no no idea at all yes she takes care of everything prime and is the same thing
For the result for 2022 Yes on all since 20 years 21 years back
Okay well then I have to ask those questions to my wife please
mm Then we finish the hearing you want to set it
The question started and then I leave the word to the prosecutor please yes thank you yes Danil
Eh Per Erik Rinsell, after all, is the prosecutor in this case and I would
want to ask you first how you feel the others here in the hall
eh no i don't feel i don't know any of them you know none of them have
you met any of them sometime eh no
There's a guy here named Soran have you ever met him
No in your phone so there is a contact named Soran South you know who
eh call him Danny or do you call him something else I call him it
mm there is i have i have read somewhere anything that you would call
him something else yj or yg
YG is there no comment no
you you said he's been your friend for a while v When was it in time about
Eh i don't know where last fall i have no idea no therefore we
Have seen we have looked at your phones and you have some contacts last fall
on different
channels is something you mine that makes you remember more easily no no
Eh armando guy sitting here too eh he has it he has told himself
That he has a signal oil called El Hamilton El Hamilton you recognize that
you had some contact with hamilton no no you recognize Armando no
No and on September 14th that is what we have talked a lot you have been sitting
And listened to I have talked quite a lot that you have heard and my colleagues
No you heard maybe the plaintiff here late and emir that two children as they
perceived had shot on them is something you recognize
No
comment whether we think about eh whether it is you or not how do you feel how thinks
you when you hear them tell us how does it feel what do you think
Eh i don't know no i asked i can say i i have not been involved
In this somehow but I thought it was quite terrible to hear
they tell us what they have rattled out how how how did you feel
Eh i v sorry now i didn't hear what you said i don't know you don't know
no have you been down in Jordbro on the 14th no comment no
comment If I say so we know you were in earth residents as you were arrested in
no v you tell me why you record the movie i miss comment
no may it have to do with San V say Diner and GS sends to you eh
Just before you send a movie showing all all weapons no one
comment no after the deed and we'll see how you
record a movie and so you say something like this aina came the second we
began to flutter eh they were there right away approximately
so tell me about it no comment doesn't remember it no
because by saying so walla eh or jalla or what you de aina came the second
We started to flutter so you get quite clearly the impression that but we are
two people at least two or more and then I wonder was there two or where
several people who shot no it was only me was I had said wrong during
the time you it was you really meant you would say I but then you said we
because you mistook
Yes why do you say that Aina came then because they did not do no one
comment is that you are afraid of someone because you
recording the movie to try to pretend that A came canceled because you were clinging to you
A comment because you do not complete the assignment you do not do what you were
Supply in comment you are afraid of
any t you have heard me read up some
conversation eh and then know and then read then i have
First read a lot about what kings you are and what brothers
You are and brother and you are fantastic and so
you recognize it no no comment no then when you fail so
is if you say the kindest you say about you it is that you are horungar
Eh how does it feel no comment no have you been exposed to
Pressures Prime.se has someone contacted you and said that you who are 14
May take on this no no comment etc. No comment you can't
even say that it has not happened but you just do not want to comment
No we have looked you know the one we have looked at your phone pretty much
And there are contacts with Dinero there are contacts with El Hamilton it
Available contacts with mixtape There are contacts with eh
Danny Eh you recognize message is that something you want to comment no
comment
No when there is a message that is as many as possible no children what
Do you think it means no comment
No will you give some comments more about on questions I answer eh like me
setting no no then i stay there thanks okay
Hello there is anyone who wants to try to ask questions then to Daniel goals
the assistant yes they were no questions i don't hear no thanks
something no not directly actually okay with the permission of the right then so I thought
Read up yes the watch interrogation etc. then the first hearing held with Danil
It is on page 650 in the main protocol etc. It was held on September 15, 1942
Started then it is recorded like this Daniel so you have to comment if you want
or not it is noted that you should have said so
Here tell yourself what happened yesterday there were some who told me to
There was a job you could do then that I would shoot a house do you remember
that you have said so to the police eh
No may it be true that you have said so to the police if it says
Note I know
[Applause]
Not since but you you don't remember this
No if I ask you like this then who was it who got this job eh no one
comment okay
Then I was going to read what is on page 600 EH 651 second paragraph from above
eh question is how does he give the contact we are still the first hearing so I read
from the second sentence I would rather not answer what the friends are called
not been involved it was me who got the job the friends heard it will
Remember that you have said this to the police I know
It may not be true that you have said this if it is recorded by the police
maybe i won't
remember and on talk about this eh I or
We remember how you expressed yourself in your first hearing about who shot it was
me or we no I remember
not again with the court's permission on page 651 then we are 1 t 3 fourth paragraph
top mm third sentence in so I read
recorded like this Daniil He writes that there is a job that you can do and
Earn MONEY YOU'RE ONLY SHOULD SHOULD AT A HOUSE I thank I I thank you later
The next day I do what I went there and shot
The door do you remember that you have said so to the police in comment in comment can
it suits if it has been noted so no comment no
comment then i stay there thanks mm and then
Excuse it was I apologize no f so a few more questions to just one question
Yes well hey daniel rodden named
I I was going to ask you eh on the same theme as these parts out of
The interrogations just read up would you like to answer the question of what you perceived
that you had been given for assignments so what was it really you would
do no okay it was read up now something that one would shoot at a
Port or similar would you like to comment on why it is expressed or
noted that you have expressed yourself so in interrogation okay yes I stay there thanks more
questions from they complain yes I do and I can say that I chose to let everyone
Ask questions first before I choose to go in and want to play parts M and
Since then some parts eh are preferred from interrogation, I intend to do so that
I intend to play a number of minutes out of a hearing and then I intend to set
Questions until it goes well It goes well thank you what hearing is that then
interrogation two it was held on the 3rd of November 2023 mm Eh and I do this way I yes
eh
should just get on so that sound is with here put it ht or been on
Something here you see introductions to the interrogation then as often on like this at
Child interrogation so it will see that there is a camera where yes etc. yes apologize I
have not connected me it is me like
So now it first starts about five minutes
with questions about general character so I will leave it and so I think that
I go forward just to show which deed much like or what deed
As Danil is served so that he is notified of him, he explains what this is about
If he is not served the suspicion but one explains what he is about it is
about five minutes into it now I will play about six minutes
Yes tell me
Mm it was probably the most important
Eh i guess you know why you are here today m
Mm and why are you here today and should talk to me it's a v
is it called for shooting in Jordbro, etc. now it is so that you are under
15 years and therefore I can't share you any suspicion
mm But if you had been over 15 years old then I thought I should read up what you
had been suspected of then
Eh and then I had served suspicion of attempted murder by together
and consensus with others planned and completed a slide with firearms against one
Property at
the depth of 22.22 in the evening in Haninge municipality and you had also become then
spelled suspicion of serious weapons offense by consultation and in consensus with
other illegally or and up one held several guns and then had
The crime was considered serious when it was sharply charged and in public place and so
happened then this crime then eh
2309 September 14 at approximately 2222 and it is the same address then on the animal's slide
317 In Jordbro Haninge Municipality it would have sounded if you were 15 now you know that
Then I want you to tell you as accurately as possible
The story from the beginning
Eh i didn't remember as much it was still quite a long time ago but i can
Explain the most I can eh so me and my friend we had been sitting
somewhere and we had been sitting and talking just
Then I had gone away I was going to go
to another friend and we would meet some and then I went home after that
But this first friend I was with he had met someone I didn't know
there was someone who had a job a job what what does it mean a job v something
he could be done for money etc. and
eh what do you think it was for work he said what it was for something you would
make sliding etc so it was this person sitting on the balcony who said
that you would shoot something not y it was someone else who had met
him and told him no and then eh yg he said that guy he had
said that we could do this how old is this guy
eh 16 i think the one you sat and talked to it maybe 16 no he who
I was in the balcony with he was 16 15 around there maybe I can't remember but
other this other guy who had talked to yig he doesn't know he knows
after all not no have you been there before on this one
the house and so have you been there before eh yes so it is one it is my
in the center type mm tell us what it looks like where you
Here so I was going to pause and then I thought to hear with Danil about Danil
If you want to comment in any way that we have just listened
on eh no because here you talk about you have
got would get a job a shooting is it really one a comment and you
Talking about a friend named Dan and called YG Do you have any comment on
No I wonder so here you sit and lie to the police there
no comment no then I was going to go ahead and play a
good bit further ahead in the movie We are on page about 23 24 minutes into the movie
Do you reach the spicy side of what I am sorry I can I can come back with
No maybe 500 ME 700 MM mm and how did you know that where this home was low
somewhere he had said it was there who had said it
yes eh had he been there
Before I think you will find it it is not me you should ask sorry
It's not me you should ask no you mean it's the other guy but
Like from the time you find you take whose pistol then
Mm Describe how you go then all so I just follow him
mm runs afterwards then we find the house knocking and shooting you said you
KNACK TELL MORE KNACKS AND then shoots
knocking what you knock knocking on the door knocks on
The door is there someone at home I know no one open door all
sorry no one opens the door no one opens the door
shocked while sitting in this hearing at Annbritt Bö it was your
Explanation before why do you tell us this one
time no comment no
Otherwise so no yes eh do you remember where you threw
the guns somewhere no no comment is that
really that you ran through a forest and threw things I don't remember you remember
not no then i think i'll take some little ones
section to MM I also get tab in with questions than this paragraph is
want my questions at the end I just ask
The question sees prosecutors is appropriate you the hare you have we may be able to take it so then
If you have questions you are welcome to shout about if anyone else has questions but
Want to take your questions now about this then yes I ask my questions too
around some things that have been said in this paragraph Danil and it is up to you
As I said what you want to answer and comment eh I first thought to ask you
If this you were asked by EH this interrogator about knocks on the door
Mm and so it is recorded and we now heard that you should have said on the question
The knocking do you remember what you've said in it
The interview you don't remember no I don't remember with the permission of the court I thought
Then read on page 739 it is thus the third hearing held with Danil yes
And it was also a child interrogation similar to conditions yes
at the bottom of the page
739 so reads had recorded like this and it should be verbatim what you have said
Mm and so says the interrogator knocked both
on and so it says that you answer no it was
me and the interrogator say it was just you question marks how but how knocked
you i just knocked yes with what by hand you knocked with your hand yes and that is
Certainly etc. you remember you have said so to the police eh yes I remember it
mm he knows you
Yeah what do you have for relationship you he like i was not so close friend with me i
felt it is he who is with it is he yg huh it is yg it is he who was with
you at the house etc. so you mean that he is then danny that
his name is you know his name is Danny or how I call him Dan Dan calls
you he mm ehm is he who finds out everything
Mm what is going to happen etc. and by who then mm it is it is he who has found out
bath yes you have to talk to each other anyway when to do something like that he
had carried dangerous he had just said we would get money and do it mm but
I did not know how by whom no how long have you felt he didn't so long
Type for six months maybe half a year and what area he lives
otherwise who else would do it mm and what was you picked up then
Out of this bolten in Larsberg yes was somewhere kind of near the park I think close
Park
M I think we can stay there and I have another question then to
then yes then what is it with the memory now then e
Danny Yg In comment It is still a progress
for you previously did not remember but now you have no comment why do you want to
not comment on that simply we did not comment
What you choose not to comment on it okay thanks then I stay there
mm are you satisfied so I am satisfied yes there are more questions to Daniel no thanks
If we are going to be nay for the day then we do so then we are ready for today and we see you
eh and that's about the middle where eh what begins when the police ask feel
you to a person named Danil Kosim and then they show a picture and then they start
by answering no comments and then the police say no comments and then
If you answer no I know him, you already know as the prosecutor said he said that
We are comrades There are pictures of him in hand I know him it is not possible to
deny mm remind you that you have said so yes it is true then as you said then
Police no there's nothing I want to comment no okay
eh and so he then know him there is nothing i want to comment okay
Armando nothing I comment on no and the reason you don't want to
comment on this and what is it no it has my lawyer already raised mm
I think you should tell you if you want then yourself in this hearing about
of it nothing I want to comment eh do you want to say anything about what you did
eh at this place no no have you handled any weapons under this
The event nothing I want to comment on these weapons found you would like to say
something about them no your defense has last week
explained that you deny this event indictment one but in terms of
indictment that as a debt when serious weapons offense he explained that you
neither want to admit nor deny so thought if you want to develop it no
nothing gö so ok this car then as we have talked
If Nissan to YH is someone you know no nothing I comment no
Have you been to it nothing i tera eh we have also seen there that at 2230 so
right after the shooting then it rings in you why he does it nothing
I comment on no these movies we've seen on two
IPhone and a samsung eh When you were arrested etc. this is your phones nothing I
comment no eh would you say why you have two mobiles
No and one then samsung had no sim card you want to explain why no no
And this phone number has 2990 it's your phone number nothing I
comment no eh you wore these phones
As I said when you seized and you also stated the code for this iPhone
The phone would you like to comment on that as no no i have also made language on
The phone during the preliminary investigation MHM there is nothing you want to comment no no
Eh yes and then i have also received questions about about this regarding the phone you
have received questions about other chats in in interrogation, including then eh things like you
have written to your mom eh but there is mentioned this phone I thought that
I would read it too and it is a hearing held on November 24 and that
is on page 603 eh and it starts at the bottom where i think i'll read it for
to get context but they mention that they have found chats where you write to
your mother and then eh a few lines from the bottom so it starts with the police say then
You also write to your mom that you are home and pick up clothes so you answer yes
and then I jump down a few lines on the last line where you don't want to answer to
Your mom tells you to play football you remember that and then you answer
No it was a while since it's two months now i don't remember exactly
What I have written and then you say if it says what do you say if you have
Empty my nap and it stands and that's it then is that is what I wrote I guess
This is how you mention that it is your handset is something you want to comment
no no eh then i thought about asking some questions about
signal ehm it has been installed on your
phone and it was then installed the same day at half past 12 on the day and off
was installed at 2230 there is something you want to comment
Who it is then no nothing I want to answer why don't you want to answer
it then no it just so i don't want no eh and do you want to answer if it is you like
writes in these chats no no eh i thought you would be allowed to meet
a bit of what stands eh in terms then this chat group go
Eh then it appears on page 420 there and forward eh on page 420 so writes
Mixtape so Danny and Peter Jalla can step know We can refer to where nothing
s no eh then stands writes also writes alias Peter jalla on page 421 bram what
do we if they don't open we'll just fucking the door or is it something you
want to comment no is you who has written it wait a little nothing to
comment We have closed doors here something in chatter no no what do you think about
What is written in chats then no no comments no
Eh since last week so eh was heard Danil and there he has then under
The preliminary investigation told us that you have done this together that you were there
in Jordbro together and that you eh went to this residence and and shot is
that something you want to comment no just that this is not right I did not shoot
So okay you want to develop it no okay so what Danil says that
is not correct no it is not true that I have shot no okay what do you have
done then no not shot you have done anything else nothing i saved on
No there is some reason for Danil to find this in terms of your
In involvement Nothing Reply to No Okay I think I will release it then
Then I thought to have some other questions yes partly found eh traces of cannabis in
Your urine is true that you had taken it I nothing to answer okay you have
any explanation for that there was in the urine no no
Eh and then we have taken in some other material from this iPhone mobile then
Eh i thought you would have the opportunity to comment on it eh partly from snapchat
so you can see then that you have sent out a message about eh that yes if several
people to several people about a rush etc. there is something you want to explain
No because that does not apply to this event so I think you might
Still want to talk about it no I don't want to why not then forgive no I
Want not it okay and even then there is that you
sends out a question that you want to eh have a rush is something you want
finished so began to start with the questions please yes thank you I was going to start with
a bit like this as my colleague with background and so I was going to start by asking
you a little how you feel if you feel danny and
Daniel not actually the first time I actually see him and this one
the person in this courtroom I have never met them before and I
will yes start from there you have never met them before no actually not
ever no okay eh but i can say eh fact that they live in the same area
like me yes eh yes it is not so surprising there are many who live in as
the same place and so eh it is very possible that one can have each other on
social media but never met so yes yes it was a bit if you take it
precisely considering that you live in the same area you have never met at each other in
the area and so no there are many living in the area I know and
feel but he is definitely not my age so that is no one I feel
Personally No NO Do you know if you have any contact at
Social Media eh no I no actually I would just
say of what I have seen in the investigation so I know that I have had
him on snapchat m but there has not been a further conversation there
Are you talking about Danny now or yes that's right it's Danny you Danny have you
had contact with on Snapchat Danny I have had yes if that is the person who
is behind the snapchat account I have had on my snap then I mean it is
lofgren it is l yes yes exactly i have had that person on my snapchat but
there is no one that I know or have met you can add the person on
chatting and besides, I have had questions read to me if I know one
person by that name instead of asking have you chatted with this alias for
I only know of some aliases in this preliminary investigation as we want to say
username that I have written with on some signal and that is what I feel
again in just that but i just got the question you feel this name person
By that name and so you say you show a picture then like I should recognize
But I actually do not and then you have also asked me the question yes but we
know that you have communicated with each other but how should I know that I have
communicated with that person but you don't even show something like alias or
Name or so on yes in terms of technical evidence so I just have
seen now in the investigation when I got to see the tatters so thought yes but it was at
Contact about it now that you have read the investigation then there are some of the guys
As you have then seen that you have had contact with what did you say again now
Have you read the investigation and then I wonder one of the guys sitting here
Dani or Armando then or Danil have you had contact with any of them on social
Media ehm hard to say etc. you can develop
It is you kind eh I do not know directly what is behind which accounts
or whatever it is eh i know i have chatted with in a group chat that i have
participated what I have already acknowledged that I am Diner
and gs on signal yes eh, that is, I have chatted with alias called Peter
Jalla I have chatted with an alias called ehm, ie doo kk and they
other two aliases found in that group but i have never met i don't know
which ones are behind it or whatever it is that apply I
Takes El Hamilton it's something you recognize
No no mixtape who is there no idea i don't even know who is behind it
alias but it has come to light that I have received many chats sent to me
of that aliaset eh, that is, it has sent lots of member to me I
cannot answer why or how the interpretation applies to that person who
have written this to me that is, he has sent me messages
But I have not responded to some announces and besides, I do not know
What I have answered so it is very difficult for me to explain the interpretation
and what it is about because it can give a picture of how you can interpret it but I
with so to do nothing at all no you know that it has been a
Conflict with foxtrot and other networks It is normal there are the news
every day so there is nothing new no no i but sometimes i can say i
sat a pretty young last week where someone said they had never heard as
Foxtrot so I have to ask the question to you anyway no exactly I have talked about it
But I have no acquaintance with it or neither any connection to
That no
Ok so you have no contacts that you know are active within Foxtrot EH not by mine
So know no but my contacts on signal so they have some profile pictures
that can be perceived that but no one I have chatted with it may be possible
that I have a GSam group chat with them like these big group chats like me d
The Gems the same contacts it automatically become a contact one does not even need
have chatted or had something with that person to do okay no I understand
But if we take you should approach then this event that you have heard us
Talking pretty much about an event in Jordbro What do you know about
the only of what I have read and yes looked at signal yes and tell you so much you
know what who have you found out the signal or when have you found out what
v tell you as much as you can, so I have only got I have received some things
Sent to me and then I have seen what has reported as on news
After what happened happened eh so yeah have you been involved in some way eh no
Actually not the least way no I have not been n in any way
involved in what has happened no so you have not received any
information about what should what to do in the evening n 14e eh no i have last
The last thing I wrote eh on the night it was at around 20 o'clock somewhere and
It was when this group chat eh go ended yes that I want to name it and
It was the last time I wrote so yes I thought we'll come back to it
here go chat but if we think earlier on the day where the 14th had you heard
Something about that there would be someone that there would be any shooting then
No any shooting taken over no not the view I had
No so then you have not been involved in any way it either I guess no
we the incident not neither BETE eh so no no you have
previously self -read or sent ads to recruit to
Shootings no I don't recruit someone to shootings no okay
No you how do you feel sinida and emir them who
were here the plaintiffs eh i should explain briefly why eh that message has
been sent by me to Doo at KK on what regarding signal eh that message has
first sent by another alias in the group chat go eh I just want
So just as well as putting out that the chat itself, there are, like times that
does not match the time stated in the group chat it wants
say that there are certain times that a mobile phone has received it
So the message so I want to before that D MED as this alias
As I want to name as Abdi that I don't know who is behind that aliaset
have sent where it is the address and from there it has been sent long before
I would like to say around between 40 39 somewhere where 1740 17739 Eh there has it
been sent that message and from there I had been aware of it and so
had I seen that that while would disappear and then I got a chat by man
wrote to me that you wanted like the address you wanted to google you were
Curious and then I had sent it to this delo and I had googled myself
on the two minutes later of sheer curiosity and that is why it stands
that I have looked it up on Mr k mm eh was that address you looked up or
were it the people on Mr k eh it was just the address i searched on so it came
forward so I was just curious wanted to see what it was why it was like man
sent eh then i also want to add that i didn't even notice that
It stood the last one in the messages Deter Meden where it stands
Step I did not notice it that you did not notice at all no I laid
not notice that, so I had just copied and pasted in and I had
not realized it was so kind of message even though i hang out with you now eh
you have received a message with their name and address to you then wait wait
I finished late and you get a message from any completely different person writing
to you and are curious about that address it is true but why then how to
one does not want the message to disappear man has disappear
disappearing messages in some chatter people usually set them automatically
or or just by being used to setting the disappearance message
and then the message would start disappearing therefore I copied I scrapped in
because that person probably wanted to search for it with curiosity and I was
also curious so that then I also googled it how did that person know you
had that then I wonder what did you say how did the person who heard of
To you that you had received that message eh I have no idea
actually it may be very possible that it is a person in the group chat eh so yes
ok so he got the same message as you in the group chat but so had
actually because i haven't even met them i can so i have been in my
housing both of these two days eh I can tough the day before the 15th so I had
passed out for a short while eh on your own it was just somewhere near
The area I have told in my interrogation that it had gone in a immediate area
For make an ATM thing then I went back home and that's the only time
ever has gone out of my home and it may stand straight off by my analysis of
where I have been and so and yes I share your view that you have been
at home i wonder if danil has been at home no they have not been home
with me no okay and they have you been involved in any way in that they go
Taxi from Larsberg No No EH has and when you sit at home there
the evening then eh when is the first information you
gets about what has happened when it is Jordbro eh can you repeat the question yes you
You are at home in Larsberg when is the first information you get what has
Happened down in Jordbro eh that event the first time
i get information about it it was about i would probably maybe someone
Half an hour 20 minutes after I get a message sent to me and then
I see it I look up and google and yes it was when I searched up
shots against residence Jordbro and such things by curiosity eh want to see what it
was that had happened to eh but before that so the only time i have ever searched on
just they yes if it is it was the plaintiff as it was then I had
searched for this with Mr K and googled it was out of curiosity when I got it
chat sent to me so okay and how did you think then when you first have
received in the evening where a certain address in Jordbro and then you find out that it
has become a shooting at that particular address v How did you think around it
Eh quite frankly I can say that it was maybe it wasn't immediately a shock
eh man hill might have some kind of perception it might have
happened something but my view was well that yes I was not so surprised but
yes eh sin like it was a pity it happened yes it was my reaction you ask
any of those involved what happened and why it became like this and so
eh very possible hard to answer yes you do not know other words eh yes it is hard
Answering no question is not difficult to answer you can answer if you know if you
eh no i i didn't think too much about it no okay then so
you the movie that Danil has recorded on a balcony in Larsberg is on it
the floor where you live eh hard to say eh you can see that it you see after all
Like a balcony you see a staircase so I have a hard time seeing if
it is it or not eh i usually don't go out there eh so i usually just most
be in my home and then I go out through another exit in that building so
that I don't know about like this is the same building or not but I see when you
looks out of windows and so it looks so come from my building and because
The police have been and filmed from exactly that is true is exactly where I feel
again that it is my building but in terms of the movie I have a hard time
tough okay eh that I ask that because I wonder
If you have seen them on your balcony before ever no
No and the phone we took out of your hand when you were arrested it is your phone va mm
and is it you who only use it or is it any other eh it can I
not answer why not eh i have had other occasions when i have been
with friends who have borrowed my phone but I would not like to say that someone
Other have used my phone all the time so that I have said as I said testimony to
i have village used eh this phone so more than that i can't s
No and you heard my colleague ask questions to Danny about his GPS
shows a lot of connections just around Larsbergsvägen seven and that is after all
same with Daniil I ask the question to you too you have not seen them there what
Did you say once to you haven't seen Dan Daniil on this close of your home
that you wrote to me that you wanted me to bust so I didn't think so
much i just bust it is quite right that you wrote to you it was
so that mixtape wrote to you and therefore I wonder why you change username
when mixtape tells you and do it eh i don't really know i changed
just names I don't see it as a big deal really if someone wrote to
me brother rename your signal then I perceived it as yes but then
should I rename my signal so then I just gave it who is he in
relationship with you eh no one i know i have no relationship with him
Nothing at all a person you have no relationship with and that you do not
feel and as you previously tell you that you do not understand why he writes
lots of things to you he writes changed your name and then you do it right away
I will perceive you yes it is normal, so you do not need to feel
or have any relationship with a person to BTA a name on a
signal source there so it's not like you know everyone you write with
signal and you are in many groups and
so ok eh session we thought I'd talk
a little about the eh you remember when installing it about in time it stands
that you had participated in the chat called go
Yes it was in signal yes just yes yes absolutely it is signal and i thought
hear with you what what is that chat about if you describe the general eh I
can reply to what I have written I cannot interpret what other people
have written because you might not write it directly to me eh but I
know from what I have written eh so it mostly I think was about some kind of
thing with some car eh so that's why I've written some chats there etc. so that it
But I don't know what else kind of planning it is if I do not open
everything in the chat and check my messages so that then there is a lot
possible that things disappear at my phone so I don't see everything and that
is common with signal mm mm and if you try anyway i am asking you anyway
try to summarize what is this group chat g yes my perception of it
I know it was about what I wrote about it was about I needed someone
that could drive a car so that's what I had it
the perception of someone who had a driver's license who could drive a car that was the only
I perceived as I wrote about absolutely and then you tell me where it was
they would drive and why and there so where I don't know why I can't answer
on it yes but then you had someone who could drive a car where
would the person drive and why I said as I said I don't remember why so I
can't answer why but I had written only what about car and that
now drives and those things like that so they want it to act a driver to a
car it is shopping for a driver for a car just yes I thought we do this then then
that I take out the chat on the screen here etc. eh and so if I should see should just
Must plug in me of course too so maybe it will be easier and
as well as being able to give a little more clear
Answer and then it says like this they give all info brother then you can run already tonight
Do you say then say mixtape and I will say all the message
Am not here I should be clear with now but I have selected some so Peter
Bile and then 418 seated the Tingsen Jalla and where you can step says mixtape eh
And then you answer a little later tamam write n everything is clearly send the address there
they are now you want to tell you what is this about eh in terms of giving about
All info so it was probably the one who would the person who would inform h
about anything i don't know eh then what is about that those people
can do that I have not read because I did not open the chat at it
the occasion I went into the chat after so you see a gap between the
Two meant so probably something has been written in between therefore I wrote yes
but sending address where they are now so much possible that there was someone who
Wanted Pick I don't know what it was for but it was the picking up of something
So that I don't know eh but I have I will, as I said, not completed that I
have written an address or sent it so that I just want to
Clarify
so that the first is about driving any car the second it you have
I read it so no it is so that when you do not open notes on
signal and enters the chat later after, so messages disappear if you have
setting disappearing messages for a group so that's why I have not seen
these messages when on the occasion I went in and I have set it
On something else everyone can set it in their own way how to set up
Disappearing message so I haven't read that chat where they stand there
two people eh with the tag can step what did you write what did you put in for someone
this kind of eh time for disappearance then what did you say what did you put for time for disappearance
said i eh i don't remember i can have set it in five four minutes four
minutes yes very possible five minutes you can set it how you want to yes it
do i know but will it not be difficult to be in a group chat if one sets
that messages disappear after four minutes yes but it is not I read after all
Not I don't see when things come in or not I get notes on
my phone and when i open and go into the chat then i know if i read
Or not so you don't see who has read what you can press
some chat and then you should see who has read it but I have not read it
the message what does it mean that they can step then what did you say if we think
to ignore if you have read or not what does Peter Jalla and Dani can
stepping apparently do something but I don't know what so the word steps
does not have to mean to go and do any shooting or so may
mean whatever it is like saying yes but eh i want i can do this
we should do a job or step forward can be anything so that I
Can't answer it really and then I wonder why should you write
eh why which address is what you send
ehm hard to reply to eh no eh I hope not what address will you send
Ehm yes I have said this by sending address where they are now eh
It would like to say where they are because they have certainly written to me wad they are
the people who want to pick yes and and Peter Jalla and Dani as this trade
If they are with you or how yes hard to answer that
Yes and then comes Peter Jalla who writes Bram what do we do if they don't
Opens we shall Panga the door or and then the mixtape answers slide from the box then eh
What is this about eh I don't know I can't interpret what others have written
I have tried to interpret as much as possible but I can not interpret I understand
not really because I what part is what you think is hard to understand that
Others write it does not have to do with me to do it is nothing like me
writes so that I don't understand it and I don't interpret it then don't read it
Yes but i don't read what i don't interpret it it is not me who has written
that so I can't interpret it to it no okay and then I think for this is after all
I think maybe I'm pretty central parts of this two guys like that
many you can take as possible no children only if it goes well today brothers I have
More tubes for your Danny and Delo What is it about ehm I
will s straight of the first one I write as many as you can take as possible and that
where eh it is as I said when I meant by a car because they wanted
Someone who would drive a car and so as many as you can take as many as you can check out
who can write to someone who can drive a car that you driver's license that can rattle an
car simply that was what I was referring to with that message since this with
That if things are going well for Erik this today then I have more so all that
the message it might be whatever I f didn't understand what you were then or
what it was for the thing but that customer was something they would do
obviously but i didn't understand what it was so it doesn't have to be either
something criminal so that I do not perceive it
nothing criminal it remembers but you do not remember the view I had
No but you but how can you know it if you don't remember what did you say if you don't remember
what it was for rushes how do you know it was not criminal then eh in order to
I usually write there is a rush and then it usually is not so much as
have with criminal do it okay eh and then I think like this eh in the balcony
Easy access from the ground floor what is the balcony to get they will access
eh obviously as one has written about something and then I have just placed
Questions about whether you have if there is access to a balcony I have for sure
just wondered a little i don't know yes but why do you wonder about the balcony in again i
have a hard time responding to what I can't remember
No and then you write further since you do not have to crush the balcony man
pushes in the glass and jumps in just tell me what is it about I
can't answer why I have written it but I can answer that it is
have not been able to answer it so then you write about any other eh car is needed to
my kids and then answers ask abdi eh they can run eh and then you answer they should
be able to unite the kid knows how to handle gat what is this then this with that
I write car is needed eh then I write that I need implementers it was
It's all about and then to my kids yes kids can be anyone I
Know so I can't say that I am referring to these two I can refer to
Anyone eh then to go down there and then it is written as they can
they drive eh then i meant if they could drive a car but then this with one
the kid knows how to handle the street and so there was just some comment to
obviously I got the idea that someone knew it so that yes I
Don't know I can't answer that last message no what does the means
that one kid knows how to handle g hard to know I will not remember
Why so you don't know what you've written about eh won't
Remember brother lives the hustle they live near no they live on lidingö then do you know which young it
is what eh is what they said they ask if they live near eh they ask for sure
If the person he is referring to then I say no then lives at Lydinge that is
the information I had about any person who lived where I said will
Don't say who it is referring to but I can refer to anyone but I want to
have to whom it refers to I say that it refers to Danny and Daniil and
then i wonder v why who is referring to if it is not Dany danil eh hard to
say why is it hard because I can't think of who it was me
were referring to for this chat was not even up to date at the time of crime or
later planning this this chat that was deleted eh it was not even
up -to -date when I was not up to date in any execution of what was happening
And then then this address will come, etc. Eh that I have pointed out now
are you waiting eh and then you write i will call my driver now have to know where mine
drives and the kids pick up the car from they cannot ride municipal it harage with
cameras and then tell me what is it about in relation to it
This address yes I have said earlier it was about a driver so therefore
did I write a driver because I had someone who could drive any car to
that they did not want to be seen on any cameras simply I don't know that it was
I wrote because they didn't want to go municipal to any place I remember
not what place they would go to and then when they sent this address it
Earlier and then I just wonder why k What kids are you why they can't go
Municipal eh yes obviously there are probably some friends that I had someone I
don't know hard to remember which one I was thinking about
said eh then writes mixtape oh no brother
municipal will not be me I solve bolt in the worst case otherwise one of
The kids drive you write eh and then you write also leave the car and and they step
in eh they can no drive on large roads aina can stop those there
Do you want to tell me something about this n n I can see that it is about the car so I
don't know what about it is about mm
eh and so you write the change of clothes were here and mixtape answers but they
have own only blacks somewhat easier and you answer they have their own dressed on late
now who have clothes who have some clothes on which
I want to appreciate maybe two hours and then I have not been up to date at something
writing I have not been up to date at any of
the other people who are defended or something of the event we
Will return to it late yes exactly but I just want to point out
that and then you write like this and this
do i really want to hear you explain now okay bera press they get to go there do
the rusen s ride somewhere and change and burn old clothes
Explain yes I am a wore something where any comment I Leaved there so I
Do not remember it was safe for one to shit in a thing and make a
other things there were just lots of things I had commented then I haven't
remembered why it had written so but yes I don't have much to say about
It no but if you translate this into Swedish then it says that okay
there is no printing apartment then they can go there and do the rush job I can
Don't interpret that so no but I interpret now so you have to wait eh and go somewhere
and change and burn old clothes it is a straight pretty it gets
Translation to a little more Swedish and then I wonder what to have a printer
apartment to if we start where you can use for different stuff but I would
not say that I meant so I printed is probably some slang word that I have
written yes it is a slang word for printing apartment and pushes positions it
is in your opinion yes and what is your view then I cannot answer
that but now you may well give you but you can be different things it needs
not then it may be a place you want
be on too that doesn't have to mean it but it's your your opinion
and your interpretation my interpretation is not the same has found out your interpretation but you
Have so desperately difficult to give your interpretation I try to give you all
chances to tell yourself but you don't answer it yes I can't simply
reply to the message I don't remember so much of it then
so they are going home and pick up black clothes and put their clothes they have in bag and
take voj tell me what is this what is it
If can't answer it simply no
Eh then it will mean from Abdi they may take a taxi to Jordbro after the yep
Simple so you say the yep my view it can be about what
preferably so I can't answer that and why should they then how should they how can
you tell me they will throw everything and their signal will be erased I
Don't know I just wrote I just wrote that they would make them come like
Remove SAS apps and so on but then they were they then did it or not it was
not on mine on my call or as one would say
so i will take everyone out and erase the group is it you who yes it was
anything I did is the you who created the group Eh no I have not
created the group but I was going to delete the group for my phone eh but when
The group was created I do not remember how it became so that I was an administrator
And then you can change and take out who you want you can do anyone
have not answered him so that I can't see what I have written but just so
that we think right here now you mean seriously that all the means that exist
from mixtape to you he has written without you responding to a single that
is a chat of course I mean seriously that I cannot answer it he
writes because I do not see what I have answered so with it so I can
not I perceive that there is some chat that I write to with him I see
after all only a few messages he sends at spaces and spaces I
Don't know what I have answered so I don't know what it is about but are we
agreed that you have answered eh I cannot answer
it because you don't know or because you don't want to answer because I don't know no
well then i thought we look a little this one and what you are just right out on so
Ways that we have only one party and we all have that for it to be erased
that will shoot someone but do you have any other view yes I do not know
It might as well be the chocolate yeah how should I know jappa people scream jappa
All the time I don't know I can't answer that no, it's clear that
may be so yes it may be candy he can mean candy he can mean it i
serger, as I said, I can't interpret what another person wrote to me for
I haven't responded to the message you haven't answered at all I don't know if I
have answered to or not that no then we go down it a few hours later
eh okay best brother thunder okay thunder brother check with the brother they are 100
What guys are it you have which ones you have checked with and no idea i
do not have I do not see anything that I have answered I can
not respond to another person but have the other clothes themselves
that they can switch to is someone you want to comment on it in some way don't know
I can't answer no eh so Mixtape writes send address and
Lars Bergsgatan 11 to Jordbro and then I wonder why he sends it to
you ehm i'd probably say i don't know simply i get it sent to me
But eh I can say that I think he may have sent to more than just
I for those who are relevant to it it was not relevant to me either so that
there was nothing that was booked to me there was nothing that I was going to so that
I just trave that he sent it to multiple people yes it was going to
Dany and Daniel for it would be Dany Daniel who is going to go in the taxi so
that but no idea no has any connection with it says he wants
An address for picking from you can't answer that
no eh and then then 21 and 27 eh yes the tabs
there in five min as soon as we drove yes my guy has shown and then I wonder
To you that someone has told him that he
Have murdered Emir that is what it is about this eh and then so pray to tie to
Your guy should check how many you shot who is your guy I can't answer
That no
And almost a little later it is between me to say there is between between where brother
Rename D Signal to do Group EH you have told you already that
You change your name Only someone tells you so you change your name on
Signal mm eh
eh and then so 23 and 27 want to know where the tabs are fucking their mothers for
Hunge what is it why is he so angry mixtape
no idea eh i got, as I said I will tough he that person has for sure
Sent many messages to me that I just read you didn't answer I know
not why he writes so obviously depends why would aa
does he send 0034 to you eh do you have any idea what you sent
mediation before the no I know may not be that you have sent a
film to him that is about where Danil says Aina came the second we started
smack no i will point out i have never seen that video for even i
saw the preliminary investigation so no that is not right
Okay then I understand and now I'm going to look at the signal
and first it is session or first is signal but then it is session eh i
know your attitude i intend to set some anyway
Questions based on my statement namely that it is you who has this session
the account and then you can say if you want to comment or
not yes eh when you fixed the settings that
the pictures remove with fast eh be blacking remove the swing it stands
away me snapp keep in touch with mixtape
Based on this is the you who have sent I have
not written that the only message I would like to point out as I
have sent it is the one at the top who had with signal jajamän so yes I
would also like to point out that it has chatted before and it was valid it
the address with the fact that you wanted to google a bit on it and it was long before so it is
the only thing that has written that is with session I have not written anything over
that no and do you agree with me that it looks like
that any person knows how Danny Danil sees
out hard to answer i don't know no i can't answer that you hold
with me that it looks like there is someone who is also involved with mixtape
That you seem to be mixtape seems to be a common contact here eh can
I don't reply to it it's not me like
writes and then someone writes here as the bolten it has now gone now or that
seems to be someone who knows they are going bolt it's the rain number you sent
it a coincidence too, as I said, I have said I do not know what it is
I can't answer it no if they stop you say your clothes you are going to sleep
over with a friend n you change with you earlier wrote in the one where you were
because it was you so did you write that they would pick up clothes and have bags
I wonder again is not you who has written this it is not me like
Writes no late
Then send a video on everything you have before you are going to move and step send when you
lonely in the car eh and then wonders
me you have we have secured a movie in your
mobile where that from within a car do you want to tell us how it that movie came to
you i f many v movies and videos sent to me i have so as
Said so I have taken out of the tion of my phone so you see mass with
Pictures of where their weapons and stuff but there are things that may have been saved on my
Camera roll as late as this video I probably got it
sent to me eh so i know don't come won't remember who or how
It sent but i usually save videos that are sent to me mm mm but it
am not me who writes that no and it is
Yes then it says 2148 Send better and longer video on all brother 10 seconds
showing the revolver and the other two brother not three seconds but it is not you no
No okay then we've talked a bit about that soran
South it was you in that it was you yes I show that I am yes what good then
am i on the side
610 then it is at 2027 and this is after this 2026 that you talked
So much about
eh we can well look as San writes to Dan Chilla then in
Ask the driver about goose is it you who have written yes
obviously it is me who has written that then I have for sure
written yes but ask the one as a driver it was as I said that it was about
something about a driver eh obviously there is something with any drug with goose
It is usually a slang to smoke any joint eh it was safe for
that he wanted the one who has any person driving any car that may have
someone smoke with it it is obviously what it is about so and
How do you know he's sitting in a car eh we chat for sure
writes that person yes no what i write what do you then do nothing soft
In the car something like that where you might snap hard to answer yes it is just snap
We are watching and the first first first mediature is chilla then in the car and
Ask Driver about Gås How do you know that there is a driver in the car as well it can
be yes as I have said the one who drives a car yes I understand but that you know
that it is a driver it does not depend on it is not that it is because you
A few minutes earlier the guys put in a bolt from Larsbergsvägen 11 no that
have nothing with any bolt to do okay and then then 2036
Eh do not take them the kids it is quite similar to what you wrote before you
not with any car to do eh or you can have but that it I mean it has
Not something with something else so you want to see I have certainly written off but take
them not the kids he probably obviously have written off but that
Is there here and this we have this I have solved this and but then writes
I certainly do not take them these kids it has nothing with any other form
of perception that you have okay eh why should you remove each other here
Eh i don't remember it there are long intervals they are sent there so i know
not what removes each other here i don't know what it is all about and then
yes eh there on session what is it about there I can explain very clearly that
eh it is found in my this analysis where there is a chat between me and one
vsto eh as to this as well as the short session conversation where it
Stands that I have seen the tire of type 300 seconds so I would like to say that
It is certainly about sending accept messages for the question
or so that is what you had
with ok so you sent to Dany that he will remove you on session you are no
I had written there send it means I add a person on this app
Yes and then maybe that person sends something to me and then he writes
something to accept a request for messages it was just that but that
where we have not had any further contact on the app as I said I usually
not use that app so much no but it still seems like you say to
eh danny to remove something should take a sport on session in any case and that tube
you is it should i perceive it is so i should perceive anyway it is
gap between it is snapchat It may have been more messages in between so
I can't answer what I know just that it was about eh that on
session just send you to accept the message for
the question but you have sent something to him on session eh surely I who will
Send type like this hello or something and then he gets up where it is unknown
the mean for the question that he should accept or send any message
FAK It's the same that if, for example, I have written to you on signal or
On Facebook on Messenger then you write something and then that person should answer
and then it must be accepted that a conversation should start so it is
it is about that is what it is about okay then I understand
eh you you change eh signal to sino and so mixtape writes that he should
Create a group I only take two members from the one it stands so shot about two
shot and then stuck or then and then three tabs and no one died
Eh it is a newly created group that you join in and four minutes after you go with
in it so do they come to land what is it
If don't know it is not me so I have not answered or written any
messages in the group chat I was admitted eh but I have not answered or
Written it
eh If I ask you this with Dinero never you who have Dinero
eh on
session then we leave this eh then I'll just ask you
Finally Crime Scene Investigators What is the thing you know that eh it
there so that eh no I can point out that I know that this has been found in my
Phone but on Instagram so several can be logged in at the same time and write
At the same time and I have not written that where I usually do not do that account but I
have had it it is true that I have had that account on my phone but I
will vod it is not me who writes there eh even at
the occasion it is written there so I was not even awake so that I was lying
actually and slept at 1541 yes I became about active on my phone around
16 time so I usually sleep around in the morning and day so that
Eh when it says late eh at 15.43 if you need more info about the earthwear event
so beat m a pling there is someone else who has been logged in to it is true that is
Not me who writes I have shared this account with other people but eh as
said it is not like sharing a signal contact like this is just that
Using Name Loss Words And I can't answer who I have the account
with but I know it is not me who has written it since another person we have
one has movies from the young guys and another person
eh should you be able to call i have no idea i can't answer that i don't
have written there thank you then i have no more questions thank you very much fida wine you want
Ask questions yes I have and I wonder Kingen if the prosecutor can get
a page Poster or if I will be what I can take bbag just say the page yes but then is
Page 422 first there yes hey
Sven here is this group chat go and then I have understood that you you agree
that it is you who write here from L GS yes and you got a question from
the prosecutor before around this medium that is actually yellow here guys so many you
can eh as many as you can take as possible and so
did you say if I perceive it right that it is something about steering a car
was it right about what then can you repeat the question that it is about steering a
Thus, a car is true that many you can take so I sometimes say yes but
Check as many as you can take as can solve this or can solve it and then meant
I simply a car and what does the continuation mean there then no children just yes
It means that I do not want to have no children who can drive a car
You can't you can't have children driving a car so it is, after all
The message okay It does not mean to shoot as many as possible but
No children yes your view may be something else but I share
not what I share that it is about a car and there should be no children who
should have for this car it is about a driver okay because you can after all
messages that are on the page before here as prosecutors want to scroll up that D is
Not you who writes but but where Peter Jalla writes then EH should we only pange
The door or J Ni Panga box and mixtape write in the box from the box then
If you agree that in this context, it sounds like taking as many you can
But no children that it is about shooting no I would not perceive it
as the same context because then I would immediately replied that I write it
where the medium about a minute after and it was a comment about something else so
no okay yes so I don't perceive it as the same context no so then have it
fallen away something about steering a car that you needed a drive or
something yeah have okay yes eh you late so i thought on page 423 here in
Proof eh so you got questions from the prosecutor before about this as you
writes the balcony easy access from the ground floor and so a little further down eh so
stands what you do not need to crush the balcony you push in the glass and
just jump in eh i i don't know if i perceived your answer what what do you mean
Here when you write this way why were you interested in this eh
With the balcony yes there were questions about eh something and then I had commented
a little eh I don't remember exactly why it was written but it was small
comments about a place so I don't know why or how so I can
not directly answer but I know there was nothing about that era
perception where no i can't answer what my view is you write
explicitly you push in the glass and jump in just what do you mean by that
Do you remember that today I can't remember that I can mean something completely
otherwise it may be anything but I can't answer what I meant
don't remember it is quite explicitly what is here what did you say
It is quite explicitly what stands here you agree with what one should
pushing in and jump in yes so clearly yes but that I understand but I can't
say that I share an opinion that you share that there would be someone reach
type of deed or so so I don't remember so much of it late
Prosecutors want to bring out page 368 in
proven eh and so the last two messages about man
can school down to them eh now you have said that dinero it is it is not you
Without this, Possession is then as Dinero writes eh but
Eh question is really like this because then Dinero writes you into the house and
Do not shoot outside it is, like a little in line with it like Dinero GS
So you wrote in Signal chat go a little earlier in the evening you agree
that no so it is not me who writes on that app so that I have
not written that and i don't agree that I have said that that
only is as I have said that is what applies with signal so it is a coincidence then
that someone who calls themselves almost the same as you on signal thus Dinero here
at session writes that one should go into a house and do not shoot outside at the same time
as you have written on signal that you should push into the glass and jump in thus
It is not at the same time where there are two there are two yes there are two different times and
Then I also want to say Dinero is not an unusual name it is quite common
It means money in Spanish so I would not say it is random that
or that it is no coincidence I can't see it but I can see that it is not so
highly likely that it is the same person no for many can call it so that
Depends yes, of course, many can call it it I understand but in
the context so it sounds like it is like about the same plane as it
written as a friend I would not on no I would not claim friend a little like that
is written as in chat go where you go away that you have written that you should jump in
At the same time as yours down and writes like this in session it sounds a bit like the same
plan no I would not say that I have not written that you are going to
In any house and shoot I have not written that what is written in
session so that no I would not perceive it as the same context and
It's so long intervals in these times so I can't say that
am i no okay thank you i stop m thanks so much r hf have you any questions some
get left only you have answered a lot now that you hear what i say m yes what
good you can say if it is hard to hear I was going to start with this
After all, we have looked at it a few times where you see the plaintiff
name and address yes ehm and then just because it should be clear you say you
had searched this because you were curious and we know you have printed
On Mister Koll link ehm what is it exactly you searched on will
you remember that eh I remember that I searched at the address regarding the people etc. and
then i had searched eh on just these as well as google man google it as
You have copied and then I google it and then there will be a link and so
If you press Mr Call you see the person so it's just I wanted to see who
it was mm okay but but v what did you write into google just so that it is clear
did you enter the names you had been allowed to send you or the address eh I wrote
only the address okay etc. yes but it seems to be true with what is in
The phone also since I follow the prosecutor's hearing I should say so that
I have put in some questions so it could be a little bit strange order about it
jumps but then everyone understands why I was going to ask you this balcony that
You have recorded a movie on EH that says reply Larsbergsvägen seven do you know
which which balcony the balcony the police have filmed from
Do you know which balcony it is yes what I recognize it so I
Don't see I don't usually be on the balcony itself but I recognize that it is
my area where I live and I recognize that it is building etc. and then is mine
Ask how to get to the balcony I can I know so I think it is
That you go up and then you have to go straight out in the corridor where I live and
So then surely you so so swing out a balcony where it is a public balcony
yes exactly it is no balcony you go through your apartment tk no no okay
And do you know if you say you don't usually be there but how common is it to
that people are there at all very common there are many who usually go hanging out
where there are many people who usually be where people go there because that is
the purpose of it is to be able to go there and and be able to smoke for
that there are no balconies in our apartments that we live okay etc. and then
usually there are also a lot of people where there are usually young people it usually is
people there and yes, etc. I was going to ask you too about session eh now we have you I have
received a lot of questions about it and we have eh yes we have received your answers to that
ehm you say you have used the session then even if it was not so frequent etc.
How to choose your name on session when downloading the app you can choose
and so start session It's like s one round as well as one as well as session
If you download the app, you start a session that is, a one -time
use mm and then you can set your name m but that's just the name you
Setting you not setting any email address or telephone num then when you
V has set it so you get a unique ID etc. and then you usually copy that ID: t
And then they add you through what you do not add through the name and then once you have
got id and you get a person so sometimes the person's name stands and then you set
self in what you want that person to be called as well you can change m if we
says you start a new session then as you call if you are going to chat with someone
Other MM do you have the same username as I'm not talking about the user for it
is something else but this name yes the username as in this case
Then the Niro has the same username if you start a new
session or you choose a new no you choose a new okay so for each
chat so you can choose to be called the same thing or anything else one might be called
how much you want whatever ok okay and is there any obstacle to that
Several people have the same username no there is no obstacle
No, since this I have already stated and I think we at least
There is a PM that I showed Sakam Consignment Visis regarding how one has
timed different messages in signal and in session and based on that we have
interpreted it that the time stated the time when a message was received in a
Phone etc. and then the police have then tried to puzzle these different
the cats there is something you want to say about it about this order of time
beyond what I have shown in my case yesterday yes eh I would like to
Make it eh to bring it out on the screen these time stamps I know
Not but it is these stamps that apply in the compilation so several are
times erroneous m eh compared to what one sees the raw material and so it is also
much of what is found in one phone compared to the other is not true
agreed with the time they have come and so there are many gaps in between so that
It is hard to say what time what exact things have sent mm yes
If we say this chat go then or go eh go or go on signal there is going
you you have been with it has been sent more messages than those who
is in the protocol so do you know remember yes it has the mm you sometimes see it as
Empty squares between different meanings Yes what have you been sent pictures or
Message you can you can say why it is Tomar Rute as far as you know eh I can
interpret it as being a message that has not been recreated and so possibly
maybe some picture there but most are means that have not recreated therefore
will it be an inch box okay and how maybe a little speculation from your side but can
you come up with something special that does not exist or or how it affects
The understanding of the chat yes I can come up with something special it is
regarding certain questions and things I have written in relation to connection with
the chat and then I have received questions that do not even have as well as someone
In the case to do in the chat and so I have written and answered that question and
so it has become that it looks like it is in the same context but it is
not mm and then I showed on the screen case production svis that it
has been asked any question, for example, about where people live but the answer Lidingö is located
on top of mm ehm you know why it may have become so there is a pm you have
any other eh point of view why the funds may be in disarray yes yes it is
signal usually be so it takes time for things to arrive i can write a
thing and so, for example, another person can write one thing and then it will
sent them at the same time then maybe the means end up before or after and that is
not always that they end up in the correct order so that times can be random
selected or they can be difficult and set simply mm okay
Prosecutors showed this Snapchat conversation and the first thing I want
Ask you is snapchat what do you usually use it for what what what is used
Snapchat to basically the bottom used snapchat to
chat with friends and write with people you know and people you just have ordinary
contact with and then it may also be that man you have
Contact with so you sometimes wanted to choose how to set up and have your chats
And the chat thus snapchat is built for the message to disappear by themselves
Irself it is so it is called it is obvious therefore so that yes but it is after all
usually for friends and stuff mm and is it both pictures and eh text or is it
Most text it is pictures and text you can snapchat Send pictures you can write
Text etc. I wonder just like the prosecutor because the first means that
Seems to write here is chill then in the car and then I wondered you have you have eh as
The prosecutor may be interpreted in my opinion received a video while sitting in the car on someone
other platform and then I wonder at least if you had got something on snapchat
some picture or similar from a car yes, so maybe yes I remember maybe
that I may have received some snap I usually open people who send snaps
And pictures and videos you open a snap and then you send back and then
maybe it can turn over to chat with each other etc. and how will
it was that eh man says something about for me to
it is you who write what I do not remember now or if you get it to
I think you write a question about goose question the driver about goose which you say
Probably to cannabis how will it say you write about cannabis here
I think it is you who writes it so s so it is probably because
It was about someone wanting to smoke you were smoking for it and
Then I said but ask the driver that you have resolved or so it may have been that
is all about but how do you remember how you knew it because I can't say that
after all no messages about it yes no but it is obviously safe on snap that
I print about it okay so you mean then there are other messages on
snap that not yes that has not recreated it is normal but that oh when I
writing something to you and you write something to me about about the chat itself
Disappear a lot then it is difficult to recreate everything then it becomes one such
The Message of Space so you don't see the whole chat
Okay okay but then i'm done there thanks etc. someone else defends should ask questions
thanks no more questions from they complain no thanks no no then is the company
completed so f prosecutor ask questions yes thought to hear with you first if you want
Start tell us about the event on the 14th or if you want questions from me I can
Great start to tell you first you start yes eh on the 14th then I will help
to convey a car deal in my opinion then mm and reason for that
is because I am basically the seller as I sell cars both
privately and at work then and knowledgeable within the car in the council then so I would go there
help to convey this deal it is not my car I do not own it
But I'll be there and support as well as a friend wrote to me that there is
a car there in Kungssängen you can just go and check it out for it has
Not been able to start I said absolutely I go there so I check and the car go
Not and start then so I get started it uploads the battery eh tanks it
and check that all documents and stuff are in the car in the hand compartment for one
Sales and then my friend writes to me that perfect eh there will a guy
inspection protocols or something that has tubes with the car dealer then eh so this one
The guy comes in I don't know him and eh we sit in the car and will
Start ride I know it should be somewhere in southern Stockholm I have
not received any address or any exact position there and we barely be able to ride in
A few minutes from Kungssängen We are almost on the rot to the motorway there
So he says fuck my mobile has died as can I can borrow your phones
Absolutely no problems and it was then in order to talk to our common friend
eh so he takes the phone where we little buzz as well as a little I don't feel
him so we just talk a little about public things eh we go there on the road
He has my phone all the time he is not sitting and like constant
the chat but he has access to it so he has it by his side i h
I don't have my phone during that time eh so he sees turn off here go here go
there and guides me as well as to the place we are going to eh we come
up to a parking there are two people where eh we go out I like
cheering on them hi hi eh so i stand there with this guy then the other two
the people eh I show the guy that I came with then as well as thought that
explain this with the key it is a little special because it stood in
the preliminary investigation where the police have not succeeded in starting the car eh because it
has been missing any key as well as the key part itself the metal bit there but the car
can be started even with the key it is thus those from that year model has
Like a chip in the plastic piece itself that can be read then is not necessary
metal loop to start the car so I showed him like that
So I was there maybe Max I think we arrived where we somewhere 2110 and
I pulled we kind of 2130 there and sometime during that period I also went away
didn't talk much about the other two people since then I said that as is
Obviously I can go you need someone more so do you have
some more questions as well as how the change of ownership should go to and so
Furthermore, he said no it is clear as I said perfectly and he had after all
Still my phone throughout this time ehm so I say perfectly okay
But then I go like then he said yes but we we book a taxi like this as thanks
For the help I guess something I said perfectly my car was left in
The king's bed you saw that I had paid for a parking there in
Kungssängen It was my car I parked there eh so he says yes but
The taxi is on the road so I perfect you should follow along and we will go back
or, like the deal, should lock what is going to happen
Eh i so i didn't think so much about how the deal should go to it is
after all not my car I am not responsible for the purchase price or sell the sum I would
just be there and help and answer any questions in case that would
come out something eh so he says no but there will then a car a friend to
pick me up and now I don't know if that's the car there was information in
I have left I cannot answer whether it is it or or not as he
mean but he said he no any friend comes and pick me like that
the one who is going to sign the change of ownership and then comes so fine okay as well as
It does not concern me eh he says yes but the taxi comes from this address it
Located a little further down it is just go there as well so will say okay thanks took
My phone starts walking back to or to taxi where it should pick up
me like going a little wrong i don't really find but i found out after all
In the end, well took me maybe a 10 11 minutes and go that distance to the taxi
and eh as soon as i get back my phone then i start talking to
our mutual friend as well and he says yes but swisha lady reach a hundred like it
With you looked there and then, yes it certainly so the lady is she is so on so on
Signal like it's a nickname if you say so eh so I swish someone
hundred assumed yes but it was well for the taxi or something like it was
For the taxi when eh sets me the taxi goes all the way back to Kungssängen and
So after I got back the phone so no message will
is nothing that you have seen so like so far I have not even been able to
get the least little suspicion that something criminal even should happen this was after all
Like a completely normal day in my life thus selling a car for me is after all
Like how to say drinking a glass of water for one for anyone I
do it constantly i always on with cars and car parts and convey
That's all I know about that thing as I have not been there in
More than 20 minutes so it's the 14th what you know is what you can if it yes
just about what concerns this then like ok I understand but you were good eh just
any control question at what you told us now for what what you said told now v
so that I understood you it was this person who went with you from
Kungsängen it was he who ordered the taxi for you I don't know if it was he
who ordered with his name but it was he who arranged so that a taxi comes
and he who arranged okay then I take eh good eh as you understand so I have
Pretty many questions to you absolutely a question I think I put it directly
about it now if it is as you say why have you been silent the whole investigation
exactly I supposed that question would come and the reason is because it
is no secret what has happened to others sitting here in this room
today with their houses or families or similar yes eh you have also read on
Some when you have been out you hear what happens and
Eh I simply have, after all, I hoped that during the preliminary investigation
time that yes but soon it will be up they will be found soon they will
Investigate they do their job they will soon find this third person to and
with when a witness has said he has seen three people at the scene there after
That I have gone in a taxi that you see that I have traveled in, it is not like
investigated if yes but who was this third person then so i assumed yes but that
Coming well in the end now it didn't come out now I'm sitting here today so then
May I talk in a trial where it actually makes any difference but I have
not wanted to say me or say anything about any person who is not right that can
expose me or my family proceed you think it is easier perhaps for
the court to investigate this third person than for the police think you or
I understand the wrong one for the police told me that they have seen them
Have had a witness and so on who have said or so and then I assumed yes
But it comes out well I don't want to talk I don't want to be how should you
say I don't want to expose myself or my family at risk simply so I
Thinking that I say nothing then I understand you I think like this
eh san have you met him no danny i come will choose not to
pronounce me about any person in this goal of my own security and I
Feel free to respond to what you think I have done or not done but I will
not want to comment on whether I feel or do not know or have
met or has not met any other person but you understand that it
will have some significance who you have met and which you have had contact
With I will have to ask the questions it understands you what no
But that I absolutely understand and I think district court must pull their
own conclusions of course i have met two people at that place i
get there with one person and i have met two other people on this one
the parking who it is how they look or as if I know them or
Not so I won't answer but I don't know anyone in this goal so so
a lot I can say okay then I understand who is mixtape since mixtape is as said
I will not go into name no I understand I will not say who it
is but it is a friend of me yes and you your defender took up as one of those
most important parts that I perceive his for I
may probably misunderstand but eh for your defense it was that you have no
criminal socializing okay and and you don't have any such connection to anyone
criminal organization and so on how about mixtape he has it it gets
So he must stand for that because I should not say that I could not in
my wildest imagination if I am to be honest imagine that he commits like this
crime certainly i know this guy he smokes on he can drug he can do
stupidity but that he would sit and plan murder
eh and i don't say it is he either I don't know as it depends
on the investigation but that it comes up that he is involved in such stuff
is yes it is shocking to me as well as yes he is involved in any gang it can
I don't answer no you know or do you want no because I don't know that
Like it he himself stands for then grasps and what about the foxtrot
The network What do you know if it is a network as a criminal
Network etc. Have you have any connection to any idea no you have contacts that
is related to it no and then I also want to add when you mention this
With that they find signal that there would have been some contacts that
have, like log of a fox or f or yes fox interest then general and signal
works in the way that if I have phone numbers in mine in my mobile phone
So the telephone contacts themselves then and I download for example then but
WhatsApp or signal and so on about any of these phone numbs in my
Here may have been numbers that I had there for friends that I felt for
ti year S which then has a signal contact number that is then in my signal list so
All those contacts are not contacts that I have chatted with no but I
understands but it is, after all, you know what after that there is a
A number who have just symbol for the FXST Network M in your contact list Yes
and i wonder again are you involved in some way i'm not involved on
some way no but also when we agree that this is your phone we have
looked at yes and that it is you like ÄL Hamilton on signal it is also correct
va for a limited time of the current date yes etc. during which time when it
Be well when we left Kungsängen that I have seen now should be around 8 8 pm
where somewhere if we start going there he prays for my phone then I get back
here the guy who will put the key on the deck then to hand over it to
you so because it says too with the tatters yes it stood where the key was lying on
the deck but it wasn't him for as I saw it if I remember right now so
he wrote that after I have been there already yes why would the key lie
on the deck if you were to have the owner with you I don't know anyone had well
CY has well used the car, so as I said, I was not so familiar with themselves
The car I don't have anyone to the car I will be at the car and help with that deal and
It was like a yes but see it as a service I have, as they have helped
me before if i'm not available and so damn there is a car part like me
need you can go to buy it for me quickly just yes, of course he has
no one control what it should be used for or what it should be done with it but
it is a car part like it is none it is nothing suspicious so i get none
question marks like n when he asks me it's not the first time i help
to convey a deal no what is it v what is it that is
perceived then it was that I should help to convey a car I will I will
drive the car there and now in retrospect so I can see it as that as I said I
is not a criminal person I have not judged since before I have none so
called span I have no phone interception I have nothing like that
That this whole thing may have been a game to access my phone
to a number that is not how should one say wanted or scouted
or some kind of connection to any gang m so that it may be that yes but
Armando has a pure name because he uses him etc. blame on a car shop
But use the phone number instead it yes so what you mean that this whole thing
the arrangement it was for you to go up there and hand over your phone to
this guy probably a part of the whole thing has been that he should have
Access to my phone yes mm
and if you now meet a guy you've never met before and you leave
over a phone why why do you leave it in one and a half
hour it so there when you say it so I understand how it sounds but
Then maybe already know is that yes but they look up well as you have
connected with BankID and such how smart is it to, as well as connect
to Swish and BankID minute after in the same place it could be
so also that you have chosen to be silent during the preliminary investigation and then waiting
And so reads and finds a story and adapt to the evidence so
could it be too it is a hypothesis that you have yes yes you we
continues forward a little eh he gets the phone about when you leave
Kungsängen M and he has it late when is it when is it you get
back on 2135 30 reach eh and where was somewhere
are you then in this parking lot in the parking lot along with whom with it
the person who accompanied me and two other people we met on the spot
Yes so we are four in total on site and have you signed under owners
the evidence and so then or no I explained to him about everything how
It should go to how it is to be done and everything as well as what he needed help
with he asked his questions I answered his questions and then I packed and
pulled like but then when you describe this either so have
he has driven it too or he is, like almost a little behind if he
don't know how to make a car dealer yes probably so he is like that
not everyone knows how a car dealer goes to either then that I have
done so many are good for the merits then for as helping with and the one who
would buy the car it was these guys you met at the place it or
I don't know yes but you have to know you were just there for obvious
After all, they were involved in the car shop then if they were to stand on the car I don't know
He said they were waiting for someone to come with some car and that
were like people who would come people who would go it was I didn't understand
the whole arrangement my task was to go there as well as explain if it would occur
some questions answer them eh show him yes but like checking the papers there
in the car yes perfect mm and the guys are 14 and 16 and I I
claims that they look like they are 14 and 16 did you think it was a car business
With a 14 and 16 year old I thought, as I said, they would not stand for themselves
the car I supposed yes but someone will come he talked about that some car
further as I said it's not my car I don't know who the buyer is no no so
that you are being asked by OL in and convey this deal understood it was so I
understood it right and he tells you that you should go with a person from above
Kungssängen down that person you lend a phone until you hit were some
guys you don't know if they are the ones to buy it but then after a while so say
you still that now is time for me to sit me and go across the whole town
again how come it up why would you leave there then it has just explained
It is because I went there shocked up so some questions I answered them
I explained to him how he does when this one then the buyer would come to
the place how you do which papers meaning what and the reason for
So was why I couldn't do it in Kungssängen it was because I
followed that in case there would arise any more questions if they should have
some questions at the service book or inspection as I perceived it
Seems like it wasn't the plan from the beginning then because you don't wait
on the fact that the buyer comes I mean it was because I have already explained to
him how everything goes to mm and you couldn't why was it then you didn't
could do it in Kungsängen sorry you said you explained why you couldn't do
It was in Kungssängen it was if new questions arise etc. yes but how
Do you know that there would be no new questions when the buyer well in place
questions from the one who came with me in the car so if he were to come
on something and think that yes but just this how do you do this no but
We go where I follow you and then we fix everything then I will be
completely honest I don't know as if the guy has a driver's license or not so it can
Rollsroyce as well as would be sold for no clue but there may have been no more
than five six 7000 bucks I think they are well there somewhere would you
pick up something elsewhere up in Kungsängs area up in around
Kungssängen Yes Yes It is good that you mention it this thing that you
Talked about before that toy would have stood for weapons then all this so
Here I can definitely understand what it looks like in this context I fully understand
and held and that he has written toy I get very annoyed by
Now in retrospect that you dry toy as a weapon but it is not strange in
the context but that thing I picked up in bro it is a whole other thing that
We talk if you have nothing with the car itself to make toy it he
mean by toy we talk about small chip boox that you trim mopeds and
Motorcycles thus cars and so on toy as well as yes it will be a toy it
Yes, internal slang words then called between me and him and some to in it
the circuit I went to Bro to pick up this chipboard
mm so that I have not brought anything into the car when I have
gone no i understand eh so this toy stayed up in your car on
Bergsvägen just then I understand you I just think like this
Then why don't you go two cars n to Jordbro you should home since why take
Why don't you go both thn and your car down to
Jordbro It is one that I would say it is an irrelevant question how to
Choosing to make a car deal so no I don't think it's an irrelevant
Ask I put it because I think it's relevant and I ask you to answer
The question why do you not go two cars because we go there there will be no deal so
If we go back a car becomes a deal, I take a taxi home so taxi and
gasoline diesel cost it is like it is the same as it is the same same
About you think it really yes what can the taxi cost 3,400 bucks
maybe like it is probably not exactly the same sum but that I usually
not ride two cars when i sell cars i will choose with you it will be a deal
So and either I ask the buyer yes but could I accompany you wherever
Should you or stose a taxi from there as well as that okay
Well then i understand
eh would you pick up something in Farstad on the road or no no Älmevägen in Farstad
no no that address was sent to me or in this group chat when I
Don't know were not meant to me because I had nothing to do there if I should
eh are you talking to them then as you didn't meet very much it was well hello
hello like mm mm mm what do you talk about, as I said, the cold talk so it was
no one like yes hi how are you yeah good i talked mostly to him who was
with me as well as mm and how was it you are at the address pagen 108 then
Eh why prime you don't take the taxi from there
It was not me who ordered the one he said it comes from there then I can
So I should hold on and just cheat just ne but v fuck yes book it book no
no but I am just trying to explain how I reasoned as well as I became
Well a little maybe a little like this yeah I'll just walk now too but yes yes
Sure I understand mm and when you leave
then what do you find out because then I guess then you get back your phone in
any case then do you have your phone yes and what do you get for the means land end then
Nothing it was later in the evening when he wrote this around 23
kind of like this all all they fucks everything something then I perceive as to
yeah fuck the car dealer did not go in locked then like the car dealer did not go locked it
Was that was the way you thought yes because I like I don't have nothing in the whole how to
one say from start to end all that I have been through I have not even
has perceived that something suspicious thus happens in my world yes so out as
Any car dealer I have not been able to perceive something I have not
seen something strange I have not perceived anything suspicious so that he
writes that yeah fuck all everything they fuck all the damn ok boring car dealership
did not lock like it was so you thought yes when did you find out that it
has happened something it was the day after the morning or in the evening eh on
the morning but then I did not perceive that there was something has happened to it
I have done that I have had something to do so under it
the time period if I don't remember wrong now it was kind of a shooting and
blasting every other day so it was like that was all you saw on the news
so that one to shooting has happened it wasn't like this yes shocking yes
was hard like and then as I said he who I talk to when he likes talk
If so he, like him, is as he is if you say so he likes to
Talk about things he likes to discuss I'm not so huge effort like that
Then he wrote in the morning there that yes something about any shooting as I
Don't even remember what I answered and that is it pulled out of such a rough context
When you can only read what message you have received and do not have
answered so it will be I understand what it looks like absolutely I take it
The thing as well but it will be you only have one side of the story so go
you don't put everything together but man I think you can look pretty clearly at
The answers there because he writes that he writes something about reaching about someone
Shooting then he writes something about the car then I will be this way to wait what
Damn now you talk about the car that we sold yesterday while a shooting
And then I write to him what do you talk about so do you talk about that car and
Then he answers there are answers where he writes no brother it is honest I will
Pick it up now so I tokar yes okay fuck f that it is honest it is that it
stands at a company and you talk about it before it also says there is after all
earlier in the chat even that it is honest it stands at a company it is after all
not only that day as said you can't see my answers but I ask after all
him then to talk about that thing is you have something to do then should
No it is honest so in this context it does not mean honest that it stands
at a company without no it is calm as it was nothing I so like
I then interpreted that I would never go with you on something like that but yes apparently so
I'm sitting here today yes Mister Locko is the same with with it I can't
answer why not because i don't want to be the same as mixtape i want
not respond to someone like someone else who does not concern me for my own security then
Do I want to go to yes no but then I will come up with a statement that Mr Lock and
e eh mixtape and so you may have it to stand for me completely
Simply do you think we have gone through about I should ask you when you go
back down and h looking for the car yes just the day after then I can start
At the same time and tell me a little freely just the 15th what happened to eh so that the 15th
Then so we talk when there are chatting eh we talk about the car and that it
Like Knas and so you know as I said he talks a lot so I know he
usually always write lots of shit to me i am it is like yes, of course i
Talk to him and what I am so how should I explain I am very
busy person so my phone is constant as well so that I have chosen to
my notes on all of these social media instagram snapchat and stuff they are
suspended and I go in when I have time but my email and yes but for example
Ordinary SMS that they have on because I always have customers sellers
Buyer I always talk like I'm a busy person so on the phone etc. so
I go to social media when I have time when I have time to play then
I go in there and he writes things sometimes as he writes I go in
just like i just write yes okay sick yes haa like it is none
greater reaction so it is but he talks anyway that evening about
that or that day the 15th that the car is not found and so I perceive
that like having the fuck the deal did not lock but in no way they have not
successful someone has probably come from there with the key on it as well and fuck
anything has happened i have no control over it it is not my business it is not
Like I am not I don't care much if I am to be honest I am not
interested in what has happened but he writes at least lots where set
you the car I explain to him here and there and so they found nothing thought
me but what the hell a car can not disappear as you are you joking well with
me i told him yes but know you damn i am nearby i can ride for car
I check quickly is the one there is the one it is not there so it is well salvaged
I don't know what has happened to the car as now you get to take care of yours as I
I have helped as much as I can I have hero with the deal yesterday
It is not my car like loose it would you get paid for you would
go down and check for the car no and as you say then this with
the money the 14th to eh but if we settle for what we have turned a little there with you get
happy to come back 14 you but there is something that you should get a salmon for
to is a completely different case as I said yeah i am doing lots of things
At the same time I am doing business I am doing
Mellanköpinge is to be sold a tire to be picked up a chipboard
In the evening then as you say I went and picked up that is right I have been there
I have picked up SEK 6500 it has nothing with the thing to do these 6,000 of these
sex and five they were he owed me since before so they were my money I
would just pick up back the 5 hundred he threw well in that as yes
But thanks for the help today as well as nice that you could set up t I fixed a
500 next to like but that's 6500 I have not received for meded one
car dealers on a car worth that sum like that so it is no but you were
good you I think we'll do the same way as when we looked with the wound look
On a few different messages yes then I am now aware of your attitude that
As I understand you right sometime between 21 and
10 and 21 and 30 are you Jordbro This is how I perceive you VA 21.10 to 21.30 so
Are you in Jordbro and 20.00 to 21.35 then you have
not your phone yes but just so we work out it then is it because i guess that
You get the phone before you leave Jordbro yes it is clear yes and then I wonder is
Jordbro No Earth residents then leaves with the taxi yes but then you leave it
Here PusShagen when it was 235 21.35 approximately 21.35 mm
well then we'll
See yes you have already talked a little about what I just me actually blown pretty quickly
Past here but you note a number of such Fox believed logos
Eh i think sorry if i stal just add that none of the alti i
Talked to during the current day it had that picture as no they have
not yes so clearly started there have not kill everyone who is it it is a person mm
I think it might be just me but I think it sounds a bit special
and call themselves kill all what yes it is it it is absolute and that it is a
is on the side it was the cat had written up
that yes i'm going to bring out
It can
look
Is it the one that starts at 325 in proof the day yes between mixtape and Armando yes
it is it thank you so much mm page 325 it starts on and then it is after all
mixtape that first writes yes it is only his with that we can see it so is
the one where he wrote brother take it personally it was the first he wrote
and it is of great importance to what is below it that when he writes
where we don't take it personally now we have big problems right now so it was for
that I he had TFF earlier in the day about lots of shit things like then I became
mad at she I said what the hell is it with you why do you keep on the chick about
here unnecessary things like that and then he wrote an hour later he lazy down
that brother is not taking personally right now we have big problems right now and so on
further and then I want to add this as I said before he likes to
vent he drugs a lot he takes a lot of things that it is as I have
been how to explain as a not safe point but like someone he can
Talk to ventilate with and then you also look at chats that it is such a shame
that you do not see what I have written for if you cut down a bit where it stands
as well as to do mine and then tag it was included in the preliminary investigation
organization he is with that has split yes it any organization
As he is in the JO I understood and therefore I asked which one is this
is your friend it is a person you have a lot of contact with which one
organization is what he is in he is well in any organization that has
split I have no control over which organization he is in no but if I
says this way as it is quite widely known and I have gone through that goal
that FXST split and then Seron Natverket went one way and bridge tver to
the other direction is the foxtrot he is in it, so it must stand for I
Don't know if he's with yes it is clear that he gets but I wonder you know I
don't know no so the others are fat active they step
on everything now after you yeah his mother and this I think is also quite general
known that it was a phalanx that murdered the so -called strawberry mother etc. is
that what he writes about here seems like it etc. but that as I said it seems
that but I can't, like yes, I think then maybe may be
more interesting because then I think like this but brother Allers it you are long way
you that it is quiet m you still do not do with that way so you don't have to be
worried but if people know you are friends with me then they can try to fish you on info
Like and so you think yes then I understand and then we are then and here
Do I know you say it's not you like then eh
have access to this to your phone then mm eh but now we are
2034 Set it on any street before called Pusshagen
If you are at the address of 15 it is written in 2045 and two min 2055
eh if you now when you read it what do you think this is about eh so yes it
Obviously is about this case that we are sitting for here today but
I didn't have my phone then so that it is obviously about
this case as well and acting it I because I interpret this as that it
That would be 2057 roughly that is roughly you agree with me about it
Interpretation Yes how is it then that you are not there for a 21
o10 it is I don't know he he can may mean that yes two minat maybe they
others are there in two in two minutes as we talk yes I don't know
actually no and here it is also when the best would have been if I solve someone
who book taxi etc. Take some good place brother etc. But this he writes to
your buddy exactly and as I interpreted when I thought I can if I can say
that as I interpreted then that they talk about like this what the hell should we do with
Armando now, as well as so he should not take any suspicions or yes by someone
Reason so yes best would have been if I fix someone who book a taxi as well but
just so we agree that it is mixtape that writes this your friend to my
buddy no no no to this guy that you don't
feel so that mix that is your friend writes this to the guy you don't
feeling mm it would not have been better for mix
to talk to you but he maybe who with him too yes but so it both feel
Do you think it took a little more than seven minutes for me I remember going
Wrong somewhere I don't I don't have the world's best local knowledge there but took
well run 10 minutes i guess you went on google maps too no he said he said
Go straight down just okay he said go straight down you got the address so i went straight
down then i noticed where fuck i'm late then i went into google maps exactly so
I went and followed from where I had gone wrong I assumed but it took well yes one
ten minutes for me to go that distance yes what do you remember where somewhere was
you what part of what you went lost was this down or was that up
or no i don't actually remember no for this route where it takes two
minutes to go also in accordance with Google Maps okay it's so there and that's exactly
Follow a road just mm so you got there what I think it was because he said go straight
down so I followed the big road if I now remember right so I went I
Did not go in left I continued straight ahead at where it stands the grass and
Then noticed that I went wrong so I had to go in through the residential area as well
around there somewhere then I understand
mm then we think go to the group chat KK and I apologize that I have where
neglected with not noting eh these pages eh i will make sure eh promise
bot and betting to an upcoming occasion unfortunately it may not be
something like that but i roll forward fast and is someone faster than me
So please tell us if you find K Group Chat
kk on page in proof car team yes thank you giant
395 I thank you so much I think it was if note is true that is true
ready at address and pick up the type 1845 it is also to mixtape or no
That's when I picked up this chip that's when you picked up chip chip the thing
just brother butterfly trail it was in bridge it was where you were up and
Picked up etc. mm then you would not have met this other guy without him met
You later yes
mm eh then towards Jordbro sees exact address but you can pair then in Essinge MM
Eh that was where I perceived that the car would thus that we would s it
somewhere there in the south side as well as mm here writes å in
1758 change car brother then go to another address brother then to Jordbro late taxi
To Essinge pick up parab give it 6500 mm it is he who decides or is it you
who decide how you get in different places I how you go between different
will put them on the keys the tire forward there is any person i guess
don't know no because it sounds like it
Not at all is that you should meet any person without it sounding on this
like there will be keys on the front tire to you etc. eh but then it was
not or the keys were there, after all, when I got there in the car then get
myself from the beginning the keys lay there assumed yes but someone has tried well
Start the car before me they have not succeeded as so they lay
Back put back the keys I go where I will fix the car and he
knows yes but Armando will fix it like that certainly no big
problems as well as maybe a battery that is discharged or how will it so that it
Not anything about any guy you should meet there here it says he
maybe best that we do this so that it is not that I lose away
something in between because it may actually be so so i go out
to and check like this
[Music]
When the Hunga is then calm brother against 26 an in
ajna where tamam tamam five t min will say to them put the keys on the deck
Fut yes brother Ölmevägen in Farstad Yes Yes brother thus
Where does this guy come in 15 minutes there is somewhere I know
not if it is or after but i have read so it is there is i tr it
maybe after that is after you go down after yes after it was when i was on
The garage I remember because after it is after 19 then not even an indication
As I perceive, he had had the car before and then when troubleshooting a car so
Can't you not just always exist yes it is this thing that is wrong you
May go on different as well as although it was well that it was soppatorsk no the battery
was discharged, the battery was discharged too just so I had to put on
the car first and when I put it off it I noticed damn I can't
turn off the car now because the generator must be uploaded I turn it off
So you have to put it back and then I noticed damn there is no soup
in the car either and then I parked it and went with my car because I don't want to
have a soup -in with that car on the way to the garage then mm and this explained
Denim for you how to start the car then mm
Mm and then there will be a lot of message about if it does not think brother
Thoughts a brother gives you pair where are you now go there no he is there if
15 is Ingo in Kungsängen this is where he meets you then no he met me at
Bergsvägen he met you on Bergsvägen he wrote he is there in 15 but he
wasn't there in 15 he was there about maybe 30 35 minutes after he wrote
it mm eh and here it and it just that
nor put toys in then go with this and tanks it full it is after all
up someone or so as I said I went on his instructions so it was
he who said drive left right here because here says that on the hunga it was another
Hunge apparently who does not answer may be another address in the worst case it will be
Another one who goes and leaves at the same address turned a maximum of five minutes etc. did you
that or yes as I said we went wrong we were waiting for a place I mined what we
had with the thing to do what I assumed it was but but now remember in
any case that you were waiting somewhere so it will be sure you would wait
There then understands
me and this it is not something that you have had someone any knowledge of
What it says about the step warn should walk and the other car and so yes
no no i don't have my phone exactly
No when are you getting back the phone 2135 where somewhere prime.se
21138 best take the bag from him and left to the guys what is it it was anton
the med i got when i had the phone then but i i knew that
He has had my phone and chatted with these then the people underneath
What does this mean something about bran and tabs i have no idea as said but
Notes have been suspended and then you notice that the chat goes over after all
Immediately after they notice that so shit they don't have to start not
The cars now what is it not to start any car no delete everything you have written
So there erase for all what did you think about that someone should erase something but
As I said I just want to add again that my notes are not on I do not have
So I haven't read these messages and if I had read them so
Had I not just understood what it means yes they have been talking about
something like that okay
eh the guys you would meet how did they come to the place that I don't know they came with
Taxi I don't know no apparently so it seems that it yours
buddy knows then is that what comes taxi yes he has been aware of it
Mm and here it is not even here it is then with your phone number not with
your alias but it is yes but it still is that is someone other than you yes
Yes he writes someone writes here in your name should fix a map for you eh fixed
that no map do you know it I don't know no he has written has done well
that but what i don't know about it and mixtape writes the revolver is in the car
But this you have it is nothing you have seen no no no no no i don't have
perceived as any weapon should light to the car no and then then it will
was on fucking mum k fucks and all they fucked but it was that the deal
Went in the cast yes so you may think he gets excessively angry man has a
damn temperament so suppose yes fuck the deal did not lock as well as mm
mm remember what it is that you have asked when he answers no they will not
talk i don't actually remember no but that i recognize that kind of
messages it is when he usually talks he likes to make his little own
Investigation as well as when he reads news and stuff so he he is attacked
Think it's interesting with such things like that and I usually just answer that yes okay
like but this is he someone has asked a question since it is a chat
Between the two of you so I think it is you who asks the question
Eh no they will not and talk what are you asked why have you asked
If and what is it that you think will talk i don't know it may have been
Someone followed the question on something he has asked no idea that it
It's not such a message that likes me telling me something about
says so no no and when you get then they had not been 100 they had not shot
What what do you think about it yes I understand that he is talking about any event that
have happened so much I absolutely understand but this is not the first time
he talks to me about any event that has happened so that I have read well
something on the news and so like he begins to speculate on who has done what
and what has happened and so on, as well as even though you you can still agree
If it looks like there is a conversation between two parties here that
you have written something before yes I have certainly written something in or that is
not certain that I have actually written he so so is just one
statement they had not been 100 they had not shot it is none it is nothing
Answer to my question l to any question that I have asked but I cannot
Like memorizing exactly what was written but it has been some discussion and
something that has happened etc. and it was here when he wrote brother the car should apparently
Stay in the area when he writes it right after he has written that there
Up then he writes like then he writes a little parked thus etcetera
Doesn't he hear from the guy who was apparently left in Jordbro when you go
Yes maybe he has done that we do not know yes but quite obvious because
What we have the contacts with you here he asks which phone number you
put the car on here he is down and looking or someone is down and looking yes
But I mean he may have written to the other person before as we
don't know and since he has not remembered or I don't know and then
written to me then other responsibility I do not know it I understand yes and you
would get a salmon then he writes they have probably cod depended on the tabs they had
on it etc. what is it about the same thing as in the morning then as as
Said he is doing well and speculate as usual and ventilates and talks and
Like but here you have to understand that there are some who have got stuck for something
That something criminal might have happened in my world is this
Still a very ordinary car dealership
Mm and then proceeds with how they tagged and they no call before not
touched the n st and parked so fast they are not even so bey are you down
and is it when you are down and look at 18 o'clock exactly when when they write
around the time there so i'm there as it was when I told him so what
Damn how hard can it be to find a car like you have placed
1000 because I am nearby I go down and check out like but no it was
Not when it then comes three tabs off a car for what seven shots in a door yes
one kid comes at last he is minor etc what do you think that
have to do then it starts to get a little uncomfortable I think what the hell so
No if we look here it stands download page 335 download session 10 11
session 10.28 mm last is when you download the yes number around it
Time yes then comes a chat 10.29 with Mr. Loco
Show is that mixtape it may be yes it may well be but is it
I wonder I don't know
No I think that since it was clear instruction here 1028 mm and 10.29
so is the first mean I think like this then
comes it and now we are two days after the deed 17.25 We have the pressure in Haninge
The guy will ride an electric kick that needs a good place but the picture on the car
gets good is there something where you are involved as far as I understand that
does not concern this anything with the suspicion that I sit for here today so I
chooses not to comment on anything if any other v does not comment on it no
Asking it because this is quite clear a criminal character and I
claims that you have one that you spend time in criminal context that you are not at all
is alien to that crime and there to question
I, as I said it is not concerned the case we are sitting for here today so I think
it okay n gets answer it goes well i have none
Problems with it and then Mix writes the 17th and
This has you been up to a bit like this but you are the only one I have home brother
brother i don't trust any people selling everyone right now every day one two dies it
Kna's disaster and everything included in yeps before it was only paired brother now
is it jao m mm do you share the analysis of what it looks like the situation it I
What I understand from this that you can see pretty clearly that he is feeling shit
So if you say so, so he is feeling really bad and as I said before
that I know he takes a lot of drugs he is very much and when taking
drugs in the way you ventilate a lot and especially so you turn
to people who may be yes but as he knows may be able to comfort one on a better
ways, like what we can we can we have we have we can sometimes have very in -depth
conversations also about yes but like yes, so general snack thus he he
want to vent he want to say how it is
Like good thanks so much mm Thank you so much Frida Vallin would you like
questions no thanks i no questions no no questions anton sundberg yes
Thanks so I got answers to most so I only have a few short you you
Have been sitting here in yes a little over than an hour a little more than an hour and a quarter
eh and you have to say if you would need a break or anything
But I think this should not take too long eh yes it has been
A lot of questions about this with the network environment and that claim as well as
I know that you eh I noticed that you moved to a little under prosecution
case request when it was mentioned that you were active in the network environment and on the way
upward in the degrees you just want to comment on the delight that I think
it a statement only that has no reason really I haven't judged late
before like me i have no criminal connections but some network no okay you
are not in something any network no okay and then so I thought we can start with
any clear and clear question at this time did you know that it would
take place a shooting then no no eh like suspect you thought either
Before or below this that there would be a shooting no I had no one
opportunity to even be able to get a suspicion it was like all all was completely in its
order etc. Okay but it is still said that you should be like a yes you are a
the fellow in this is the claim how do you think about it that
is a pity that they have not been able to investigate forward and find even when witnessing
have said that there has been a third person on site there after I went
me if i'm wrong eh then your view is that you would help
To convey in this deal It wasn't you who would sell the car
correctly just just yeah okay and I mentioned the matter Visis here and
You were also in it a little earlier at the beginning of your interrogation here to
You work with cars yes what you can say that I work both at work
So at the hbis company and also at my leisure as well as it is my interest that
is what i am doing it is all i do from morning to evening almost okay
and and just so we understand what like and when you say it says so that
thats all you keep on what are you doing on a daily basis or
Weekly or how to see very broadly, so everything that has to have cars to
For example, do the same day n here you pick up that ECR box or that yes but
hidden no what most people know about it, so it is usually almost
all my friends who have any problem with car or should sell a car or and
so on when they contact me because they know that yes but Armando is in control of
Most of the industry as well as etc. Okay eh so that so if you need help with
something with any car then you may be one of the people you call it is one
Correct view yes okay eh and then so this goal is a lot about
encrypted chats and so this is no secret etc. eh and you have after all
told you that you have used El Hamilton Eh during periods eh and only as not
raw any doubt about this because you might get an incorrect view here
with signal what is it to you that one in the amount of communication apps like me
had been laid down on my phone when the police took it it is like so
As I am interested in cars so I am also interested in yes but different
Programs Some certain chats or some chat thus applications they can
Send larger files download larger files it certain benefits certain disadvantages
You like to try around all that was why I didn't put an extra either
Ask like when he said down session yes what fun it is new app we can
test like mm okay so that so just so that I don't know maybe anybody
who believe it but only we are apparent signals it is something that is only used for
crime no okay without you use it to what extent used so friends
all like it's ok m good eh
and i was thinking like this for this i also know that it was something like you
reacted to so thought to give you the chance to comment on the eh and the prosecutor showed
after all a timeline here when they kept their case over different eh as well as when
chats started by the ended and so there you have some reflections after having
For example, as soon as I get back the phone etc. they create a new
group chat and do they write this continued about this event that is now going to
happen like then one could have thought that but if Armando knew what would
happen what was the meaning of creating a new chat without him then to continue
discuss
crime scene to hide this from me you mean these other group chats late
that you are not in is that are the ones you mean just so we are clear ex yes exactly
and then the only group chat that I was in was called car which is yes is true
Agree with what to do where car I will sell a car as well as okay eh
And but you have told us here you have picked up a car and you have transported
that a Jordbro started it and refueled it and everything like that where it is
the car yes eh partly because eh so this would have been a car deal then quite
Clearly but now they apparently knew that it would not be a deal m eh and
The only reason I can think about it is that they know I am not judged late
Before I have no suspicions on crime I have no so -called SPN or anyone
cops after me or like something that arouses attention they might be thinking
that so at its height that yes but if the car were to be pungent as is so
It calm it is a so -called white driver as well as there is nothing on the register and so
further so that yes it is a rather sensible reason why they have chosen to
use me etc. but I thought you got some questions here from Åkl but I
don't really know as I perceived the answer but why this person
as you pick up then eh why not why not he can just drive the car
Yes yes when we went down we talked a little because we were buzzing I told you that
I had dropped my driver's license this summer eh and then he just talked you fuck me but
I am a driver's license now as well as so it is a pretty big reason for
he can't drive the car eh but then i think there was something behind it
also that he wanted to access my phone but a large part of it all is
After all, he can't drive a car legally on the road as well and that is yes if you
should do such a thing so it is too much risk just because you you mentioned after all
This parking then yes okay and and just to be clear about
Do you leave on foot you said something around 2135 somewhere there right there
somewhere yeah ok eh exactly and then you mentioned you went
through how you got there what you made it eh and but a question only eh when you
have gone thus the taxi stands there waiting for you when you arrive or
As for prosecutors, now this showed a picture when he has produced how long
Time it takes to go etc. Like you jumped straight into the taxi when you arrived it stood
where or how what happened there as I arrived, I probably waited one two three
minutes on the taxi would use okay i can believe because i think if i remember
It was in 2149 so the journey begins so I must have been there sometime 21146
where somewhere something you remember you waited or something you yes I remember
some car would come so i guess that is that car then so it is like
a yes qualified guess on your part that it could be the one that
he then talked about most likely yes okay eh mm and then I guess but only for
clear then you have not received any weapon from that car absolutely not
no no eh mm and in this it includes that
eh the assertion is that you should instruct these people on site
about how to commit crimes and how to escape from there what do you have to say about
that no that I have not done I have had extremely limited conversation
with them it was like hi hey yes how is the situation like okay eh yes so if we should
summarize your story so you have you picked up this car the thought it and
driven in to the parking lot it is correct mm eh and you have picked up one to person
during the trip you've been leaning from in your phone exactly you are at
the parking for about 20 25 minutes something that way mm and eh and you
Not if you've seen it but it didn't look like that when I left the car in all
case no but how did it be out then it was may have been that I put it in
the front seat after I refueled it and then when he got into the car he has taken
it and put that back okay but you said something about any box I have not
seen the one it has been heard about yes and I would put it you think then under
the seat or what did you say yes exactly according to the mediocre i have read so it would
the box lie down by the seat of the seat where I sit and drive as well as
Well you noticed nothing in the car that it was stuff there or something like that yes
It was a little stuff I don't know exactly what stuff it was
Pretty dirty eh you looked at the pictures there so there was some bottle here and there
Like but box so I checked to the back seat I jumped in and
drove like and the other guy sat was next next to you yes mm mm then is
I satisfied other question then of end can only be apparent
After that question you received from the chairman has this box you have seen
This box no no good thanks then I have no more questions good we will then
break for a break take 15
minutes the recording the prosecutor should start by asking questions well yes
Thank you hello you hear me and see me soon maybe we'll see there yes yes yes and you
Got to ask here now eh that you knew what event this applies to etc.
Eh i was going to start with question it is true that you are living in the area certain
is that so yes yes yes eh i was going to start with that you would be able to tell you what
you made for observations eh this evening and then maybe i put a little
Complementary questions after that yes I have told everything actually
eh eh i have i drive i live i go for
my for my house on my car on the street since I was going to go to my wife family who
lives in nara and then leave a stuff there and since i sit in the car i drive on
The street since I heard two shots so it was maybe close to me since I brakes and
since i see two eh two guys running in front of my car
and since they disappeared d a mm okay yes and you said you sat in a car you can
describe where you sat then somewhere in in my car I drive in
my car yes and where did i stand to go where the car was standing somewhere
Ah thus i i close to parking which i actually live mm okay and where do you live then
I live in old pile okay eh but stood the car at your residence or someone
elsewhere no no no on the street actually it is like this maybe it was
close as this event that you happen so you know I was told after after
So I do not know but I heard was close to me near me etc. so
here etc. Okay but you don't know what the street hot like you that you stood on
Ah no so like i goods here old haagen but i don't know the name of
street actually okay but we old garden anyway yes gammelhagen just ok eh
And but you don't know what is relationship with this current home
Yes no i think the left's side as I heard shooting comes at
the left side where i run on this street okay eh i can say old garden
It is the road that crosses this deep Nile that is on that street there
The shooting happened was it on it okay yes just yeah just okay and so said
you that you heard two shots mm How far after that did you see these guys as you
described a few seconds okay and can you describe some eh how were they dive
up and where they disappear
eh they so you know they ran out of my car and since you know I so
So gets mixed in my head what happens what is this shot what
that runs but as they drive in front of my car since it was all disappeared since I
stopped a little I checked it was nothing and since I yes it police
something no actually no idea no no i can't actually see
Them do you see how what clothes they have no it was dark actually mm mm it was
dark so you saw nothing eh how they looked or so no did you see how old they
looked that
be no but i told i think the young ones
So you look at bodies they don't have they are not as adults as you see it I
so at least think I don't know if I'm right or wrong but it was
maybe young because it was their bodies like the body not as marked
They are not adults yes sorry can take the last they looked young yes why did you
that assessment when yes these little coroes actually small bodies
small yes small bodies okay you saw roughly length of them prim crime dse no that
is hard hard guess yes do you have any appreciation
no no that it is hard it is hard to
say mm mm and you said it was dark what did you look like then with the view
How far away in acode they faces how far eh sorry how
Far from you were from them
Type three fy meters all five feet yes and do you remember about what time was
Because with finished thank you so much for putting on testified you want someone
compensation for witnessing
So but then we will start prosecution may ask questions, etc. Thank you hello again
Hi eh i have understood that you are staying in this area eh because you knew which
Event this applied to etc. EH and we have s some pictures of one in a garden and so
Has it been a camper next to me as I understood it is your camper eh and you live
By at this parking lot that the motorhome stood on yes eh then I thought you
would be able to tell in your own words what you did for observations this day
And so maybe I ask some questions after that yes I had a little trouble to
Fall asleep so we were this Thursday evening I was
want to remember so I fell asleep t over and then I woke up right after then that I
heard bangs they were sharper than
fireworks I up and look and then I pulled up and look out and so yeah
Then I saw two people moving in the garden
Who disappeared went right fast and shortly after that, the police came
try to recount here the police but then I thought they were in the wrong place against
What I heard the bangs from for direction so then I called them and
Tips I think that down there is something has happened and then came a police officer
And then we went around and look so I could point out where they had touched
sig and then we find some weapons under my car
Also mm so it was all the whole thing mm
eh and how long after you hear these bangs did you see these people
about three four minutes maybe mm okay and then you saw the first time yes
After all, it was three going through the window yes and where in the garden they were then up then
at the trees and for us who have not been there you can describe what is here
The trees somewhere they lie out with the blockstone road etc. Okay so that it is
Like a spruce hedge etc. Okay and do you see what they do in the garden no it was dark
and hidden they were well -clad so that it was hard to see mm okay and what
How far from about would you say 30 40 m okay eh but you don't see what they
do there at eh at the trees then as you described yes they took well through
The bushes just ran on I think okay ehm and saw you you said it was
dark and that they were dark -clad you saw how they looked otherwise no the only thing I
could read out really it was probably colorful shawl that they had around one
had around the face etc. what was it for shawl then s a type rastafari color okay red
green yellow what did you say a red -green yellow okay but was it like a what was it for eh
garment a type of scarf scarf that was wrapped around yes around the head okay but
nothing else that you saw eh did you perceive any age at
them no but i thought they looked younger anyway mm and why did you do it
the assessments it is the movement pattern okay but when you say younger what is
for the type of age then younger than 20 okay but not we can't say more than so no that
is very difficult to say mm eh you have received some questions about this in police interrogation
Do you remember what you have said then yes it is a long time so yes I understand it but it
is nothing you can remember eh what you said i can only read it
then fast ehm it is a hearing then held eh on November 14
eh and then it is on page 428 EH and then the police ask then you would be able to
Appreciate the age of the guys and so you say no younger than 13 to 14
Eh after 16 so you start to get a little more determined in the movement pattern and so say
so much yes hello ronnie we said hi outside too
And you know that H will think back in time now until 14
September wait now they are not from SIS
Then Ronnie then I thought you should think back to the evening and then tell
for the district court for the district court has not read anything so they do not know what they what
you have told the police so I thought back and tell the district court v
What was it you saw this evening what I saw was that I have gom
The microphone also excuse so we hear you really well so mm
Eh yeah yes i would or me and my daughter would go to icamaxi and and
Thought we went out to the parking lot then I saw two yes pretty
young guys standing there almost just opposite my house etc. with bag where eh de
Yes i never seen them before they stood there only and kind of looking at
something or yes then yes it was no more than that I
waited for my daughter for her to come and then we went to the car and then
Was it a car in the parking lot that did not belong to yes the neighbors who were there and
I stood the farthest yes in the parking lot in the corner of an edge
there then is not with it then we went to CXI traded a little yes we took maybe
a 20 minutes 30 minutes and then we were back again and the car was
there and eh eh it was well since i think that then
we saw as we turn into our parking then we see that there is
movement or people in the car yes and then we took our bags with
food then we went into our house and then I saw another guy's yes a little older
who stood at chopping there too in the same place why it yes
It's a little reverse thing there before my house and he stood there and and eh
smoked and talked on the phone yes too that I don't recognize him h i to that
there was someone from our neighborhood since no more with it then went
we in and it was it felt a little funny and have these and eh yes late
We start to look a little yes the window and toilet the window up there in the second floor and
check a little what they did such a thing there but just that before it was
that yes no when we got back then eh I went on the back of my house
and eh took a cup of coffee with my daughter and
We talked about this that there were yes strange people who moved on there and
Then we heard these eh that they yes we only heard eh that it was shot somewhere prim
Crime dse eh since yes of course after that then we went and check and started looking from
our toilet eh windows little windows and check on them eh with phone but we
never filmed we just zoomed and checked and then we got to see they found
themselves in the car or so there since yes it is probably that as ends it
what i remembered now mm i understand and i i will put some
questions control questions so that I understand right and that and different details how you
mins and so on but if i start by setting you said if we talk about the guys
Here you first said that there were two younger guys one that was a little older mm eh de
two younger guys if you try to think back and describe them so much so
many so many details you can come up with yes that as
I all as the one that one is most noticed when it was
that they were quite nervous etc. we meet just so there I come
not remember the face of them or something like that I just get the ones they yes it looked
Pretty yes as you say now shady yes so there etc. that was mostly why we laid brand
on the fact that yes it is something that is going to happen now or what is it that is happening now
It is well that do you have any age of these young guys can be yes between yes
13 15 somewhere mm not older than I think somewhere where yes yes you will
remember something where it was the big guys or where the slim guys were
the tall guys slim it was pretty yes no one was so exaggerated no pretty
normal body but yes short yes normally i can say yes m mm mm do you remember what
Was any of them colored no I don't remember
No they had eh luva it was it was an evening yes
Mm what I remember most they had a one of a paper bag they had mm one or
whose one it it understands me and this slightly older guy how would you describe
him pretty yes what should I say yes he was white he was not the color and and eh
What I remember where he was kind of freshly cut
Also, I remember freshly cut, so fad on the sides and
good yes good combed and stuff like that yes he does not hide faces or such
eh remembers how tall he was or how old he was reaching the kind of thing yes too
between 20 25 no more than that no no l läd
about I know it's hard but I ask yes the length there but that he when we
went in then he was there smoking and talking in
phone and eh then he was at hux so where he stood
you saw him stand on the phone and smoke talk on the phone and smoke yes but exactly
Mm and if I just so I understand it right it was the trip to the max it took
about 20 30 minutes type mm you remember when it was you went out and saw
the guys first what time was
then could be nine nine yes so somewhere at half past ten where somewhere i would
Tip yes then I understand
Eh just that and then you went and scouted a bit you said yes and then
Did you perceive that you saw the guys it was when you saw the guys by the car
or was it after the shooting you saw the guys we the car after the shooting
After yes after we heard the bangs m excuse it was me who concluded
the shooting but I think it may be that for it yes etc. eh and then you saw
and zooms in towards the car and then you see that there are people in the car in the car
Yes just then we were also doubtful whether we would call or not to the police
and tell us all the but that
Did you stay there thank you so much is reaching another who wants to ask questions yes
Thank you yes, goodbye Ronnie Hello It will be a bit strange to sit like this but Anton
named my named at least i am one of the defenders in this goal i have
some some control questions just so we get things right and properly understand
Is it something you don't understand or don't understand my questions then it's just that
Saying is the most important thing that it will be right and real jo eh like me
perceived it now when you got questions from the prosecutor so did you think that you
Went to Ica Maxi at about eh nine o'clock it is true yes and
eh remember you remember what you've said in i
Police interrogation about what time eh like this could be no no and then
shall come with the permission of the court we where the page
438 It is then a hearing held with you then the 15th so there and I know that
is a long time so that's why we read up and then you tell you here in the third
Cuts that Ronnie would ride and panta cans at Ika Maxi with her daughter then is
at about 21 they talked about that they would really
ride may be that it was maybe 2110 then rather than nine yes yes yes
okay eh and then you told you now that you met this man eh that stood and
smoked and talked phone eh when you came back from Ika Maxi MM
is that how I perceived, do you remember what you said in police interrogation the day after then about
back when to shop no I don't know it it didn't take that long in all
case was when we got back then yes exactly
Eh but yes and then it is again on a deviation then it is on the next page san
439 in the second paragraph where mm eh last sentence in and paragraph there when Ronnie
Coming home again or I read the whole for the context when Ronnie comes home again
so he hits headlights straight into the gray car and then all three sit in
the car with hoods over your head and some kind of half -stock buff up toward the nose
It was a little before 22.00 mm it may have been so that it was closer to 22 there
then yes it can be yes yes eh and then we and only for the context then
So we at the time of the hearing that was then held with you on the 14th then just before midnight
There you mentioned the time 2150 could be somewhere between 2150 and
2200 made this observation then when you come back okay you remember you
that there are also three people when I saw in the car after eh after when I have
heard the shots no yes I do not actually remember
Okay yes but then I stay there thank you there are some more questions know something no then
Is fret with you finished ronny thanks you should have for coming
Witnessed so then the recording is running the word to prosecutors Hi Per Erik
Rinsell is called Prosecutor at Söder prosecuting Kam man omad just at present
Eh and I have asked you to come here and tell us a little about what you did
As the Deputy Chief of Eh the on the night of the 14th just that
And I thought I will start by asking you to tell you a little what you remember v what
did you get for entrance values and what did you do for action etc. I will
Certainly ask some questions yes it goes great yes but current passport so
I served as an external commander in the police area in Stockholm south etc. and then
were alerted out bangs in Jordbro I think it was the depth mile or
something similar to the address eh was called eh and was pretty quickly appointed by
on -duty commander to police operations manager EH and within the framework of the operation we received
to a lot of resources etc. that were applied to the effort and my initial
directive was to locate the crime scene ensure no one is
physically damaged eh and thereafter begin life -saving action care if it should
needed eh and then then secure
the preliminary investigation etc. parallel to this so I chose
that the patrols that would be closest would handle the crime scene and then
Supply resource would set up in strategically good places in order to
start hunting for perpetrators and so I appointed a
Police colleague to site manager eh crime scene but fairly quickly so
landed one or more resources at the crime scene and then got feedback
that there was eh most of the sleeves outside the home and you could see bullet holes into
The dwelling eh then I don't really remember was in the facade bullet holes were like
But then immediately after that was where was my directive to step into the home
ensure no one is physically injured it is always most important eh fairly quickly
Then I got from my colleagues that they had contact with two plaintiffs about
I remember correctly and they were physically
unharmed then i felt yes but good crime scene we have control of eh
The colleague who was the eh site manager for the crime scene is superb in that
Detail that work then we started hunting for perpetrators the majority
resources dog drivers if I min's right we had helicopter in
The air yes and at some point I do not remember exactly how far behind but during the stake
so two individuals eh young guys were checked relative when the crime scene I
do not remember exactly how far from but but relatively close for eh eh and then assessed
I those who are quite interesting in the context of the effort when controlled so were
they don't together but eh yes they have bit apart but not too far my
Directive then was to obtain personal data on the individuals EH Secure
their phones and strive to get into those cartridges worked on
That pretty quickly I got personal information and if I remember correctly like that
was a 14 years one was 16 and I think both were resident at Lidingö late
Could any of them or the two not really recount what they were doing in
Jordbro I did not judge it as a huge tree anyway which did
that they became even more interesting in this one you got into either a phone
or both phones eh in any of the phones so had any of these
The guys entered the address at the crime scene itself if I remember correct
it some kind of map app you had written eh it on and either in the same
phone or in the other phone there was a picture of these two
the individuals together it then made me could tie them to each other
and to the crime scene and then I decided on
that the 16-year-old would be arrested and the 14-year-old would be brought for interrogation
or picked up for interrogation eh shortly thereafter where my directive to be both
hands would be coated with cardboard bags in order to secure gunpowder if they had eh
had to do with the shooting but they were handled by
patrol sometime during the effort so a bag is found I think it is a
dog driver who searched it eh and then it is looking for
Humanity bag Eh found I think there were clothes in that bag and I
could not put out that eh it was the perpetrators if one had been able to change
If so I decided that it would be taken in seizure in order to hna for
Technical examination eh in parallel with this so we got
from a witness who calls in and says that two young guys had been found
on his eh garden if I min's right we sent a patrol there if I miss right
so he lived relatively close to the crime scene anyway eh and the patrol task was
to hold interrogation with him and demonstrate one last position on them so that our
Dog driver could start searching man checked in the garden
eh that witness had a caravan or camper parked h to it so were found
the two eh gun -like objects and then I decided that it would be blocked
of where eh in order for our forensic technicians to
deal with the weapons afterwards
yes eh then it was another witness that
had any video surveillance from its front door out towards a walkway I remember
and there you could see two young guys either go toward the crime scene or
From the crime scene I don't really remember and if I remember just right now
did the clothes they wore in that video with the clothes that we
found in in the pine I think it was as I remember correctly and parallel to
This is so the work at the crime scene it was yes but sleeves you held interrogation
With witnesses eh man started Dörk Knacking we activated of course
Poä cameras in the immediate area occupied them with resource so that they began to check
Ehm yes so in summary we managed to control two individuals who were for
us who were interesting within the framework of the preliminary investigation we found a bag with
clothing that I judged were interesting two weapons lots of sleeves outside
the crime scene we got a crime scene
Even a gun dog for searching more sleeves to it
Here after all this, the effort went down in intensity eh both of these
the guys were in transported to Flemmingsberg one to the arrest the other
to any interrogation room Man started eh reporting into Flemmingsberg eh
Remaining on site so we had our EH blocked off areas pending techniques
And sometime in that vban I went to Flem for the purpose of yes but help
with the documentation and sew the bag together in there
ehm what I remember too quickly we got eh during the effort
that the crime scene that it was the parents of
An individual who was abroad but was interesting in about for Foxtrot
the conflict that we understood that he was the target in some way it was
the hypothesis we worked on
Yes but in short it is kind of what I remember I can say it was not like that
short moves it was extremely extensive and well reported eh i was thinking now was you
Inside that at the end eh I have noted in events the report
that it is noted from EH RLC then that S Frank address exactly what does it mean
For us who are not police officers it means that it is an address that is interesting
within the framework of our EH conflicts and above all then this wave of violence that
who shielded us in Stockholm linked to primarily the Foot conflicts and that is
usually an address on which one has either eh solid surveillance on or supervision of as far as
of time or good for us to know if there is jobs going out there then can
be of dignity so within the framework of the conflicts so it is interesting
Thank you great here is someone else who wants to ask questions
No no questions then have asked with you thank you so much for you
comes
Witnessed the good then complains mm thanks and as the chairman was in to say to me
If there is something you don't understand yes etc. good
or puts you a little closer to the microphone but if I repeat a little neighbor and so
may you see if I understood it right then but you it is you your wife and then five children
five children who three adopted adopted yes and one of the kids up barrels I plugged in
USA yes US but h she has done she has got married in France okay so we lived in
before in jro mm and since we were 10 pieces it on it and since we also bought a
locations to the man -year road okay so but at this time then October 5
Last year how many were you who lived in the apartment we we we were four
Four children and me and my wife it's six person six people totally okay and where
you at home in the home in the evening the fifth eh eh in the evening I work afternoon
Mm and s my skema and then the 6th of October mm eh I end at half past 10
eh from my workplace to mangos it t about half an hour when but it was a
fifth you worked in the afternoon yes and when did you say when did you stop the job then that
was the clock half half electricity yes in the evening PR then yes
Okay evening etc. and when about where you at home when I get home about the clock
eh 11 okay yes yes and was it someone else in the home then eh when i get home etc.
when i get home eh it my kids were also my velhabar etc so that after when
I come home I would start eating mm and
then yeah you know that time eh but when i get home i can't sleep right i
have to check on news and then shower and then eat ä food it was about
clock eh half mm you can say i saw a
bridge gft to outside eh eh apartment said
You he heard noise outside mm yes and then when I look at the balcony etc. I saw
a guy with a blue jacket etc. he was outside the door okay and then I
Should I be eh ask my Frum but she she was already asleep because she was going to wreck
At f
eh i
Ix five and since i say i can't ask her and since i'll be back
In our room I am watching TV too I thought it was maybe
neighbor who moves stuff they have lost perhaps something on the floor etc. it
were very much word at once it was maybe they
try to cross that box to port entrance etc. and then and then but h you several animals
then no it was just one it was only once animal and that was then when you look
out from the balcony balconies i couldn't ask those guys because it it
Time that happens a lot in Stockholm area you look at news and it
there is something happening in an ine in v is called
in every area in Stockholm so I couldn't ask that guy so I will
can't try eh ask those like the ones they do something where it it in entree
Mm I say eh I'll check maybe tomorrow piece if something happens mm
mm and then i i come to spring day room and since i go to bedroom
and so I sleep mm at five my wife she woke up and since she went to the shower
after when she was going out to go eh t train train so she went straight to out mm
She found the tank you showed it in stairs yes these different containers yes and
then lots of stuff in in stairs to port entrance gate mm mass stuff that I showed
exactly but tank also mm and then eh expect and then spirit the mass I showed so
She saw all the different things the cards yes when she went she called me I said George yes
It is very it sounds strange here so what they have brooks in entrance etc. I saw
lots of stuff I don't know if they have used etc. I tell my wife oh it was
At half past half I saw a guy mm eh just outside the door but I don't know about
never out and checked if I understood it right but you went then to lay down
just yeah m and then police they have written and since i will be back home i
tells my my doter you can't go to school we have to wait mm for that
happens something we do not know we don't know we we don't know if it is we like they
would come to make against fire to us no yes we don't know and since I ask
The police police say we try to investigate etc. so you have to wait eh
After examination etc. I understand yes eh I may only ask you you describe that
It's a guy like you see yes a guy yes yes you see someone else is there anybody
Anyone nearby after it was in six o'clock
Pois stayed until 12 o'clock yes but I mean there when you heard something you heard
Some form of noise you describe you go out on the balcony and check out there around 2330
someday and then i will say you saw a guy then with a blue jacket yes one
just so so no one else is no no you hear if it is talking to someone else
or seems to be in the company of any other person no i don't h i check
just to and s i get back to home yes so that time it was a little
Many people looked at n the shooting everywhere in the entire area of Stockholm area so man
You get a little scared if something happens so mm and at this
The time eh all the others who were in the apartment were they waking up too
there someone who was sleeping at the time I didn't so I didn't see one one person
that has floor in your apartment then no it was this morning where I saw many who
floor now they have started but I thought there at 2330 when you heard this sound and
check out the others in your apartment your wife and your children were they wake up then or low
they and slept they slept they all slept so it was only you who have wake bare okay
eh and you said a little bit about that you talked to the police where etc. I will
testify to the police n yes did you get any information eh at
So something you talked to police at some later time also eh
information from the police yes no they have seen they have told me the so -called buy
examination etc. and since they have taken personal numbers and then telephone mobile etc. and
Then they say yes when we try to work here so we get to see etc. so you know about the police
one came to which apartment or if there was someone
special apartment that one would do anything toward it we were the apartment
because it was all the materials the one that eh they have shown it was outside and when you
So say you mean these pictures I have
showed it was outside the EHT ENTTE ENTEE you went out and so it
was a bit outside the gate okay but you say it was against your apartment how
Do you know that because my wife will come hut etc. it is she who has
told me etc. she to me s I saw a one tank tank like bomb mm eh like v
the bomb like this gas yeah exactly it was closer to v reggen mm okay when man
will be stairs and then it was a little closer to the door etc. and then the eh tank
Benin it was in almost in entre mm in entre it was in but the bomb that you
have shown it was closer okay eh our lenh m yes mm eh i have no more questions
to you right now mm Thank you very much julia fight f you ask some questions yes thank you
Eh how did you experience this situation i yes yes yes situation it was
Very difficult on me and ora family eh because it was they have tried mban
the family and since it there are many consequences as well
eh when
one thinks there will be a criminal f will eh kill or family so we were
a little worried and then eh eh me and my family we have forced to
leave the apartment and then eh we we were lucky because the police they have helped a lot
they have they have taken over eh and since they will always help us move to
otherwise because we would not eh stay there because it will
the other one I don't know about the local criminal I don't know they will
to us it was eh next because they come at the time
[Music] eh at the clock eh at the clock
seven something or six o'clock eh they come to us the ones they receive three
I say but eh my son yes we were we got we got
panic so we say yes we think eh we have to ask with my son what happens
because we understand the situation we do not understand that situation and
then she guys he try to get h so we don't want to open the door so I
thought my wife you can't go down because you don't know them we have to pick up a
witness because maybe we want hay what they want to talk to us and so we I
come to kad to my spruces i see my spruces to e excuse me can you
come out there are three guys here they want to talk to us but we don't feel
them because it is what is something is on the one the eating we do not know about them who
come here eh try eh mother fire family or what do they want
my neighbors come out and since we went down eh also talk to them they come in
We open the door and then they say now you have to move it otherwise you can
not discuss you have to move from here I tell them why you should take
The decision who are you who are deciding here in Sweden or they say
You can't discuss with us yes otherwise if you discuss with us it will
Other problems but now now have to go to say to them but do not want to
aet that we are going to pussy we have to plan I what should I go with it with my
kids and s my wife and my daughter say dad you can't discuss with them eh
you don't know them it's better we pussy at once because you know that
happens a lot is in Stockholm and s We don't know them so after the white n my
Neighbors he was there and since he was very much fun he also says yes eh
Why I will not meet criminals so he thinks so can he was very scared
A two hours you can say they have tried to talk to my
Son all fam and then says eh you have to stay here we should start working on this
Turn so and then after that police went so we say we can't stay
here otherwise that will the problem we have forced eh move to a friend as they
have they received the whole family eh via st
Prim after pole will call us and then we
tells the police we don't know what should we do to this as we live just
Now that is our opportunity only we have to go to a place that we are going to live with family
Kids have to go to school i too i have to work my wife have to work too
all the children we hit with the situation it becomes very difficult eh for
us they have created many consequences eh former we prejudice sea
Don't know what happens we don't understand the situation because why they come
to us what made us the situation we ask my mine my my
son eh so too h he tells dad i i know nothing i know nothing i
don't know why they come to us so we have
try to ask question there is no answer kids say nothing we also say
nothing so we say the police will try to investigate and so we
just waiting for the hard come to the police and so we've stayed there in
Police they have found a one apartment pling apartment we have lived occasion next one
month there and then after the police they will always help after maybe
three days they get to where they can manage the family so that we should also raise to
we can't put down eh all the stuff we have to live too
can come too sometimes and then police they say eh right now
You just live in addition to you but we may try to help
eh you will go back to our apartment we will always work for
to guarantee security but it is not 100 % and s police they have they have give us
an alarm form there is something that is eh than where we can directly activate alarm
To call the police the station we had just and s we cheat eh live with
the paranoid if you get it stuck here in
UV it gets stuck uv you know what you think we will be in Sweden
Tr will we be going to protect us and so we have not done anything and then about it
Will a person kmin fam we f
Viting so I say I would explain better in French for I
would use j
stive volon n la famille vic
your kmin gray yes your family has been exposed to
bearish
So it cries the court if you can find out where this situation is coming
from the very root of the fact that we have been exposed it creates a lot of prejudice and
It creates difficulties for us PR Moral Prud
finci cr
Psychose yes it affects us at all levels mentally physically and it creates wounds
in the soul psychosis in the soul but soulful
sob okay etc. I didn't really do with but everyone is responsible in this
need to be held accountable or something like that m book m thanks I have
no more questions in more questions no is any of the defenders who want to ask
questions no thanks i just have one question i have not understood hello anton
named my hey hi and is it something is you don't understand or
Something's just saying so I'll try to take it to reach problems eh
I only have one that I haven't got clear to me real eh n I don't know
If you saw when the prosecutor showed the pictures from your stairs then thought it looked like
that the mailboxes are inside the entrance door when you enter your position
Is it is so it looks like that picture no but are you have the mailboxes in the entrance or
Do you have mailbox in the door no mailbox no mailbox eh it's just that post
it is inside yes inside the door therefore this one the criminal they come they have they
have kossa they have kossa just ask the mailbox if they are in the entrance it is
not in Enté no it is inside or me in three in three in entrance with inside yes I
understands inside this crushed door in there yes okay but
Thanks then eh then I have understood how it looks eh then I do not have more
questions to you thank you very much thank you very much a comped short eh i forgot
Ask if you can describe this person you see in any more way you said
that it had blue jacket that you see you can say anything more about age length
look yeah yeah it he i don't know what i can say eh i saw a person
with the blue jacket etc. but it is very difficult to say
eh on long because it was I just check there and since I go back etc. I
couldn't dub check understand yes there is nothing you remember reach more today yes it is
just the eh blue jacket and then yes it was yes blue jacket exactly there as I watched
The picture it was blue jacket that I saw that person eh on at night mean you mean
that this then the jacket that I have shown that it was the same jacket or mean
you just that it was similar color similar to that but those who come eh after that
one can describe because I met them I can say he was not calm
he had a cap yes but then you talk about the day after yes yes yes because then I think
You have provided some information in interrogation when you were heard by the police October 6 there
In the morning eh where you have left some more details about how this person saw
Out and then I would like to read it to you just see I don't want you
should not eh come dir mix people there is
Mm and that is the one I talk about yes it he what you talk yes etc. it was a
person there as i say and since he had blue jacket as i say mm and so
i think cap also cap i think cap it at night mean i think i think i
Use KEP cap cap so as yes I will read what you have said in this hearing
Then you'll see I think and that hearing is on page 113 Eh and then is
the question or question from the interrogator what did this man look like
As you saw and then it noted that you should answer white skin blue jacket looked
About 170 cm slim he had the jacket any text on the back of the jacket type so yes
just as I say yes it so it gets yeah as with it eg yes t exactly
I came when saying to the police yes and here you have described that it had white
skin white skin v a little blan a little blat a little he was white a v white not black it
is true yes it is true was white but i can't say which one is nationality i
can't say but no no no but that task is right and he was slim and 1
is that is it too yes I understand yes okay eh then
I have nothing further thank you no and this event when you got when it on
the conversations and so he had a person with him then mm eh but he did not say so
much without it was the one who talked the most and so he said that you must
Open the door you have to get down because we have to talk to you we have to talk to you
son what happened here the day before it is concerned it was towards you so that you
really need to talk to us we don't want to stand and scream ehm over as well
the balcony railing without you need to come down and talk they said m eh and then so joined
a third person to this meeting then eh and when he arrived he was masked
Mm eh but when he friend saw this they asked him to take off the masking
eh and said take off your masking they will be scared type in something in it i i
that style eh and then we then made the decision and go down and meet these eh and then took
We with us the neighbor then just like dad explained etc. and what what happens thereafter there
down then eh down there they explained a little bit what happened and then they said
that it was eh they said it was a one boy who was there 15 years they said m eh
who came and would light up at home with us and then the plan he had apparently
a phone on them as they had then taken eh and then there were messages on it
here the phone with our address and my little brother's name and also how all that
here would go to eh and then he had eh gasoline cans they said and eh and then was
the idea that he would pour gasoline eh with the help of towels
or rags through the mailbox and light on eh and then pour this whole
the way out to the gate then as they described it
Eh but they succeeded then eh stop him and then they had taken
Though him and abused him and threatened him that he would not come
back here okay and if you can just explain it again like me so I hang
with where they had seen message on his phone yes and it was both
Information about your name and your address yes it was my little brother's name and then
our address then yoke mm and what was it you said it was about the approach
eh they said he eh would he had gasoline eh and so it was rags
handduka they said ehm and then it was that he would pour on these rags
or towels or whatever it was and throw it into the mailbox and light on so
that like it was lit like that and then he would pour eh petrol then all the way off
the front door down to the cards so that, like everything would burn
up okay how did you react to it eh we were, of course, of course, etc. they said
something more what had happened to that person then no they just said they eh
managed to stop him because he had received eh this mission out of someone
older eh and then they managed to stop him and abuse him but they know as well
Eh can you say anything about how you and the family
experienced the situation as a whole ehm around this fifth s seventh yes
So the first day when this happened and we went down and talked to
The police got to see the gate and so it was more just that you wondered what has
Happened and yes a little so as everything going on they had just built fires
nearby and there have been shootings and a bit so that it was more like
sheer curiosity since the day after these came then and like said that this was
Against us, it was that we were eh you were scared of course eh and
eh very cut and and we did not want to sleep in the apartment eh
and we slept that night yes that night we slept so the first night we slept
there eh and then we all slept together and I slept with my siblings to
I don't want to sleep near the front door and a bit so that you were very scared
Mm
Eh how did your life work you could go to school and could take care of jobs and eh eh
I didn't go to work the two days after I think it was just for
that one did not want to be in the area and did not want to move as in the same
movement patterns because I have very square life so I take the same bus
every morning the same bus home and then you were afraid that they may have I know
Not as well as followed this in any way so that you were afraid and like that
You might be persecuted or people knew where you lived and a little so eh but
Then we didn't live at home and then it was that I could then I went to
The job as usual that I did not move in the same area
mm you have told you a little about being scared there was something more in it
the experience around yes both this gas tube and that
that stood in the stairs but also to be identified as a target for this
through these boys eh you become very paranoid etc. eh you are a little
more cautious a little more vigilant over as well as their surroundings and also to yes
am a little questioning to every young guy you see outdoors as well as so that
yes then it was that it was
Eh there were conflicts within the family as well to
that yes you stood against each other and someone did not speak the truth and a little so
as yes it destroyed pretty much ok affecting that relationships
yes say something more about it eh for this was aimed at my little brother ehm but
He claimed that he did not or still claim that he does not know anything
If the whole situation or thus he does not know why it could happen against
him just and then it becomes that we others become very questioning that he
is the only guy in the family and eh the whole wave of violence has been against guys
Speaks truth etc. Okay
Thanks etc. Some questions no questions t no questions no then we finish prime crime
DSE is recording started this is something you want to start by saying yes yes
Tell us about all this eh should I tell yourself yes you can tell yourself
do it first mm eh i was at i b on hb home and family homes almost all my
life and i sat on my hvb home and we talked pretty much about making money
and crime and stuff where there were some others there who are doing such
eh since i have a friend on my hvb home eh police have seized his phone so
he uses my phone instead of n he wins on someone
signal gray he told me from nowhere just fixed job to you
since he showed me his naps he had or my nap he had written like this yes
And then since I didn't think much about it I didn't even know what it was about
them and i thought okay it's sure i didn't even get myself eh since i
Received this phone I checked It said I would burn burn stuff
so I just ok so I don't even want to do it myself really I think
eh but I was still trying to persuade myself so it felt like I wanted to
do it eh since i took a bus to kronfors eh and i took a earlier
the took from Kramf because I was pretty stressed eh so instead of having it
real took as i one was going to take so i took an earlier eh since when i came
Until Sundsval eh I was very stressed I didn't really know what I
would do but thought so I still tried to persuade myself since I
comes up to Stockholm eh since I meet this girl who is on it
car what is it called picturel or what it is called eh since when i already understood then
Self that I didn't want to do this I can't do this eh
and when I was pretty stressed and I was just trying to come up with some way and
wrapping me out of eh i will come up to this apartment eh i see that it
lies a gun where eh I don't know if the gun is real or fake but I
guess it is FT because there is something that stands out in the barrel so I
Thinking it is certainly any airsoft or something so I what the name is I pull
this one what is the mantle of this thing backwards so I happen to access someone
button since it stuck eh somehow since i'm filming with my phone
eh think like this yes what I thought I don't know what I thought I had nothing
I didn't think so much about it since I checked I pulled the b mantle again late
I saw that there was some bullet that was stuck eh in what is the name so I
Thought oh it might not be so good and I was quite terrified now thought
maybe someone will kill me eh so i called him who wrote to me
on signal I don't remember what his name is eh I wrote to he I thought it is
calmly did something he told me it's quiet and then i have bv pretty
what is it out what is it called yes or what the hell what is it called
I was not a happy shitty sounded huh
relieved yes exactly exactly it got pretty relieved so i put back this
the gun where it lay and i never redded it again because i didn't dare eh
Then they told me it was time so I was very tense and I knew
not and before they asked me when it was time they asked me too
wanted tramadol eh i told them you didn't want tramadol i told you
them because it was to have not taken tramadol before and I didn't know about
she was going to be paranoid but really it was because if I
Took tramadol I might actually light fire and I didn't want to light fire
eh so I went to this place in Visätra I walked around I pondered
didn't know what to do eh it ended with me walking around maybe 30
the pot I don't even seal the stuff I just put them somewhere so it would
Look like I've been trying since I just went from there eh I walked around wise
maybe 15 minutes about since there will be some guys to me they asked me what
I do why I am masked eh since they should be questioning stuff as I am
afraid it is those who have given me the job that has come here to yes they
angry at me eh so i told him what to do since they got angry at me
Eh and they took me to the forest they interrogated me lots of stuff drove for too
drove for you I didn't even know myself eh since h began to knife in my thighs
Eh my legs and everywhere and beat me they took my phone too
eh then a police car drove past so they ran from there eh and then I could escape
So I limped myself from there to what is it to Flempan I think so
I understood it right then EH HVB home in northern Sweden I say a little sloppy eh
it is true that you yes it is true it was quite far up yes eh but if i
understood it right then you describe as it is any friend to you then as
takes your phone and enters reaching grup no i lend out the one i lend it you
lends it out yes eh since yes okay so it is not so that you have this yourself
the phone and is invited to any group chat without it is any friend who
log in then and take this job for you exactly
Eh but there was nothing you wanted to do really did you say no not
Actually but I wanted to play tough in front of them and I talked like
that I tried like make them think I was a criminal or something
I don't know no eh so that's why this situation at all
it eh and i didn't think so much about the consequences I didn't even understand
really even what it was I was going to do at all I knew bore that it
would burn something okay they were not entirely clear either in signal I know
not if it occurs anywhere but only he wrote that he as they
I thanked then just stated that I would just burn equipment eh and
then sowing yes and then so out what is it called then they changed f all the time
until it ended up in the end it became an apartment okay and when did you find out
That it was an apartment then eh it was when I was on my way to Stockholm okay
eh and did you find out some details about where this apartment was located
somewhere in Stockholm or why exactly the current apartment the only thing I
got to know why it was a little later when I was in this apartment and I
asked them eh when they said there is someone driving for us and driving for someone else
now something like that mhm that's all i've been told okay
Mm But but what but what was the very purpose as well as from the friend's side as well as to
add it to this one i don't actually know maybe it was maybe he wanted to
playing from maybe he wanted to show that yes I can I can solve so you can
Get money maybe I don't know for yourself no eh you may ask him okay
Mm This task you come up with here today around that there is some buddy
that adds you in reaching in any group and that you don't really want to do it
right from the start there is any task that you have left in interrogation before eh
I actually don't remember but I think that no I can say that there is not
Confirmation or whatever it is called that what I say is right so you can from, etc.
man you choose to answer that okay but i asked you spontaneously so you said yes
You think you have said so but you have not mentioned anyone else there but there
Do you rather write like it was you who was in any group and it goes out
a job and you thank you yes it sue you get a ticket the details that
I gave they don't match? No. Okay. And the reason that they don't
is it true was simply that you don't want someone else to get shit
I understand that right then exactly okay
eh and as I said you say nothing about it to go on to something else
put in any of these other interrogations that agree with you either
Okay but that's the same reason for it then that you don't want someone else
You have yes okay and how do you take where do you go then then eh we take any bus
or or subway i honestly i actually don't remember no if it was
bus or subway i remember i was sitting in a vehicle
Yes i think it was a subway but since we also took a bus
Okay you know where you ended up in the end eh yes we ended up at this
the apartment yes this address it may be difficult on the shooter's street there in
Bandhagen I couldn't the address of it that was why I was googling on
my phone because I tried to get back to the apartment eh because I
didn't know what else i would go anywhere mm eh so i didn't know
the address etc. I think we will come to it a little further ahead but I it you
Talked about now it is then when you have met on this Esmeralda then after
eh you know about when you arrived at this apartment after you go then
from the top northern sweden eh in stockholm etc. eh so i I know can't it was
that I think I arrived at type one mm eh I met this one
the girl a little after 12 if i mins correct mm
Eh I showed some surveillance pictures and stuff like that around 0140 or 038 there so
Was there any bus that you should get off in Brandberg Centrum it can be true yes
It can sue etc eh just this with how you get to
This apartment has you provided other information about
What I don't know I just said lots of those stuff on my interrogations because I was
pretty nervous eh i was tense eh i i was a little what is it
Confused I don't know I have a hard time with it when I was in custody I I
don't know that detention center it was just a difficult period
mm okay
eh if i say this way when you have described in the first three interrogations yes
that you are being picked up by a man who comes with a car at the Central and drive
you to this apartment no what did you say that is true
not yes ex and in this third hearing then so
Do you then show up these surveillance pictures then that you meet
This girl and that you see that you go down in public transport and after
Mm ok so simply not to pull in someone else is so i will understand it
yes would you eh how would you say that your yours
story about this person that is, the one you had in these first three
interrogations how would you say it was i don't remember
No if we go to this first hearing
then page 487 and what I want to demonstrate is that I mean that you have left
very much detail about then a person then that is completely invented
Yes and it is still then on we shall see
here
[Applause]
[Applause] Here we'll see about where in the wrong interrogation first
and
The interrogator you went to Stockholm Central what happens there and there describes
you like this i wait for three hours at the station a guy comes and took me
to the apartment how did you know it was the person who would pick you up
I didn't know who it was but that it would be a guy with black
Adidas pants and armani hoodie how does he look other 30 years you will remember
If he was tall or short quite tall as you 0 yes what color on the hair brown
mustache and bearded he said what his name is no it said nothing they said just came it was
A person yes where did you go when we sat in a car it was a black Volvo who
The police have and then he drives you to an apartment how long did you drive maybe 20
minutes remember where you went somewhere no you recognize something at
the road no actually and then you describe a little neighbor in this one
The apartment I mean that here you have then provided information about
estimate of age and length color of the hair mustache and beard even then
The car they asked for a person then as I perceive then is completely invented
yeah yeah what why do you leave so much details i don't know so if i
understood it correctly it was because they asked me and then I just said
something okay but all this was just found on yes
Mm when you can then finally ask in this third
the interview when you are set against this about why are you so different do you remember what
What did you say from the hearing or because you say here today that it was because you
wanted to pull other yes mm in that interview then as starting at
side
493 ne sorry it was another task that you actually got no one
Ask about should I be clear with or something but that I will say
Initially in the hearing so you were asked to describe this person again
that came picking up you sorry just so i
know what interrogation are we at now now we are the third hearing he never got anyone
Ask about it was another question that I had read so
that but then it will be again before you get to see these pictures then and that you become
aware that one has seen with this girl asked to describe
this person eh and then it is recorded like this on
Page 495 You said he said it was a male who picked up you yes in what way was
masked he had one of these balaklava and black clothes you remember some
Details of the clothes no not so I thought he had this like this Jordan f Red
Founder on but I don't remember what is it for the red
Jordan's Jordan 4 Yes it is shoes prime.se yes so you have not just described ÖVG
signal element also then what kind of shoes in this then the person who is completely
invented should wear yes yes
Okay I thought if there was any reason to leave so much
Details eh then you scored when H asked me this I had I had
forgot that what I had said in for in the last company so I just said something
Random again okay
Then I understood it as you arrive at this apartment
eh and you tell you pretty immediately about a gun
Yes is that is something that you note directly you enter this apartment
or how should I understand that eh where somewhere when you come to
This apartment you have come to Stockholm EH and you come there around 0140
time sometime just before two around midnight there eh yes what what is it like what
Hands when you enter the apartment I get into the apartment eh
me i bench myself on the couch eh i look a little on my nap and then so see
i this phone or gun okay where is it
somewhere on a bench or whatever the nighthouse bod type even eh sofa
okay and you describe a gun you see some
other weapons or weapons -like items in the apartment eh no no okay
and do you do anything with this one
then here the mantle as I said eh I happen to access some button it gets stuck in the back I
Takes out my mobile I take a picture eh then do you press the button again so
that it goes down back etc. Okay and after that when you described this
For that I don't remember but I at least added to the back in the same place
okay
Mm eh
These movies that I have shown then from Snapchat Yes are you on the movies
Yes you are in this apartment on the movies yes etc.
eh you can describe this apartment in general eh yes it so out as so g out
In the pictures what should I see yes there was no one there what I know lived and
lived it was only me i was alone only since there were two guys who were there
A little while with me until I went eh so I don't know the deon lives where I have
no idea but i vs only who was there no no but got it someone
feeling that someone lived there and so there are there were some like that
here personal belongings reach pictures or similar personal ie I
Did it know that it was eh such a print apartment so that was what I got
Hear at least okay and who did you hear the eh person like g with the job at
eh you i was going to jump back to it
here as I asked you or as you told us about this one
signal gray who or how you ended up in it and this with the mission yes eh and I
sets you against a task that you have left in interrogation around it from one of
The interrogation but I find another task in in another hearing as well there
you have described this and I mean that you describe differently to what
you do it today and it is in interrogation the other
the hearing with you that starts on page 485 that held on 16
October so there is a task on the page
EH and question from interrogator then is that Sebastian gets asked why
he refused to crime considering he describes how everything has gone to and then
stands on the sign so iebastian has not prepared anything he does not know
Who did what he has not met the person he has been in contact with
Two people the first one was on Tuesday or Monday at Signal It was a group
where one on his hvbhem added him the group's name is an emoji one
Chocolate gruffs
to him in the group friend did not know if the job he would do in
decided to tell you the truth yes
Mm eh i also have a question and it is in
This first hearing so you were set against that there is
eh on snapchat then when you went through when you were logged in to this
The phone so there were some snapchat conversations and such
Snapchat conversation that showed you in connection with this first
The hearing that you agreed with you, you remember it it was a while ago
I barely remember anything from mine for but
eh no it's a conversation with some ross yes it is one of my friends yes
from linero yes okay and do you remember that conversation eh yes yes eh he said to
me eh that I should come to Linero and work for him instead okay eh and
that he will make me make a lot of money yes and do you remember what you wrote in
That conversation yes I said I would only do a few jobs in Stockholm
and that I will be there since I think I said so but I don't remember okay and I
thought I haven't relied it before because the setting has
not it stands anyway like this one
Since maybe we should look at it so mentions may look at it as well you want to show it
Or should we show the one I can show the one I have mm prime.se
ah i take a while before these warms up it seems so
Mm now it starts
So that is then a snapchat conversation that the police then found when
man eh checked in Esmeralda's phone where you would then have logged in to your
Snapchat and then it is some ross it is good kei how is it good o all eh
Should become yeps in Stockholm you should come to Linero yes after a while should only
Make money first a little type 30 salmon on burns and stuff shoot at house and
So on when I have 30 to 70 salmon I ask about holidays for a week in Lund I
brother come to us i have jobs for you will get you and poop money yes when happens
this conversation eh no idea but maybe I happened
Remember it was in the apartment when I wrote there yes okay I vs not what day
No ok there you write like you should earn 30 salmon on burns and stuff and
tried to sound cool in front of my friends okay eh there was something like that yeps
What does it mean to be a hose target Langod for murderers etc. but it is
Nothing I was thinking about being no okay it tells myself that
does not stand anything about it to kill someone it says what is closest to death reach
standing and shooting at houses so I don't even know why I wrote
Yeps I don't remember no okay you remember what you've told the police then when you get
Ask about this conversation in the hearing that one agreed with you as I said
I hardly remember any of my interrogations it was too long and I was nervous
and confused yes and this is the very first to hear it on October 6
which starts on F Page 468 EH and you then get questions about this conversation
then as I just showed up eh on page 477 and at the bottom then is recorded
Did you get the 30,000 no I haven't done anything but you said after all
15,000 Then the record is that I would do several jobs I would do a job
For 15,000 and the next day 15,000 it says I will shoot at the house but
nothing that is determined they asked what I am prepared to do I see everything except
to kill it is the conversation on signals and brought up to shoot they
called me and said it was coarser stuff when it rang on the phone that
called on signal when they called the rough stuff once on hvb home and one
time in Stockholm in the apartment they asked me what I am ready for they said you can
get more work to shoot at house i said okay yes eh this about this job it
is true they have asked me eh or asked me and asked me it was
really not even a question it was more that they told me there are such
here work as well etc. and then I replied that there are such jobs not to
would make it that there are such jobs and then I said okay as okay then I know
But I don't know what I babbled about in this interrogation eh yes as I said I was
Pretty confused eh and when I said those rough about the rough stuff etc. eh so
I thought he meant that with lit electricity on the house
Mhm okay eh because here i get the perception as
that it says that you should say, among other things, they asked what I prepared
to do i said everything except to kill like that you still have discussed then
about what assignments you can imagine to perform yes they asked me too
told me these who you told you if you turn on this house late
He also said there are other jobs then I told them okay then they said what are you
prepared to do as it stands here and then I told everything for all the tens for out they
were dead m and as you have understood and what I told you before eh so I said
just things and i maybe i don't want to kill anyone then if i had wanted
Kill someone so I had lit at this eh door and I had taken Ramad
also mm eh but nuur should i understand it as you have it it is true that you have
had conversation about doing other jobs but there was never anything
As you were going to perform exactly but you still told about it to the police I
want it to look like I had plans to do it and I don't want to
that it should look like I didn't want it to look like I didn't want to do
any of that that was why I said so okay and because I was confused
But for whose sake you mean it should look like you had intended to do
stuff when they read my preliminary investigation so they see it it was ok so you mean
that you think, as in that step further, then that these then the people then as
have hired you or what to say that they should get the perception and believe that
you had thought to do this yes okay i i get the rather people n as man
Then, at least, thought I would rather get people to think I wanted to do it and
I am sitting inside maybe a year at SIS etc. Ann that I will be on something free or
gets less punishment and then gets killed it it is pretty obvious okay you thought
that you had no choice but to say yes is that so I will understand it yes
Okay
eh if I just jump then after this supplement then it stands it never got off
is left lance then question then it is noted that it would be off but did not become
because I sit here I know is also then just because it
should look no there if that is where I don't even know
So that it didn't get it was not because the police took me it was
after all because I myself chose not to make it okay so and that because it was
The police took me the police they took me like I can't so much time but
maybe one or two hours after I chose not to do it so I don't know
even why i said so that i it's not even relevant no eh yeah okay
It is not that you here today then try to tone down your intentions and your
intent and what you thought to do or not do eh what do you mean by tone down
Yes but that you simply try to make it appear like you never had
thought to do something just because that is what you should go free it is because I
is going to be free or for me to be free I tell the truth etc. I ask
you yes it is like how what tasks should we believe in the ones I tell you now you you
Tells now okay and then I think this way you don't think
that these then who hired you then find out what you say here today eh jo
But I have made a choice and eh that so it is yes I do not know
what to do so no okay
eh I think before the break there I was on and would ask you then what
is what happens since the day here on this Thursday the fifth it wants
say you have arrived there late at night what do you do daytime there then were
other people in this apartment then eh earlier yes in my latest for mm so
did i tell mm but in the three earlier then eh no no that i told it that
was because I had a hearing I don't know if it says but I don't know
When was I the detention had a hearing and then they asked me like this eh were you yourself
in the apartment then i said yes since they said sounds land or John not as you come
remember mm eh yes i remember it but i told them no mm eh and then so said
they yes but it was scary because these two people have mentioned someone
that looks like you or described someone who looks like you that I already knew
that they had told me about me so I thought I might as well tell you
it g no harm mm okay yes but for as you mention yourself so in the first three
The interrogation you get clear questions then in all of them if you have been alone in this one
apartment or if you have been there someone else there and in all these three interrogations
Have you replied that you have been alone and that there was no one else there yes
At any time for one you then in this fourth hearing as you are inside
on then mentions that they must have been there for a certain time yes and what is the reason
that you mention it first then eh to eh I told my former
lawyer eh and my lawyer she didn't think it might be so good that I
told it m eh i don't really know why but i guess yeah i know
not even by yourself but there is certainly something behind it mm eh so I chose
self not to tell you because of that yoke so you mean it was like on
the advice of your lawyer then as it said so that way
I went from the apartment to Vära I thought was at type at half past
nine something like that okay and do you have something with you then eh when
You go there yes a gasoline tube mm a can with gasoline mm eh dk flush liquid eh
papersticks and a lighter eh i just believed it that mm and what has
you got these things from eh i i got them when i was in
the apartment okay can you describe how it went to eh I'd rather not tell
I have mentioned a person in my interrogation M but I would rather not tell him how he
What I said until it's just something random that I have said eh that's right
Not when I described the person who gave me the stuff and I'd rather not
Tell me who it was that gave me the stuff because of my own security okay can
you tell me when and how it went then yes I can tell you it was when know
I don't I don't remember but it was on during the day not during the evening it was
not dark outside no eh i went out from the poort i received eh bags eh two
pieces of bags with stuff in or if it was one I don't remember since I went into
in the apartment
again mm
ok but you don't want to describe this person no
No did you want to say something whether it was a guy or a
Girl eh no
no okay it wasn't that wasn't my target call
that left the stuff no as you claimed
Okay and what is the reason why you don't want to leave someone further
And what did you do with these things when I went into the apartment and put them on
the floor of the living room etc. you understand what it was
Eh yes mm did you understand what it would be used for m
yes answered a little slowly there yes it is clear I if one understood what it was for
Things I well realized it was for me because they wanted me
would do this thing so I assumed that was what I would have
helped with okay or what it would be used for and what did you do with those
here the things then eh Visätra or the apartment yes in in it
Here the apartment as I said I just put on the floor since I sat down on the couch and
chilled with my phone okay and then the journey to Visätra
So how does it go to eh taxi by taxi is the usual taxi company or that
was a car with when I got into the car so I saw that there was some screen
somewhere where there was taxi mm okay and how did you find out that it
Taxi would take you there eh they wrote to me that your taxi is here eh I will
not remember what kind of name I would use but they told me to
say some name I don't remind what it was if it was Isaac or Magnus or
what it was but it was annot name that has said i was called okay and was it
also through the signal here then the group you received that information yes okay and they
Here the things that you have received earlier in these bags you will take with you
them or do you leave them in the apartment no i bring them yes yes
Everything all of you
Mm It is a bit shady if you leave with stuff n and
Going and you got to reach information about where you
would somewhere which address or similar no I my I knew
not even myself that I would not even know that it was Visätra no I
Remember that I went since the taxi stopped since they told me I will drive
up it all the way to the pot and I said yes
Mm okay so you didn't know V where you would then do this job
somewhere no I only knew it would be 25 on the pot and that it
would stand and k on the door okay and how would you have received in that information through
signal via signal etc. Okay but you didn't know further then as what what yourself
The street itself was called without 25 at the gate and it was the taxi that drove it all the way
front yes the street I found out in after the police okay yes okay so you had only
the number itself then and the name of the door
Yes eh and what happens then when you arrive
I understood it right then that you think it might be
around eight nine in the evening so it is yes
Yes what happens then when you arrive where that taxi stays there at this
The gate you describe the first thing I do is that I take these stuff I
Put them in a bush etc. since I walk around thinking about how to go
access to get d to get away
eh because even at all to do it it was completely excluded it was not
even an alternative ehm i just walked around eh late in the end
I came to the conclusion that I just break the pot eh I just put the stuff
Like in the stairwell so it looks like I was trying to do it m eh late
I just went from there ok since I know I thought I might
could come up with any story that someone came out and someone came out in
the door and screamed at me or something or something like that mm yes for how did you
intended to take you from the site eh taxi taxi and in what way would that taxi
So how would you book a taxi just before I went into the pot so I called
or called i wrote to he who goes with the job that i did now since he
wrote to me ok I sent the taxi etc. Okay and he had sent to me
the address that the taxi would come on m but I do not remember the address but I laid
in it in Google Maps or what is it Apple Maps or something so I could only
see a blue dot so I knew what to go such a green blue road etc.
the phone okay and then you thought that if you get it look like you have
attempted but then had been to try to find any story then that they would
as well as release it eh or how
travel I don't really know how I thought no but eh
I thought it is better to go back in the apartment than to try to escape
tan that the white name maybe if I escape maybe my family and rilla out
eh so for the reason I chose I to go back to the apartment and
come up with any vott explanation and see what happens so you had thought of trying
Get back to this g attack the apartment then on the shooter's street okay and
did you think anything about if there was any risk that you might be allowed
reach another assignment then because you have not completed this I did not think so
a lot i was pretty stressed i i don't really know that my brain it was
good closed mm okay eh if i start with this with
time and you now say if I feet you around Åta nine in the evening you have
that in retrospect might speculate on what time
where so stands in the middle of that side of 487 itself the question is finished
To the crime scene and before Sebastian crushes the Sebastian box to 2330 to
Visätra and so he was thinking he was there for maybe one to two hours
Before he crushed the box to the gate eh yes it is true that is the right
should sue okay unless time perception was wrong but it felt anyway as
one to two hours
Mm and then I have to ask you a little bit
around for now here today so perceive it as you get where you put the things
In a bush you go and think about how to get your story and go together you
crushes this gate takes in some things and then you go out and become then
to catch by these people yes it is actually quite a long time before these
the people even come yes eh because as to said but that with the taxi eh I was
I went around I didn't even know if I would go back to the taxi I went
Around and wondered if you would walk around the taxi for maybe type 15 minutes eh
invented yes it is true
yes i describe like you say it as to confuse no i don't know
even but yes yes I thought
Yes
ok but it has not been in any other apartment but it was it
the apartment on Sagittarius street and then you are then taken via taxi then to to
Mangårdsvägen Yes mm Okay
And then I ask this
Eh There are information that you have provided in interrogation about a soft airgun pistol it
something you want to mention and tell us about spontaneous eh that soft airgun
The gun that is not right I don't know why I said it eh I don't have
had on me any sofa pistol
eh okay you remember what you've said then around
Softan Pistol and why you've had it and last you
have received it from and what does with the one I told me I would have on
with that eh in case anyone would open the door
mm Do you remember who you have said you got it
Here Soft Aron Pistol by Eh
No really not but i f me to say anything about that i got it off
someone i don't vs vs. who eh maybe any of these two people
in the apartment I don't know but I told you anything about that I had received
it anyway and that I didn't dare say no eh because then maybe they would
Shoot me etc.
eh and it was just something I said about this s gun I don't even know reasons
was because i said it with ants well it was because i don't even know myself just
threw me out something okay in in your first hearing like that
Have you described it as when you come to this place and this then stands
On page 473 in this paragraph is the longer paragraph that I just read then eh that
noted that when you come to the scene that it is a police car that drives
past and you need to hide then the criminals came and saw they asked me
what i did i had a soft ergan as i showed and they went from there and
then describes like you were in the forest for three hours went to the apartment and took
break this box and then then these criminals came back then and took
you and this abuse took place so there have you described it as you should
directed this soft gun at any person on the spot also eh I said that
I did not show it that I directed it but it still does not true I do not have
even had me on a sedve evening okay but why do you pull with that roller me
don't know no i actually don't know at all
why me
Eh
so you describe it a bit similar and it's in the middle of the page
487 and it was then that I read around the very time then that
Sebastian goes 2330 to the hydrogen was there for maybe one to two hours before he
crushed the box to the away it again describes that you should put a police car and
hidden you in the woods and that people wondered what he did there then it took hold inan
he found back too he hid all things in bush at the gate that you
waited and bite
he thinks they called their guys for people stood ready since when Sebastian had
taken the gate door so you also describe it as you encounter people who
Wonder what you do there and that you then crush this gate and then then become
to the captive eh yes i don't know why i have
told about this gun at all no eh but this with
that they were standing out outside and waited but not either I guess they woke up
because they held this bang probably or not woke it up
gone another period of but February 18 with you and there you tell you
a lot also then about this soft air Gunnen and you were a bit into it that
what you said then that is not true it was just something like you
said and what what are you thinking about then what are the tasks that you have
left as you now want to back off you said for something what is it for
details that you mean you have left as you now no longer want to stand by
But before that I am not really
eh you have described in all previous interrogations as you have a softgun on
you eh okay yes and it does even in this fourth hearing it is first now
here today as you say you have never had any softgun on you etc. and then
I wonder what why have you left the information that you would have had one
Softgun on you probably like me don't even miss why because it was like that
a long time and I was tense but I guess it was because if I said I
had a soft on me that I showed it to someone so it would indicate that it
was a reason for them to try to stop me from lighting on this
the apartment that they would then follow me and be ready you understand
eh because if not had directed a gun or shown the soft to them they would
may not be present at all
or near this pot so I certainly wanted to make it sound like it
was why they wanted to stop me because that's why they foal after me you
understand what i mean no i actually don't really think
that I understand how you mean but I can explain better than you etc eh I think that
that I told you about that air soft it was because they were if I showed one
airsof for them so maybe they would call their friends and maybe look for me
And maybe it was there for so he stopped me before I would do it
In some way there no but that's what you mean here today yes yes it but
I don't even know myself but I think that's what I meant
If I were to get okay guess
Mm eh
What it has also come up in this fourth hearing brand new information
and also information that you don't seem to be stuck to today if you understand what I
then mean eh yes that we were two pers and stuff yes yes no we weren't two pers were
self because that was a task too
As you came here in the very last hearing that you would have been with
you any possible fellow jaid yes but that was what I reacted to
You didn't tell us about this today now no because it is not true that I said so
was because it was another at Siss's home that you sit with he said to
me that you can say it because it sounds better then then you might just get
Assisting for preparation That was why I said so mhm okay so you mean
that you got a advice from someone else at the Sish home to about leaving it
the task in interrogation yes
Okay you understand that it will be quite difficult to eh to know what information you
times in these different hearings it understands 100 % yes but
eh as I said I tell you the truth now you then you will believe what you want
But then at the site anyway what you do
you you crush without and you go in but this is only one as well as planted for
that it should look like you have tried to implement this and then should you
blame that you have come up is that I will understand you as well as that
that which happens and happens
where
Eh I wasn't going to talk so much about about what
late but eh about how long would you describe
that you are being beaten and robbed by these people who then as man
Meeting you It is difficult to mention time perception in such a hot situation
Yes but eh it felt all the case like 20 minutes yes since i don't know if it was
less no it may as well have been five minutes but it felt like 20
minutes okay eh and what to say how to be interrupted
the whole eh police want to drive past
okay and then what happens then eh when they run away with my phone
I call a friend so we are outdoors but i don't think i called he then i think
M wrote to him and snapped with him for some what has happened to eh though
I don't remember no but I remember that I called two in the apartment etc. and
that I called someone too in the apartment okay and what is your thought
around to call 112 then eh yes why do you call 1 t because I
bleeding pretty much and i need help m
Mm and what happens then there will be some ambulance
Yes, the police will also yes what do you say to the police eh I say hello then then
around what has happened to eh they take me to the car to hear me etc. eh they
Asking the same question several times first tells them that I rt for my HVB
home i boros a friend then start asking more questions eh and i would rather not
Report, among other things, and then there are sometimes information that you should have said
then that it should have something to do with any drug sale or
similar who had gone wrong yes quite frankly I actually don't remember that I
have said that no
okay and yes how do you go about when you try to get back to
the apartment then eh I google on g attack etc. and but
I find nothing I go to find.se trying to find but I find no one
Apartment tied to it or any address I mean no eh so in the end so
i call bare tv okay so that search happened before you call 1 to tv yes
mm
Do you get any questions from the police around that apartment yes they asked me what how
it looks in there yes eh but it is not at this point what I mins
I believe this on my first interrogation etc. after they have searched through
apartment eh and then i tell me i was in the apartment i see someone
plastic gear s that looks like V done to keep Ven eh and I see a gun
on the ny table eh and I tell you a little how it
the apartment looks sofa what the sofa is what the bed is and a bit like that
Mm okay i thought there was also a task in these events the report about
Like you tried to confuse the cops around where this apartment or where
This print the apartment was somewhere what yes it is true
okay
I leave this part a little neighbor and jump back to this gun
And the weapon
eh and did you see something more weapons related in this one
the apartment v there bullets in this plastic thing in the plastic stuff yes plastic box
What was the box it was a box that looked like I don't know but when one
opened the box so you saw that it was like this what is it not called cotton type
frigolite type that was adapted for guns because i saw pistol pressure
impressions there if you remember from still images of this movie I showed you saw
something black that lay on like the living room table that I call a
gun bag is the one you describe that low bag yes or a weapon box then
perhaps rather based on your description etc. it is the one you mean that was black
Okay
eh I perceived you as you said you didn't think this one was real
that you assume it is fake yes and why did you assume it eh because it was
Something that stings out in the pipe and I didn't think real guns look
so eh but i have seen airsof guns that look so mm eh so I ant
was fake okay eh would you say you have good
Knowledge and check weapons no you have any special weapon interest not one
Interest I have shot with a weapon on a shooting range once yes eh with
Also some videos in my snap with such airs' guns as I am me jokes a little
with so mm it is not a crime related it is just an ordinary image that man
Sent to my regular friend okay you think it's cool with weapons eh I
thought it then but now i don't think so okay
eh do you know anything around
After all, you have been asked about what kind of gun in interrogation was remembered
you have been able to answer about what it was Glock 25 on it so I assumed it was
A GLOCK 25 mm It is also what you have said in interrogation should I say
eh and as we went through then based on NFC when they have gone through this phone
or the phone this weapon so it was cut off and so it was
Tagged as Glock 25 on this fittings package
No but you read there on the yes that you played with then as you have described played
and played yes yes that you kept in and mantled at some point it is true
yes
eh and exactly how would you describe what is
what you do in your handling with this weapon I already told me I I
I draw mantles the mm eh I take a picture eh I press this button
so that it goes back again mm eh yes then a few minutes later so i would
Take it up again because I had nothing better for me since I saw it was
Though a bullet in the barrel that was completely fucked mm eh and then I thought I r away
But now I mean then like that it we have an opportunity as you you mantle it
But you pick it up again and then you see like this ball is stuck
Yes, okay
eh you have told you that you should have done a little more with this weapon in
interrogation also eh what did i say you have told you that you
have done a little more with this weapon than just what you have described now in
interrogation yes it is not true what did you say it is not true that is exactly what I
have done with it okay then maybe I perceive you wrong then but then I would
want to read because I mean that it deviates and that in the first hearing so is
it a task in the middle of the page
eh and it is you yourself then that makes an addition to reading and in others
the piece there it says another thing at the beginning v that I played with the gun I
brought it up loading it twice took a video that was what I did
called and said a bullet was stuck and he said it was quiet so that
do you describe that what we twice you load the n I loaded it so that
I loaded it twice eh when I meant I loaded it once when
I filmed etc. and when I would charge the time after that was when I noticed
that it was a bullet that was stuck I
again okay eh in the same one because otherwise I didn't have
been able to notice that a bullet was stuck unless Dr. Back it again
Okay it is through your handling that like this bullet stuck eh yes okay it
Didn't get stuck before but there was something that happened when you were doing
the
Yes eh in the second interrogation on the page
486 Prime Crime DSE NEXT EH The piece North at the bottom eh so is a drawn like this
Sebastian saw a weapon he doesn't really remember but think it was a Glock 20 he
touched only one weapon there were several weapons but it came since Sebastian touched the weapon
Pretty directly he played with what he took out the magazine took in the magazine loaded and
Took some pictures as well as video he held the handle and mantled and you write
It as if the weapon was lying at the balcony door there was a table it was completely open and
It wasn't charged He never loaded with bullets but maybe someone
walking mm so it is described as you have done a little more than that you
describes yourself with this weapon that's exactly what I said now
As I have done with nothing else
Okay
I was thinking in the first company the hearing so also gets a question about what you were thinking
We don't use it so I don't know then it looked real and I said yes it saw
After all, it looked obviously genuine but I didn't know if it was genuine airsoft
Pistols also look autumn okay but why do you assume here today that it was
fake to assume and guess I don't even know if it was fake I know now I
Know now I know it was real considering you tested them yes but
I thought what did you think there and then there and then I didn't know I assumed
assumed it was that it was fake but the first n right when I saw the one I
saw that there was something that stuck
Out that what I know of my knowledge so don't usually stand out anything in weapons
No
Okay maybe come back to it
late
eh if you can only explain this when and how are it you regret that you
is going to do the job m I regret immediately when I met this girl on
Central station okay
eh so it was not right there at home then when the friend as you say then
have taken this and your behalf no, so they tried to hype me that
first saw burning equipment when I thought I might yes maybe burn
Someone's clothes that I may have used in any crime I know I don't know
Not what I was thinking MHM I didn't even know I would do this
I don't know why I would regret it on some clothes for 15,000 that is not
even a crime no okay but when got you mean that you found out what it
where exactly you would do then mm it was so it was on the way to Stockholm when
I was in Sundsval on my way to Stockholm Yes then I found out that would lit
on an apartment okay but then they said someone would open eh pot to me so they
all the time changed what it would be what it would not be
try to make me want to do that
Okay so this as I read then around in previous interrogation that you have told you
like you or work goes out into this group and you take in spirit then
it was quite detailed what it was to do but you mean that
that it wasn't without you just thought it was something else to be fired
At InIS so I think I didn't even know when they immediately when I got there in the bu
my friend wrote that you wanted to do what they said so and so would burn
Equipment etc. Okay
eh and what is it that does feel that you like continuing or what to say
that you are in this apartment you receive these things I have seen eh v
What happens to people eh I haven't seen but I know what happens to people
14-year-olds through 14-year-old has died for such little stuff or small stuff
I don't know what they have died for but they have died etc. you I think and I
with even older I sit here so they have my name they have my last name they
even have my third surname n they look up a bit careful where mm you can
they can find out what my family then came to peace at
everything but what do you think when you tell you the way you do here
today i mean then it comes out of everything now that you never intended to do
this and you don't think it will be even worse then that you had intended to
try to deceive them eh shall i let the thing
done yes but I was thinking of holding on to this then the version as you have
left earlier the same it is the true version yes but I think like that
Here you choose to tell the truth now you say but I think then the risks
behind telling the truth that is what has made you choose not to
tell the truth earlier just sit inside sis and
Hkt what did you say then when I was thinking like this I didn't know how it was
Inside Siss or sit inside the detention or seated in custody I knew but that
sitting for a long time now it feels like i don't know the world is gray i can
Not even I can't even call my friends etc. yes I would rather call mine
friends and obtain a protected identity than to sit inside than to sit inside yes where
Do you mean you would sit inside somewhere yes I don't know in the last in one
years yes i came i might get a year i don't know but no matter what it is
As well tell me I can only get protect you identity if it is so that
It is needed but I have not mentioned any names eh so it should not even be needed
Actually but you think you you won't have to be on SIS anymore jo
Of course if you tell me I have LVU so what will be the difference then if I come
it stands for something then it says where you have read somewhere page 471 pretty
far down
Mm yes how do you know eh that it was that kind of of ammunition say these i
had eh i had nothing to do so i checked everything how many 9 mm was
Type four type three 32 and TV 38 and then there was another ammunition yes and how
looked the carton yes when you buy a gun so you probably get one that sounds
Like you have a very good squeeze on this with ammunition anyway I have
not so well pinched on ammunition but I don't know how I might have
Good squeeze on ammunition if you I do not know but as
said I checked through because I still had nothing to do and I know that
You get such a box when you buy guns because I have seen this on
Youtube memes or whatever the hell it is called okay how come you can
answer so detailed on these questions i don't know since it was detailed i
don't even think it was so many or them but maybe it was i don't know but
It was about so okay thank you I have no more questions no ok ok eh drill bro
Well thank you very much Sebastian you you asked me to tell
you were on a Hb home yes etc. and so you accept this
the mission or your friend does it but it also means that you in some way
also do you accept eh thus I accepted d accepted eh thus
Actually in itin I don't want to do it but I suppressed it so it felt
Like I wanted to do it and as I said told me equipment so I knew
not even that was any rise I would do okay what did you think or
You mentioned earlier could be clothing such as burning clothes or
How yes the one who wrote to you we like this
The client in what way he or she wrote he wrote like this
He tried to hype me so he tried to make me really want to do
It said like this yes 15,000 since he stepped up eh like what I would do eh late
he told me yeah that's good you I don't make but h tried to hype me like
Mm
okay you have someone or if we say you as a person are you easy and convince
or yeah actually one should be completely honest m there is there is some reason
to why it is that way it might be because i have adhd mm
eh maybe i don't know adhd it i haven't got my medication for a good while
because e okay but what about adhd is something that affects
Just how you make decisions for example yes it yes it affects after all
concentration and of course it affects quite a lot of impulsivity yes how are you
with that you are impulsive yes yes, actually etc. and how was it with medicines then eh I
have not received medicine in a long time for eh i use cannabis on my hb home eh
so they chose to remove my od hair medicine so I have not received it later
D If we talk a little about about Stockholm you come to Stockholm you
TAKING FOR SA you you took previous train or what did you say yes I took
A yes I took a previous train because I
Was pretty stressed and I just took the first train to go to Stockholm
or Sundsval and you had received tickets through
email to an address where your name appears or how yes but you did not take
that train or bus like the ticket why eh without you took it earlier as
said I was stressed I didn't know I I don't know I was pretty tense
I just took the first train I saw as much in the moment's case I saw that it
comes earlier so i didn't think i just took it eh even though my ticket
probably didn't work on that train but they controlled never had you
been in Stockholm earlier reach eh no is the first trip so
Yes in that case I stay there thank you so much and none no matter are no questions I
any eh and no danger to myself either
mm When you stand there you know where you are going then you remember this name that you have
got eh yes i remember it was kumba or kimumba or something like that
Mm and you will find that name no
How come then that you could not find the name so I am not
afterwards when I get into the stairwell so I see that not so name
on the doors so even though I had been looking for VIK UMBA so I did not have
found it unless I had been less stressed and actually Viljat do it so
Had I might have looked at any note or something or googled or
something you would have been less stressed if you had wanted to make it no I think
not that okay i think n i had been more
stressed if I had wanted to do
it and you walk around where you do not find the name of the doors you will see you
should be up the tube to the door I actually don't know I just assumed it is
greater chance that his door is further up the stairwell at the bottom with TKA on
that there are several
floors okay
eh how would it make any difference how would you imagine it
that will then know that you have had this one
Gasol type where you call the police the police may play the area they put in
that in some kind of preliminary investigation eh then sees it lay there okay it was
you saw in front of you eh that they would do it
Yeah ok thanks fl questions
Mm I have any supplementary
Eh i was thinking about just this with that you told me when you find out
on this job or not I read a little neighbor from from this first
the interrogation eh but there is also a task in this other
the interrogation and eh which is October 16 thus starting on the page
485 A task that is on page 488 and the second last eh paragraph there
Back back to before all for heard lance note note that Sebastian
find out the job on Tuesday the same week they said he would do already in
beginning yes they have not done anyway they said i would burn equipment
What did you say they said it would burn equipment okay so you are stuck to it
That it was what you found out before you go to Stockholm then yes
mm Then I have nothing further thank you no there is reaching fl
Asking then we finish
The hearing Yes Questions Complain Starts by asking questions or do you want to tell
myself by the way yes I can very much do make it perfect eh then
I think I account because I experienced then these deeds
and handed over it I have done it is nothing that I deny eh but the purpose
by buying and purchasing all these things eh is as I understood it then
would be used for a workshop that we had talked about for about a month's time
Before I bought all these things then and it was me and my friend who right
Maybe already know, I work with cars eh both on as well as the work itself
where I get salary for it and at leisure time where I am in the process of cars
and i mecca on cars and it's like it's my hobby
that if you say so that it is my life circulating around as well as we had
after all, talked for a long time me and my friend that should we not take and fix one as well
garage space like yes but we can be there and mecca on our cars when we bought
some car and we can sit there and polish and yes but keep on by cars you
know take it easy in the evenings grill during the summers as well as as a small
Hobby workshop where we can be at So no one here's no business
Like where we should sit and have customers and so on but to our own for our own
Interest then so he sounds great but we we should control it and so
So we can start moving in and keep up with our things in there
and the current day when I mined exactly what day it was when I bought
all these things I have for me that it was the fourth or fifth there
somewhere eh those those days I was on all cameras as well and I
Was at work then around 13 40 45 the time I would end at 16.30 eh so wrote
me to my friend eh then as I had talked to the workshop if I told you
he you I am free after work today i have no plans eh shall i go and
buy these as we talked about these gloves and and further things
Then for the workshop he said yes really well but you can buy a flush liquid and so
Furthermore, you can also buy this and this then s me but you send a
shopping list just so it becomes easier so there will be no mistakes like so send
something in case I feel we need it as well as I expire
from buying the things you ask me to buy when he said perfectly so he send it
here the shopping list and we talk a little about those things just eh then after work I
I end up going it would be there at Södra somewhere south Stockholm at
Haninge held eh so I go and yes but I go to the car theme you see you have after all
Everything like prosecutors has produced everything at the case there so I
go around I buy all these things and then I get an address he
Says yes but goes this address then like then I guess the garage
Lying there nearby somewhere eh I go where the plan was that I would
Go there and like check out the garage and yes but be left there for a while and
see like yes but this is our new place we should be on eh but some things
had taken a little longer and shopping some things had taken a little more
Time than counted and I would meet my girl right afterwards so that I go
to this address then there is a girl eh she came and met me she stood
at the turning zone and met me where she had such buildings or not building clothes
Here the workshop and then she points a little towards the apartment complex where she
says yes but it is over there somewhere so yeah it is not like
exactly where she said no it is type two three thus reach some bit of walk so okay but
But you I probably won't be able to accompany you and like to see the things so that
You may take things now so you will surely meet me there within the days
Like I will surely come to the workshop I will be a blame I will be there
a while too eh but i won't be able to today so i gave her things and so
did I go and meet my girl at McDonald's afterwards and so I want to
also add that because I looked at the prosecutor's case present that that eh
There was information that I would have been near that location of one
unclear reason it stood the day after eh but i just want to add that there was
a PM from the police there and that had the police written that I had been at
my girl's address the day after and i'm about four to five times per week
So that was a pretty clear reason why I was near that place
And I wouldn't say it was nearby it's a pretty good bit
From where I was like but yes what I just want to say that I was there
something like that I have not known that there has even been any apartment like someone
of my friends have had access to or something like that I knew it was
This would have been your garage and that's what I have known about the whole
Here's so thanks mm great gets the flag
Ask questions etc. I just thought for formal sake this phone as
You have seized from you It is your phone exactly and it is you who
used it between the FDE and October 6 exactly
eh signal found you installed on this phone yes you can say
something about that application why have you had it it is one one in
the amount of communication apps that I use to chat with friends and
similar yes you know it is encrypted it is nothing I have laid
any extra thought of i i have over 30 communication apps i have whatsapp
Snapchat Instagram Signal as well as everything possible so it is one in the crowd only
Okay so there has been no such reason behind that you have just that
Application no absolutely not no no eh is it alias l hamilton do you know
to it yes it is my mm why just that name sorry why just that name
Hamilton or Hamilton it's one that is a formula 1 driver yes and I am
Giant enthusiast as said by cars and driving a car and so on so it yes but
some kind of idol you can say okay but why have you not used your own name
I thought no it's pretty funny as when playing video games that's pretty
Sad to choose your own name as you are a little inventive so m okay
I still thought you had such a means of communication you explain as was
Therefore I wondered why you choose a different name than your own name then for
That usually comes you with friends yes and they know who you are
Like okay so it's a funny thing just there's no extra important it
Eh you found some then signal chats m in this phone eh
And you can't see anything what you have written, but I mean that this
is incoming message to you is true yes is this message
as you have received yes yes eh eh and there are then among other things
an alias kill all mm can you tell us about it it is an acquaintance to me yes it is
An acquaintance to you yes who is it that I do not want to go into now in that
We are sitting here today and there are such serious suspicions so I do not want to yes but
risk my own security and or my own
describes as is this friend that you have talked about this garage and or
This workshop yes but just okay so it was you two who communicated around
that yes so this shopping list then as you describe that this friend sends
it is the shopping list that we have seen then that you had everyone then sends to your
signal just mm okay eh and you then describe that you should
make these different purchases for it to go to this workshop etc. what what
Do you think about these different things it is both as well as gasoline
flushes the liquid and gasoltub so what should it be used for yes but the fine I
thinks there are pretty good explanations eh gasoltub a partly we had talked
Fl days before when we talked about the actual construction of the workshop we had
Talked about but damn what a nice it had been and like fixing a grill there
And just like yes but soft in summers on summer evenings as well as take it easy and
so that all the things I bought gloves we use when we work on
cars eh mask it has that when you are to solder or weld something
There are normal things that are found in any workshop to spora fluid uses
we wipe off greasy surfaces etc. there are like no weirdness with it no
Okay
eh you have received a lot of questions during the preliminary investigation of police etc. what
Have you answered when I have said no comments on all mine for mm how
Will it see no I simply don't want to sit to speculate or talk about
some other people when I don't know what has happened I know what I have I
What time we are living in right now and eh you have heard still not told about
someone else in any way he might be able to answer clearly to the question thank you eh as
said I don't want to sit and speculate or talk in interrogation you have heard what
that has happened to other people it can be misinterpreted as I say that one one
person has written to me and so on and yes but that it comes out that
that it gets wrong in some way so I have chosen to keep it on
secure the page only and see no comments but I am giantly gotten to
All your questions here etc. Okay It's not that you customize your details
based on the preliminary investigation that has emerged it is a hypothesis that you have
But that is a question no but that it is not that is not true no that is true
not no no okay eh this car then this bmw car yes
eh is that your car it is my car yes yes okay is someone else who usually
Using it No No Okay eh you talked anything about you
confirmed as you would come with any gray BMV MM when you told you
When you said that you would go to this place that you thought was then it
Here's the place of this workshop when you made your purchases so you said you
Confirm that I am coming with a gray BMW no I said the girl knew I
would come in a gray bmw my friend knows what car I have so he has
probably said that one that yes but there will be someone in a gray bmw okay
Mm you i t then thought about your attitude i have relied on
Some of these chats yes eh from signal it also has in a hearing like
been held with you shown when an image appendix on what to say some
more chats that extend then still over the fourth then but that
is a little longer text back I thought if we would look at them absolute eh for
After all, you write in these, then certain things then, then, then, then, that you
Should fire in
The mailbox just those cats I saw they have they have a tism here
If they are in Chat, we may be able to look if there are several you should go through or
Should you show off them I was going to show up because it's a little longer side than
what has been invoked since before so I thought I can connect and
show
76 and is then on page 576 so 576 to 580 is also invoked then
And it is partly then the same signal chats that I have looked at before
But there are some
More
Here, for example, is then the fourth at the top, there is some Dark Wader who
then writes to your signal what is Dark Wader Eh as far as I know so have it
Here these chatting nothing with my criminal suspicion that I sit here for
otherwise yes otherwise other criminal or no other that does not have this
The suspicion of doing okay
Eh you sometimes talk that Dark V writes sometimes that it is fat with Aina
in JB in the evening where the fourth
Yes but that has nothing with anything criminal to do
at all do you mean no it is a statement from his
side ok but i thought like this v what did you think about what he wrote then he
have well informed me that there are police officers in Jordbro but like okay I
cannot find that there is something no no I do not know what to say about it
It does not concern any criminal or any suspicion so as well as okay if we check
here then it is this one then kill everyone then this friend that you describe as
then writes at 13 o'clock where the fifth can buy gasoline food and one
Map Tradd Brother etc. What is Trad it is Tramadol Yes okay what would it too
to this workshop or no as I said eh I have admitted a
Talking here etc. and there has been information anyway that it should have been found
Tramadol then perhaps then as the performer would use mm no it is
Nothing such a tramadol it was found home with me so it was tramadol then
petrol it it was the same day so it may have been a part of this one
the shopping list then okay yes but thread what is it an abbreviation for tramadol it is
Tramadol etc. Then it is written a minute later or shit in the thread bar food soda
and gasoline and a fifth sutt etc. what is Sut Sutt is hash etc.
Okay so what does this concern then I can yes so I I have nothing
memory of what it means eh he talks well about buying any m hash
or tramadol similar okay so it is like no i can't i can't
remember but there are a lot of people who just sit at home and like to smoke on
and take tablets like so I don't know what it is about actually no
Okay then you answer something we don't really know what but the response will be haha
But brother guy takes you Talle Hah Talle what is it then mm
Okay have you answered then back something about tramadol because he responds to
that way or what and what guy do you talk about no i probably don't
answered you can see that he has not said anything after I have written it
occasion or something that he specifically means at the time you have been
something internal joke possibly or something and that is what I want to come
up to there when you go down and scroll when it says this about
the apartment and so on eh no I get where I think I take it
I ask the questions so yes eh so that you mean that it is not always
so that you have answered in this thread it is so I should understand it in some cases
maybe you have answered but in many cases so you have not answered at all because you
working while m etc. then I also think it will be pulled out
quite rough context when you only see one side of a conversation so that
Man man I buy what it looks like I absolutely understand what it looks like eh
that if you read only one page then I understand I understand what it looks like
Had you been able to see my answers, you could have understood much more thoroughly V what
What why you have the opportunity to explain your weak yes but exactly I want to carry
just want to present it so that you know about it but after it in the chat so
what he was abroad we at that time mm and he had complained about
his neighbors who were the ones he had rented any apartment at something
apartment complex or similar as well and he had complained day in and day out
to me that this damn i i would come down here on vacation and so
And so I have neighbors partying all day and all evening and the ones they do
Lots of noise and I can't cope I get I get so damn angry and so on so
So should we laugh like what I said damn what a hard holiday you got
Like and so he writes where you also see down that he writes that this is how
eh that but I would have shot if I come in haha I will burn through
the mailbox and so this was an internal joke that he has some sort of
rough ad hd so that when he becomes excited or wants to joke something like that
does he go in just like him drive all in now now want to make a great fun
jokes like so he is about that when he asks you know something that burns
A lot of it is not a serious question, so any person knows after all
that gasoline burns is good it is not that I have given him an answer like him
have not known when you say you know something that is burning a lot it is like
an ironic question a rhetorical question to yes but fuck use gasoline if you are to
burn on this apartment there where he was abroad as well as if you want
disturb the neighbors like that so it was a joke it is not that he does not know
what is burning a lot mm but he is no longer abroad you said it was
When he was abroad he was abroad he was abroad current time I have
been detained for six months so I don't know where he's okay
Eh but then my question then you answer that message yes yes and what do you answer
Then gasoline is okay because then the next will burn well yes etc. but you mean to
it still this fun context then that he is abroad and disturbs
these neighbors who, like that yes, the rough joke between thus
Thus which person who then if if someone asks you know something that burns
A lot you see gasoline and then you say it burns well as it can
after all not being anything but jokes who doesn't know that gasoline burns well as well as mm it
is so i okay and then comes next then lighter fluid with bees do you think it
Works etc. and you are part that he wants he wants to draw the joke anymore he
He likes as well as exaggeration you see the tatters below also as coming
like you will surely come to them but the tatters that are there under it
is just an extension of the joke so that he likes to take in when he
he jokes he is he he gets excitedly simply as we can talk about a good
dish he starts like and yes but he should pull out what he will pull it out so
long and that's how he is it is his personality as well and then comes then
Next with that apartment you've written something in between I think
Yes i have weak memories that i wrote that like this but v where was it you lived
Like it is townhouses or villa in apartment, he replied and apartment so
Then I realized that yes but they are wall to wall with these hard neighbors
Like mm and then we get a little closer to what you have mentioned yourself
then there at 1336, then die all no if it was so I could go into
the apartment I had shot hah etc. exactly and then I took
already understood that this was about our internal joke as well but there you can
also see then that he writes hahaha as well as yes but I had shot about
I could have come in but damn they certainly have so like me to fuck
Burn so and then also that he writes to fire through the mailbox and so
As I have understood it then on the very suspected crime address then
There were no mailboxes so it will be quite difficult to burn through a
mailbox that does not exist mm but did you know about it then sorry you knew about it
Then I can't answer yes, so I still can't know about
These things I bought if they were primarily meant for use
then about shooting because that's how he likes to write there that no if it was
So that I could go into the apartment so I had shot no no I think that
Because where he asked all like this you know something that is burning well and so on and
so on so it may have been so I have said kind of this no but what the hell go
into the apartment and like eh pour gasoline everywhere or it may have been
some draw to the joke and he said yes but I will not get into positions
So like so okay and then then this will fire through the mailbox
Mm What do you answer to it then or do you answer I don't remember v it all that
this in a joke context so i don't remember exactly what i have joked in with
Like what words I have chosen but there has probably been something in the style of
Yeah haa like okay g do your thing as well as mm and i understand he jokes
he would not be at a fire to burn an apartment abroad it is, after all
So as I interpreted anyway this is a raw joke only
Like how do you usually say dark humor etc. since we 13338 where yes because I want
something that continues to burn etc. It's just continuing on you to
This rough joke that all it is the same time you see it is, after all
just a 30 -second difference or whatever it is like that, so it so it
It is the context as well as then comes a mining where between 13338 and 1345 on
What is seven minutes seven eight minutes and when he writes it yes why I
were h who continues to burn eh either I have not answered or so I have
just written hahaha okay reach similar like but then have that conversation
died out and as I said I was at work during the time I customers occasionally they
Coming in every now and then so I have been able to have a two customers as well as and
Then when he writes A you can fix such brother that is the answer to one of my
Questions and then I write to him around 1345 when I write to him just
it heard i am free today after work and then i start talking about it
here the workshop so should I go shopping these things we were talking about
To the workshop I thought I might go and buy gloves and like
Yes but worms and stuff in when we are going to solder and the like and then he writes yes
can you fix such brother buy flush bag and gasolo tube too and i know after all
We had talked about this grill a few days before too so that yes it is
Absolutely I fixed like MM had you why did you buy no grill sorry
Why didn't you buy any grill but the grill was rode that one like I had understood
That but he was abroad how had it come there when he has been blushed around
It seems like he had the girl who received the goods so that it
Isn't that he he doesn't have people he knows here in Sweden eh since at
141 where bridge takes out from ATM etc. What what are you going to take out from ATM
No idea I have not taken any money from reaching ATM so that he
maybe had some chat while and because it is completely out of context it stands
only 141 there are no medlands the one who in the vicinity before or after that has any
connection to it that possible he has written it yes but in the wrong chat
possibly or or the like and, as I said, still should be deleted that
I was at work and I'm not like the screen and checking out I get notes
Constant and so plus I have signal so I have signal snapchat Instagram
All these notes are suspended with me I don't have notes on I have only
Notes on on, for example, ordinary SMS or May or yes but things that concern
the job then then social media I go in when I have time I go in and read
means when I have time it may have been that I haven't read the message okay
these purchases when I understand it as you go on, after all, that you have done all
these purchases that I say that is to say both then at Biltema Eh that it
is the IA MAX purchase then of these pizzas among other things that it is also this one
Refueling on Ingo EH and then eh of this gas tube etc. Many of those purchases
Implementing in cash yes how will it no I usually have contact cash
It is like there are no major sums as I said I am doing cars
I do a lot of car deals sometimes pay the buyers in Swish sometimes they pay
cash and i usually have cash on me okay so this message then that
You should then encourage the stout from ATMs it has nothing to do with these
upcoming purchases then that will be in cash no but I have not pulled out anything from
ATM I have not done what you see on my card purchases that I do not have
pulled out something so i have i have i already have cash on me mm eh
then at 1523 where I give your address then take you back what you laid out for plus
your rush plus 5k that you have posted to loo just eh what is rush rush it
can be a purchase a car deal a service it is all possible and as I said my
life circulates around to do yes so a completely normal day I can write
To my friend you I can't go here you can go and buy exhaust pipes for me
or can you go and buy this battery for me or would you be able to
go and solve these things to me or so can he ask me you I need to go
and buy this these these rims you could go and pick
up them to me and just leave them here like and yes but when we do such
Business it might be that yes but I post these 5000 to you so k
back as late and so on it is no massive sums it is not so
that I have lent out SEK 100,000 it is like that so 5k it is 5000 it
is 5000 exactly and that it is so we usually hold on about d that in the days
Like when I have free when I have the time we are doing business here right
left like mm okay then some addresses come and then it stands 17 k it
are 17,000 that's 17,000 but I have no memory that I have been on it
What I haven't been where I haven't picked up SEK 17,000 No Okay I think after all
for itself the message before it is only half an hour before but then writes
I, after all, that person to give you an address and that you will then get back
that you have laid out and plus then for any rush that I mean stands for as well as a
assignment EH and then plus 5000 that you should have posted no as I interpreted so where
that address that address Skytten's street where I left the items to the garage
Yeah okay so that was where you mean then that is the one who comes this one has like
nothing to do with it as it can another send to the wrong chat should I
understand it so yes because if if I had sv so I cannot say that it
are there any answers from him on my answer or then if you understand what I
mean it it it is completely out of context there is not what I have written and
Ok but you don't know where you would have it somewhere probably to
the garage spot but i didn't do it so that it may have been that I to that
I may have answered I will not be able to or similar etc. Okay eh and here will
the then this shopping list that we were talked a little bit about and then it is after all
gloves bandanas then what would it use yes it when you solder when you
Welds sometimes we go moped in the evenings it can be nice to have a
Bandana on them like so we usually have it when we keep on and mecca and
rides mopeds and so and similar prim eh freezer then and cola and and sigg and
snuff exactly and that is what I think confirms that I have not been
part or understood that it would have been to any crime scene not in my
wildest imagination I might think pizzas are used for a burn
or that one would use cola for a burn and then also there are none
Small quantities it is like six big pizzas there are three large cows it is
Six liters of cola etc. Who drinks six liters of cola on an evening as well as before they go out
If I would now know what would happen if you understand how I
mean this is like this is the amount of stock that you put in
the workshop so we have pizzas and we have coal that when we are not to
Using the grill for example but then we have freezer pizzas we have cola we have as well
we have snus we have sigg it should be just like it should be a happy place on
The workshop it should be like a place you can go there and you can take
it calmly and chew good food and be with friends mecca on cars as well as you know about
you replied to this message shopping list
I don't know I may have written off perfectly as well as yes because when I read late
then the next remedy then from dead everyone so brother thinks of the guy he has in food brother haha
Then it is like you question this exactly with the pizzas around that it
should be purchased exactly and I think it may have been so that I have answered
him there that like this that we have talked about someone who has been to the workshop as
keeping on and advising around there and like clean similar eh I know we had
A couple of phone calls as well around these times I remember saying what time it was
But we had probably received the information that there was someone there as would
have food or similar but hardly he would eat all six pizzas on a
walking okay so it's not like Sebastian sitting in this one
the apartment that you shop for these pizzas that you think about
have food no and now that you still mention my target camera I say I never have
had any contact with him anyway i have never seen that guy
Before I have no connection with him no I I don't know who I have
never had any information from him until I read for the survey okay
eh if we jump down when eh comes a job -related message there and then so
will there be one to message then from dead everyone around there at 1705 brother buy
KVIK Fixed price 145 as well mm what should it be can to the guy who holds
on and RDA around the garage where it is Samsung also charges as we should in
the garage but what is it for guy who prevail around in the garage I can't s
me i know i don't in that guy but it is someone who is on and
Clean there who need a peek fixed price as it is not, after all, some
year s they changed that peek solid price cannot be linked to it as well as that one does not
can thus that it must be linked to BankID and the like as well as so that I
Can't see it should like someone how to say any strange connection
or or the like like he needs we got broom price i'll anyway go around
and buy all these stuff it is not that I would then if he were to
write yes but can you buy a biscuit chocolate too it is not that i would
answer why do you need a biscuit chocolate too no it is like yes i will end
Go around and buy I also buy it fine what was his role there then was
he employed by you all and clean I don't really understand no no no it was
Surely his friend or similar okay it's the same as I because I
was detained type five days after all this so that unless I had been
only me and he according to plan that would have access to this garage
and who is he then you mean kill everyone no but i meant
this one you describe then that would have this comic subscription where yes it
don't know who it is you have no idea who it is no as I said I have mine
friends he has his friends We have mutual friends if I would about
I would write to dead all for example yes but you my friend is going to go there
he doesn't know him okay okay like yes eh new samsung charger too
Mm it is it too to this one
the person or what is it for now should we be in the workshop
Okay eh and then so this person asked to kill everyone then how far have you
arrived at 1745
the job and would buy it like why he asks how far you have
come it is probably the girl waiting for me similar to he question how far I have
come no but i don't understand why did you wait this girl on you why
Could you not just go to this garage yourself I don't know she was
Well where the plan was that I would go there you serrer when he writes how far
Have you come the plan was that I would go there and bring my things with me
to the garage I would be there for a while as well and take yes but were there
Like and hang on for a half hour or similar but I didn't get me
he just hand over things and aka to my girl after because I had after all
promised her that we would meet etc. so he has written how far have you
Come there is probably someone who wonders when I arrive at the garage as well as okay
I haven't kept key to Garet so someone is there and waiting for me with
the keys or corpses thus access to the garage okay
But I don't really understand this when it starts to be tough about time or what you
This girl is connected and will receive these things no no I think that
The plan from the beginning was that she was she was already there and that I would go
there and I would be with her and the other guy when we would be there
like and advised around but i he simply not mm
eh and then there at 181 brother check something only you can cover the face
mm and and it is for what purpose then you just saw that I bought
He had written Bandanas, but I bought this Konam worms instead
Then I told him when I was at Bilt I find no bandanas as I know
Not what should I even buy something like this is how we might be able to buy
Then like when we go on the mopeds or or similar and then he said no
But check just if you can cover the face as well as it will be nice when you
The car when you go like yes but some bags smell bad then you have as well as
Great for the face when you go and it's cold outside on mopeds
or motorcycles then you have something for the face so he said yes but buy something
just so we can have it there and as I said before he gets so excited by some
Things that he wants like yes but we will solve it now now he is really stressed
person and sometimes you have to tell him yes but calm we solve it later but
Now you are still in Biltema as I had I H I was I who had offered
myself and said you are free after work today for a few hours I can fix
This then I think yes but I buy it too I fix it then I bought
Crown masks instead of bandanas then mm okay and then it comes then as we have
been inside a little neighbor on this then the address Sagittarius road 542 eh eh yes as
Well then the shooter's street 540 then ends exactly and you mean that then that
This is where you get information that this is where this workshop simply should
lie so you should then leave these things m in close to and that area
exactly eh and so you describe that like this late
Do you go to the gate yes not for if you check in 1821
Stands in Sagittarius Road 542 where he writes the address of me as I should, as well
But then that I have the address like so that I know where to go late
he writes in 1835 yes bridge park God meets you where you give her five salmon since you go
to the gate I have not met any girl who have I given 5000 until I have not
gone to some gate he writes it 1835 36 where somewhere i arrive
to Sagittarius street approximately 19 10 19 15 It is type 30 35 40 minutes after he
writes it mm i can see no meaning in that he writes to me 40
minutes in advance that yes but I, like her meet you there 40 minutes in advance
i tlk so i can only say he has written it in the wrong chat or that
he has written what I do not know why he has written it but I have not
met any girl I have not given any girl 5000 SEK as or went to
any gate for that matter either no ok but what is it that happens then when you
arrives then when I arrive there so is what I arrive at a
Turnzone where Skyt's street it is located at the far end of yes but no road as well as just one
main road if you call it so it is a turning zone at the far end of a little slogan souls and
So on I arrive where she stands there with her building pants she knows
I get in a gray bmw I go out in the car hey hey is you who would have
things yes but just yes it is just names swear yes but exactly it is he
Like perfect so we do hay here the stuff I say but where is the garage then i
he writes like you couldn't help her haha like mm it was like that
I gave her the matter and so I went mm okay
Eh and then you then write then at the time at 1920, okay brother take one and
a half you brother then there are four salmon left etc. what is it for something you
talked about when it was money we talked about what I know may not have been any
expose some kind of expenses or purchasing goods I do not know if he on he at
any way yes I don't really know that is money yes but it has not with it
Here to do you mean it has enough purchases to do that certainly
It is not with reach it is not as well as that payment for any service or
Similar no no okay eh but then you go to McDonalds
then your yes just meet yes eh how long are you there then do not remember how long I am
where I am well there half an hour I met her and her friend we stood
there took a sigg and bought someone frappe and the like then I went home after
The okay I thought so it was the meeting as it was so in a hurry like
This half -hour meeting you know how girls are you should have promised about
Something so you go there and you are in time okay yes but because I just wonder
If you continue to read in this conversation etc. eh then it seems
be like you have some other conversations there too around 20 o'clock
exactly eh and then you talk about any address, among other things in Sollentuna etc. I
after all if yes any kind of tramadol and I have admitted drug offenses there then etc.
okay
Eh you've heard what I've read about or read about this
the survey that you have done by this alias kill all yes I have
read yes what do you think about it it is deeply alarming that I have had
contact with such a person but that I have not had any knowledge that he
Bear so deeds and that is partly also why I do not want to comment on
something no ok but now that you understand you have after all
understood that these things then as you buy they end up in the end
Here the crime scene they have your finger of pressure on you several of these cans
What do you think about what said it is deeply alarming
someone i know the works i don't know the plaintiff i don't know their
son I think that they have gone through it is terrible I as I want
not be part of any kind of crime gang but now it is so and I had hoped
that during the preliminary investigation it had been cleared up now you have not done so
Now I sit here and then we may say as it is I was going to say about what way
would it have been cleared up then that one had somehow listed that one
had seen maybe chatting i don't know how i how i really thought
Like but eh so you think that if we had seen your answers then on these
messages it had been to your advantage it had not been to your
disadvantage yes mm okay and this one then d all would then you would
say that it is like a close friend to you no it is an acquaintance it is a friend
It is not my best friend it is not my worst friend the one a human
Feel that person has, like put in the shit if you were to tuck so yes
so that I know if I will be at you g all these purchases and t them to this one
the place and then they should then be used in it
here etc. so I think like what what do your thoughts go about it
the person I said before if I have understood this
right so that when I bought things etc. the plan still wasn't that they
would be used for this crime gang without it has come in a later stage
Then I cannot answer whether it is true or not what he has thought if he has
thought he'll fool me like or similar so eh i am as I said i
i'm undead since before i have no connections to anything like this network
or similar and then you can discuss on whether he has wanted to use
themselves out of me because I just have been judged since before and would not have any
kind of span or similar but then yes he has done it he
have done he can stand for it as then then can't so much more i have
Did what I have done too so I have bought these things in good faith
Like okay
eh I think it was if it was on the phone if it was in the analysis of
the phone so there was something initial reaching
initial summary where I read up as any police had written
Eh there was something like you should have had the role of some fixer and
as well as that in such types of deeds it is a statement drawn out of no one
context I like if if you buy a gasoline and gas are counted
As a fixer then I am well fixer but it is not reaching Kell in anything criminal
context no ok but you are also charged for another
DO NOT HERE THE FULL COURT NO NO BUT it also has connection to what should
You say this conflict etc. but I do not think that you are dragging
up it in this case that case is by itself it may be cleared up by it
Thus, they think they are closed to the saw, we must leave to the court think
i mm eh but yes i stand charged but i'm not convicted no not judged before
either no no but okay but then it is like a coincidence that you are in two cases then
has been drawn into it or how should I first it it is a completely different
case if you say so it has a completely different interpretation that case
That case has I have become how you say I have been put in the shit as well as
without my knowledge but that I don't think there is no point in taking
up this I am not convicted of it yet so that it or I I do not know if I
will be convicted of it like that no that it is not relevant no but
You have no connection whatsoever to any kind of criminal network or
gross organized crime in any way no no I just thought it
Will be right what I said mentioned about what you have written when it is this
the review of telephone emptying starting on the page
360 Then it was under the result of the review on the page
364 as the one who has done this then writes that signed the one who goes
Through the Marm Manos phone phone is emptied that case and so you mention a
Kummer and has a certain fittings number what emerges is that Armanda has
The role I would describe as fixer he is the one who buys and
transporting crime tools and food and so
Furthermore, but you mean it is like a glossy statement from thus that
claim that there has been crime tools and food when I have bought the things so have
I did not have intent that this would be used or that it would be a
Crime tool it is not that I have bought something illegal or that I
have, like no but sorry I might be unclear it what he says it is to
That is what he describes as well as in general as he goes through your phone and
Then he writes he is the one who buys and the transit below I will
Document they are there, after all, consider importance to our investigation found in
The phone so then focuses on it so generally he says there are others
things in this phone to indicate that you should be some kind of fixer
thus generally and generally I have already explained that when I did not
am at work or that when i am when i have free time like i don't know what
he interprets as a fixer about buying tires and rim it like any criminal
deed no okay but yes i go around i'm on the block a lot i buy and
Selling things that's what I do I like it's my hobby so you earn a
extra crack on it too mm okay but you understand when you look at them
Here you chat when you see, among other things, you write about it being poured into
mailbox that there is any guy who needs food
eh these purchases do since you have talked then in relation to a fire what
burns well and that it is then left in when connection to this press
the apartment what it looks like mm no i real i drive on it absolute i i
have responded to all the chats and therefore it is pulled out of such a rough context etc.
Had you been able to read what I say or what I write then you could have
understand got a bigger picture of the whole mm and that I buy a cane gasoline
Or then as if if someone writes to me buy coal and pizzas
I don't think of anything criminal no okay
Eh i understand your attitude and explanation for these details
I have no more questions for you thank you g k would you like to ask questions
[Music] mm first a question like this one usually has
a barbecue at a workshop that said it was not just a workshop it would be
Like a Safe Place a Happy Place It was probably a garage I haven't been there as
said I haven't seen the place yet but as I understood it out of the explanation like that
would it be yes but there would be any place outside we have a grill there
We have some sofas in the workshop We take it easy We have music at Mecca on cars
and jaw good food with friends etc. Then I think about this situation
When to hand over these things that you have hand
eh she then says that this workshop should be type two blocks away or
Like just a little bit away mm was not strange then that you did not drove there
And leaves them then, after all, the gasoline tube weighs 8 kg and the can 5 kg
And then flush fluid and all the tangle no as I understood it so did not lay
Two quarters away without me asking when I arrived at where is the garage lies
and said h yes but you you should drive around with the car was a bit like there to the garage
so yeah so that it is like, for example, at home with me then about if only
to give you an example then that if you are going to park the car in the garage then it is
better to go to the garage but if you just have to leave anything in the garage and
she was standing there on the turning zone so she probably came k not that it was a little
weird to hand over things out to her the just such things no ni i
Know it should be used in a garage you knew it is obvious that
I knew it would be to the garage okay eh then it said eh big
parts or part of this chat that it is
ehm era as well as internal conversation and that
It is humor in the MM can you understand that it is difficult to see this humor it
depends on who you ask when I read hahaha so it's humor for me
Okay so when he says eh he says something he would have
shot in that case no if it was so I could go into the apartment I had
shot haaha mm so the thing is that if you could have seen the cats from I
no then it was another thing too eh you said there was someone who would come
and clean up and stuff mm eh but you had no idea who it
This person was no as I said this garage it wasn't just me and that
this is then that had access to this would be a garage like we
can rob out to friends we can be there together or we can be there ourselves
with our other friends and that there are people there like people people there and advise
around and clean up together and like fixing the place to make it nice
mm you call it a safe space what do you mean by how do you call it safe
The seas about if you say so in English as well as a one place where we can be at
evenings hang with friends listen to music mecca on cars that is we
likes to do as we have we have mcked on cars and like held it
that is a nice place to be on it is our hobby it what we like so
As some like to play Padder or Tennis in the free time we like and Mecca
on cars in your spare time okay so I would but so
that I I just want to be clear and mean that Safe Place would not be
any connection to any pressure ice apartment or similar or green quarter
as prosecutors then explained that is not what I mean without safe space
would be a place where we are there and we like to take it easy with friends and have
the fun etc. based on the context we look at now it sounds pretty similar
a pressure ice or bunker cola and pizza and so there something sounds
similar it can not answer but it is not like that
target tree ended eh it can be sometimes hard to find the right words can i
imagine but safe space do you say if i say gathering place is a correct
designation for what this could be that it is a perfect term yes
yes eh and as I interpret you, this is a place where one could
Be able to hang it is true yes yes sees like a youth yard is yes as is this
any professional activity where you will, as well as conduct some kind, thus
professional car repair shop like Mekonomen or similar no absolutely not that it is
No place that we should, as well as receive customers and the like, but we shall MEA
on our cars maybe someone go help any parents car and similar as well
Mm okay so it is it you at the same time as we hang there and jaw
food and like similar and so exactly eh and i was going to snap up on some things
Of what you have told about it, I have answered most of the time on the prosecutor's
Questions eh but eh if we start with this one for that i know you yourself reputation
to and you were careful to point this out too but this one that you connect
up the day after eh that it mentioned as it would be unclear what you
did there m can you just explain some sdare what what was it that happened there
or why did you connect this day after as the prosecutor claims yes
exactly I think that an unclear reason is, like it it is
Not an unclear reason it was in the memorandum that the police established there
that I was at home with my girl that night and that yes it depends on v what
one interprets as proximity but I do not think that distance is a closeness to
Like it is in Haninge yes but there are two completely different places so I I
have not had any connection to the address then as no maybe I get
reason to show it since we get to see okay eh and so were you on it as well
The plaintiff has been sitting here everyone is not sitting here but you have received
read the names and heard what they have told us and so there you feel the plaintiffs no
I don't know the plaintiff when I read the fup so it was first song I
read their name I have no connection to theirs as I interpreted it then that
it is that this would be something real to their sons or similar
I have no one I do not know the son I have not heard his name late
before no and yes I don't know the corpse you have something you have any bad blood against someone in
The family where no no no eh and are you like you are part of any conflict
where someone in the family could possibly be on the other side no I
is not with any conflict at all no okay eh eh but you have eh it has you
yourself told you that you are going with with with a person who according to the police in
All cases are is is a criminal etc. So how do you look at it
The situation thus the thing is like this that I have not received any suspicion that
This person should be a criminal then that he can smoke hash at some point
like and so if it is considered criminal yes then he must be well
criminal in that term yes but that he would like to figure in such gross
suspicions that I have read like so that it is nothing that I perceived
There is nothing that I have seen out of him as well as most of the time I have had
with him it is it that revolves around cars and the like as well as it that it
is deeply alarming indeed but it is as it is where is you upbringing
somewhere I grew up in small little ones there are people there maybe people who
you have eh childhood friends and the like that may have gone wrong wrong path in life
It is very likely if you are going if you are going if you are to start from statistics and
similar then like i can i can not raw because i have friends or
I have friends that I have been hanging out with me when I was a kid who unfortunately has chosen a
criminal path when there are still people
as is not just like criminals at
whole about if you say so criminal full -time as well as it is friends like me
can go out and jaw with them I can go out and a hamburger with them as it is
still friends to me since they commit criminal acts it is
really boring but there is nothing that I can raw because there is nothing I can stand
for and like yes but eh according to what you you didn't know that then this alig
seen killing everyone that that person was involved in something like this
So we'll understand you no no no ok ok eh and this workshop then it has
been up there is no secret that we have had a few days before here eh and then
Has this got your engine interest has had some significance I thought
We should be clear there as well
eh can you describe what it is you work with i work with biro rental on
Arlanda Airport and I can also add then only a little quick to three
days before I was arrested so I had been promoted to manager there too
that it is not that I work there and just like ah as well as lace around
without it it is my goal in life as well as mm okay and on in your spare time you have
after all, been on that you have a big as well as car interest what looks like
Like the weeks out as well as with cars private and vehicles at all
The thing is I have then so far behind I can remember then childhood as well as so
That it is like if the dad should go and change winter tires then I get so extra me
want to follow along like so that what I like cars I am all I do
Like it's Youtube that's all possible and it buys and sells cars
In their spare time, people help with cars help friends with cars so it like
my friends know if there is something they have any question about a car or they
need help with something it is Armando you write to as well as so that
that yeah okay and this with open a garage you can you can just describe so we
So understand how the discussions have gone, etc. mm etc. thus the thing is as
said as you said then that this is not as to the Mekonomer or
Car mechanics Workshop We will open but we have yes for several years before for several years
we have, like yes but maybe sowing in a place or in a parking lot
Like and kept on mecca cars or you have gone to OKQ8 on these wash
Self -Thyr has stood there and mucked and so we said that like but then about
We still do so much with cars we should not, as well as rent into
reach some kind of garage or similar and yes but make it to ours as well as yes but
where we can soft and take it easy and so it was a great idea it we drive
Like we get a grill we sit down there speakers as we have fun it is
what we do etc. okay and when for as i understand you so be this
That, like this garage, was something new now that you had to take this
Can you describe how went how went that discussion to the thing is that I have
not where I have not seen the place but the discussion went to that
here kill everyone when we had talked a month before or in reach month's time and
He says then that we had talked about this idea then he said you I have
found a place as well as we should run on it as well as the like so yes but then
are you sure it runs on it like eh we we don't like talk
ehm mm and what did you know about this garage so did I know and knew we
I didn't have this the world's information about this garage I
knew it was about if we say so here you knew where it was there somewhere it
Low in south but I don't know exactly V now I have the address so nearby
somewhere i yeah okay it was so you perceived yes yes yes of course and and and
Then you have described there that there was someone there and and kept on and cleared and
like that as you understood it mm before and why was it why was that person
There, as I said, he was there and he also had access to here
the garage probably via then my friend then and eh thus when moving into a
garage when to move in where I assumed it was completely empty as well
There was nothing there or so there was lots of shit there from the last owners
Or similar and yes but to clean around as you go where you might be removed
Old oil stains or as well as raises old furniture or setting any freezer
Or similar to the garage this was this was during winter time so that or
Winter autumn then, like the plan, was perhaps to be finished then until
Yes but our slopes there somewhere as well and like so we get started for real
mm okay
eh and and this is something like you
have discussed as i understand you and kill all yes yes okay and era
Discussions have you had you told you that you have had conversations thus we
Either through then signal's call what do I know or and and message
Communication apps just different apps as well and similar yes yes
And both conversation and with okay ehm etc. and the prosecutor has gone through
message so i'm not going to take them up again and ask them to explain it what
is there anything you want to add where you have come up with just in question
If with no I do not want to add them except to prove that one does not see my
Answer as well as that no yes I understand and I note that it does not
is evidently evident about this particular apartment that we are talking about these two
the days eh or the plaintiff in that conversation has it has either
as well as the place like this really happens or the plaintiff's name or
something about they arose in a different way than through through
Conversations I have not received neither this so -called security apartment
or the plaintiff or goal shot to do I have not received
any information at all about something someone
this joke mm mm eh and like how is the jargon between you two how would you
So describe it the way I buy what it looks like I absolutely do when you
puts it in the way I understand what it looks like and then some may think
that what kind of humor is like m but yes to have a dark humor with
Like friends it's fun as it is fun it is so we joke and then
He, as I said he is, like I was at work then and I know how he is he is
He becomes like a he becomes like a child when he jokes he wants to like yes
he wants to go out on the whole joke and like holding on for a long time and then you get
after all, he gives him a little like a little ah hah yes exactly ha as but that he
asking me what burns well mm all people know what is burning well it is
no serious question like gasoline is burning well it knows well but when you get it
where first what to say the first notice of those where prosecutors have
shown like m eh and there is something about what is burning or something to
that way eh like there is something in you
background that you can, as well as refer it to yes yes yes, absolutely as we said we
Had talked not for several days but for a couple of days then before that he was
abroad and he had like the hell what apartment I ended up in all of
places so I ended up staying in a fasting youth gang as I had
Talked on I think it might be snap or phones or similar some
days before and he just had like this but then you drive I can't cope
with this like so I understand immediately because he had talked since before
Just like this damn i'm going to fucking fucking burst up that place but
as well as in a joking way I had I didn't think he was going to real
blast up the place but were on a joke so i can do the fuck no more
Like and then when he writes like that, I take him he is joking
again as well as mm so when he writes it then you understand at one time then
or do you need to think about what it is he is referring to no I don't have to think
after because I understand what he is referring to directly because we have talked about
that before like okay eh and just that might be a stupid
Ask but to be obvious as we have seen you shop these
The products and some things are as Åkl for the displayed so there is nothing
ehm nothing like a receipt or similar that just or camera that you just
have traded these but we these occasions when you have traded this
that you have agreed to as well as at some point there thought that something of
This is to be used for something illegal absolutely not it was after all
The shopping list I followed it and I had read the shopping list as before thus
When I got it I saw but this is the stuff that we use in a workshop
It's no wonder as well as exactly and then so if we go over to it
here when you hand over things eh if we go over to that part then eh so
Like and that is something I have put in mind as I sit now here
today d like thought of what has happened as well and the like and then I came on
That but she had Byggab's pants on it so it means that she has
been in this workshop when the number worked or similar like v was
the interpretation you made yes it was that interpretation yes yes okay
ehm and can you describe a little just so we are as clear as possible because it went
a little faster I thought in the interview but as we are as clear as possible from
when you then when you then stop the car when you go from there how to go
conversation and so much you remember are things friend are the things you don't remember
so do you say that but so much you can remember i understand it t no but i i
Remember I went there as I arrived at the turning zone where I see it stands
a girl there like me going out in the car hi hi eh was it you who had talked
with our friend then like to have things yes it was me like yes what fun have you
been in the garage yes you are there and we a little cold talk as well as about the garage and
similar they are on and clean up and the like so okay here are the stuff blah blah
Bla like me gave her bags and so she said yes but shouldn't you follow in
Like and the like like this seemed a bit heavy maybe but I said no fuck
I don't have time, she said yes but I must carry them herself like she took
the stuff and she went like and we we he didn't talk as much it was well
just a little cold talk i don't feel i haven't met it since before
The only connection we had with each other so that was it naturally
to talk about that thing yes and then you got some questions here from the target bit the tree about
that it would be strange that you left at the turning area and not in
the garage eh and then I was just going to ask one question was you who decided were you
would be seen somewhere no i had got an address and i went there just so
You went there so you might as well have been in the garage yes yes so I assumed
So I assumed that the address there that the garage would be there but so
As I understood her, it wasn't far from there but it was just about
You would drive in there with a vehicle so you would have to go around
the place and it is like a slightly longer detour but if one should leave something on
the place just so it is easier to just stay on the main road and like dropping
off and go from there but this was not something it was not
You who decided if I no no no so I just went there as well as the stuff
Oke okay eh did you experience something strange with
with this girl at the time at the meeting that it was that she was nervous or
something that got it and f suspicions no no no
nothing thus a normal girl a normal conversation as well as yes and mentioned
she something about fire or burn or no no something that way no no
and
eh and i think you did something to hide that you handed over these
things this was something that happened as well as around a corner or thus
somewhere when all or absolutely not so you can say this way for
The first, after all, they leave on a turning zone among the positions complex and as well as
After all, anyone can read it like so it's nothing I hid late
Also I have traveled with my car I have stood as in front of the cash registers I have
gort the things i have like i have not been so i am no professional on
Police work if you say so or professionals on something similar but so if you now
would have planned something criminal so that where one was not standing as in front of a
camera and bought things about if you understand what I mean and like touched and laid
DNA Finger Imprint on Everything But I don't have miss this would be used
to any crime end okay
Mm and how like you got you may have answered a little bit to this but I
shall see if you have anything to say but how do you think now that all this
that it was found at one at a crime scene for it we do not question
No, it is, as I said, it is deeply alarming, thus it the defendant
Dishes the time as well as ok well thank you then I have no more questions etc. F Mag
series or query no questioning thanks eh Robin Hedman Johansson etc. is it is
Someone you know it is an acquaintance okay you can develop in what way it is one
friend yeah okay and what does he do today i have no idea if i sutta arrested in
six months okay if i say he's sitting arrested right now then okay he
have been found abroad but recently came back to Sweden and
arrested that he is then arrested on suspicion of when a murder linked
also to this ftr believed the conflict okay what do you think about it he he
is well suspicious okay have you somehow been in contact with him around the
Here the days I have very possible been yes yes okay in what way pray
This is the general talk like nothing that concerns the suspicion no okay but it has
also been a friend of you it has been a friend yes so it is then dead
all then that one has come up with has had a very large involvement in several of
these different then gang -related cases within this folkrot conflict and the
Here Robin Hedmar Johansson it's just a coincidence that there are two acquaintances to you
but you have no srö any time with fox trot to do as i said i have grown
up in an area where several pieces have or perhaps become criminal etc. but
that they are there and that I can take a hamburger with them at some point it is
nothing like it does not make me a criminal no okay then as I have
understood it anyway so they are just suspects
Okay but it is not true that he has been light then because he has not
set up for any prison sentence during the time it may stand for okay
But there is nothing that you have had any thoughts
around how should I know he is bright okay no yes but I t not say you said
that it was just suspicion he is not convicted he then he is convicted of something
If yes it had no knowledge of it but then he has failed a
imprisonment that is nothing like no it he must stand for no okay
eh i have not invoked it before but there is one like first draft
to this telephone emptying pm that starts on page 352 and it is then the same
then Daniel Strömbäck who has written what was a bit of this that I wrote about
who wrote this about that you would have had the role of a fixer and it ends at
Page 355 I can take it up because I think
also that and Kelisa what defends a little was into the fact that eh there he has
then made clear then that it is then at your girlfriend's address you connect the evening
where the day after, so it is not at the shooter's street so that it is
Significantly yes eh for that task appeared there so it was perhaps where man
had read
that but I thought I would show then on page 355 for in general so there is
all this included in it in the memorandum that you then established but one has not
brought this task for some reason you thought of this one as we
talked about just yes exactly eh and partly here then as mentioned now we shall see what mine
so you point to then that there should be some kind of transfer then to this
Robin etc. What is it for the transfer it is
a money transfer have you made it yeah okay why then it has not
The suspicion of doing I have sent money to a friend no okay
eh and has it been like to help him for him as well as
able to keep staying away abroad somehow absolutely not no
no okay eh it should apparently be then SEK 6400
Like you
In addition okay yes what what does it concern it is money that I sent over to one
friend okay and then then at 1855 then so
Should you then have sent through Snapchat then as a receipt on this transaction
Yes it is so that he should be able to take out the money he needs a
confirmation number to withdraw the money yes okay so it still is to him
It is not like to show to someone else that you have sent over
money to Robin without no okay it is still then to him as you
writes it yes okay but you have nothing whatsoever
Consulting you claim with this network at all absolutely no no
Okay
eh benzema is there any person you know or have known perhaps
one should express oneself no no okay i check a little borne at contacts it can
after all, be some completely different person but it then stands as a tictoc contact benzema
9 I think there is my user account on tictok what it is your user account about
I remember correctly so I am so called on tiktok okay we will see it is under contacts
We're on page 370 so I can pick up
It yes it maybe so I no it says User id think
I regera show out of the mobile phone all saved
Contacts yes but what is it
So that's tictoch I know as I said I think it's my username I am
not sure but what I do not know it is probably someone on tiktok that one has added
Okay because if you go down then like this list then will then kill everyone and
Dark Vader, so it is people who you have had contact with it, that is
Contacts not your alias no but it is possible to be a contact at TikTok then
that is very possible but i don't know what it is about no no okay no
Then have no more questions thanks thank you there are more questions to
Amando no then
End recording good prosecutors may start with questions etc. Thanks Hello Simona Hello
You are oop to be heard as a observation around October 56, 2023 the night there tell
what do you remember from that days yes eh i mens that we were awakened in the night
Therefore the dogs we poured the two -storey apartment so they sleep the dogs
sleeping down in front of the window so they saw someone in front and started pouring a lot
It is not unusual they pour so hard and so I was spent right away and just said
Name to the dogs they should calm down sometimes something else but they ft seat
a lot and my husband went started walking on stairs down and I opened curtain eh
biner that they should see what is what is in front of the window they see and I saw
Direct eh We have patio Lit patio and the bushes are in front of the fence so I
immediately saw a group of people in front of the h eh bush
the bushes they stand the group so I s right with a man that he g dont go in front of
the window because we have quite we have close small kitchens and we usually leave
up a verin in the kitchen so it shines lamp in front of the street we once yes it
stands a lamp it shines it is pretty good
one these three or yes I think there were three or four people were in
the group and one was in the middle so it was a grip and they have something like that eh
the noise yes one was arrested in the hands mm eh one stands forward I think it was two
Behind him it is about everything from outside the other side of the bushes so it was
so there but i from exercises i see them in the groups etc so they have some kind
noise they had conversations but it is not nice said
they yeah i hear nothing but i see it bubble something it f giant in the room
and outside also mm and then the ones I think it was such a moment that they saw in
window the dogs pouring and my husband so they decided to run away
so everyone went up the hill we have a little hill in front of ours
eh balcony and the one it goes up towards the street side gaton etc. so they ran after all
together that page mm and about how many people did you say
that was it so that it was a group of people yes exactly it was one as a
Gripet and then one front in front of him I think two more was if I remember correctly a s
one also back about and one was the more on in front of the kitchen's eh window so it is
maybe four people etc. and told the police in the beginning i don't remember no okay
and did you perceive that it was like it was the several of these
the people against this arrested or had this arrested also some friend as well
or no he was alone in m it and everyone was in front of him kind of okay about
what time is it like you do these
hunting phone there is like but what time was it yes it
was what time it was and two maybe two t two three mins not okay eh and can
you say something type like this about where is that you see this
what address where are we somewhere that happens everything from in front of
Margs Road Futan Okay Behind the House Yes Eh Can You Describe His Elements on Night
person this arrested person for example what did he look like
ehm as i told you to the police that I met one by day
After he was as I saw from the lower floor
downwards I looked down so it was not very clear but I can tell
But he was a little narrower in the body not so powerful person etc. eh looked young
eh had something dark eh black hat dark clothes it could not see anything clear
face or some eh clothing that one can mm
eh remind good but all were mke those who also in the group were with so bakers or
something like the quilt facial etc. he also had it
Eh I don't remember I think no I don't think but I didn't see his visibility actually
that he be yes mm narrower than maybe not so round mm you so young can you
estimate age
a yes about you can type yes up to 20 maybe mm not older mm okay you saw
Someone did you see his complexion you can say anything about it
Eh i think it was l hee with tender hair mm black reach
Things like that but it was the night then but yes
[Music] eh what what happened then then
Eh they ran when we saw that they run away we immediately called the police and then eh
yes they exactly what we looked at the window later also yes we were a bit close and we
calmed the kids too they just awakened by the dogs
eh later also saw one i think two people passed by like this with mask etc.
So after type half hour maybe or quarter
mm mm just the two just passed by we had an eh point in front of our house middle
Two with are one point so they came from this point up in the hill Ängen mean
i kind of gray just grass etc. since they got from there just up the hill and walked toward
Gatus side also just calm and no noise like that etc. Okay where it was
the right time when the police actually arrived this day after in the morning I mens
Not that was thanks I have no more questions to no some questions etc. Yes
eh how did this person have his hands like this or he who did not hear
to the gang etc. How did he behave eh as I can appreciate or say he
was a little scared he was such calm eh not calm man say he was yes calm he did not
wanted to quarrel he just stood like this and listened to who is around and he he
is not noisy he was not the way he was scared maybe or scared s mm his
Menstunion yes he just yes calmly mm says it mm
[Music] mm do you remember what he had at
Sig some jacket dark jacket maybe black
Mm I don't actually remember mm
And how did these people seem to interact was it eh was there outrage
or how did it go between them eh a person who was
in front of him bubbled something to him carried
said to talk or talk just all the time so not to
high level there is no one used no one that
screaming nothing like that just as otherwise might be heard more
Hi thank you so much question from the defenders no question thank you any
ask good thank you so much eh as I understood it so it is on
Mangårdsvägen 14 Yes Eh and I looked a bit at pictures what it looks like I look
that there is a one main entrance it may be the only entrance to to
The home thus the gate to the home etc. and so that I should understand where
What you see is it in the way or is the no other side of the house behind the house
Rear Prims and
eh then which direction did they go they went eh if you see if you stand in apartment so
I look at nerö so they went right side up right side right side eh de
big there is small hill there and it is continuing another house too it is tovan
there 12an and then again too so they ran that side and it's the street side it is
relatively often that I hear things eh because it is so heard eh but I
Still thought it was a bit strange because it was eh it was a
Thursday eh and thus a Thursday at night does not usually happen
eh so i thought it was a bit strange so then
Eh so like this yes but i kept like listening eh if there comes more sound
Mm and so okay and how long it went on as eh has no idea no okay can you
appreciate [music]
ehm not really no no okay and now have you described it like what you hear sound
from it is like from the stairwell and the railing exactly have you have you perceived
Like sounding can come from something else anywhere else eh no no
Eh then I would like to read a little from a hearing that held with you will
Remember that you heard you yes 6th October
Eh, that is, there in the morning at 1048 mm
and it starts on page 215 Eh and it is recorded then a little different you have
partly then described this as you have sound in the stairs but you also have
described a different sound and I then thought for the guilt of clarity and read it
also and the first question then it was heard or seen I heard when I
would sleep so it hears that someone ran up and down the stairs and dragged
up on something I heard something that knocked out of the top type on the floor maybe
Neighbor above us yes eh i don't remember it but m my possible
eh and so what it sounded like they stamped etc. and I interpret that as to
The stairwell the stairwell was a minute after so you still describe that
You have heard a sound in the stairwell in this company that you describe here today
But this with the neighbor you don't remember that you harju from there no that
happens so often that mm eh then perceived you here today then as
that so that you might be at a two -time mm and in this company so stands
he signed when you get to ask then about what time was this
between 24 o'clock and 0030 okay yes eh there is also a lot
possible as I said I just appreciated the time but do you think you were better
Appreciate the time there then October 6 than you are here today
Eh i also asked about how long you heard this eh and then on
last page then in this hearing 2016 so there is something to add everything
happens in a short time maybe 15 minutes and then it was quiet mm it can
tuning yes very possible yes okay then i have no more questions to
you thanks it is someone else who wants to ask questions yes the sound in the stairwell that
that ran up and down sounded like one or
several i can't answer that no for in the same interrogation as the prosecutor read up
UR so you asked you sounded like it was one or more who ran and
And then you have answered it sounded like a mm can be right yes okay
t mm questions no no question thanks then is brought with you completed
Thank you correctly the prosecutor thanks hi esm all hello you you should not feel that
there is some homework interview and that you have to answer and remember everything without where
clear if there is something you do not remember or if it is uncertain about and is
that something I think is very important that you have told you
I want to hear you a little about yes a little different observations can you tell us what
is what happens ehm yes it is quite late eh in the evening
I have been in town eh met friends
from the education that I go and it has been a very nice evening eh
The last commuter train home has gone so I take the bus instead
eh it is also a pretty eh cold evening earlier so autumn has been very eh
gentle and warm eh but this is a really cold evening and i l a little clothes
on me so that I decide to take a shortcut home and
eh eh on the road there so
Eh i go fast i listen to a pod eh just want to come home as fast as
possible eh and so is an eh person approaching and i think i
Should eh just ignore and go by because it feels a bit shady so late at night
But this person stands up and continues to talk to me eh and I have
after all not because I have headphones so that eh I take off my headphones eh and hear
what the person says eh and then I see that it is a one
very young person who is beaten eh he is dirty in the face he has
swollen and cracked a lip and jacket is broken so that it likes out
padding out of the jacket eh and he tells me he has been robbed
eh and eh got rid of their mobile phone wonder if he can borrow my mobile phone
And call a friend eh and so he also tells him he has been knife cut
and showing up eh his hand which is completely red and bloody eh and
Then I ask about eh eh we really should call a friend should
we don't call the ambulance instead prime.se eh I would like to call a
ambulance eh but eh then he tells me that eh he
does not want to call an ambulance because he has escaped from an HVB home
ehm and quite early in the conversation there he says he has made eh bad
Choice in life eh and eh are trouble and need help eh eh and that he
need to call a friend for and get help getting away from the place
eh and I understand that there is something pretty
scary with this situation but eh i really see an eh young
guy who needs help eh so he can borrow my phone and he gets too
Lov to download Snapchat on the phone
eh and he does and he calls his eh mate i sit a little bit away from that
Is there such a blue box when you have sand
in a chat group eh and try to get hold of someone who can help
eh and
Eh i think eh that i have been told already in the first call when i am carried
talk to him that eh that he has taken on to light a fire on a mailbox
or it sounds pretty innocent eh but in
eh conversation with the friend so it appears that
eh he eh shall light fire on an eh stairwell and
ehm eh that he eh when he was there eh he
had been given the task of pouring gasoline into a mailbox and turns on but when he
is in the stairwell so eh there are no letterboxes on
the doors eh and then he doesn't really know what to do and get eh stressed
and get from there eh he has also been discovered on
The road to this stairwell EH and EH has been beaten
ehm and eh managed to scare away eh those who
attacked him eh and then
eh when he decides not to light fire eh and is on his way away from
the stairwell he gets hounded again and eh extracted in the forest
ehm and for me it sounds like eh a real torture scene where he gets
eh beaten and carved with knife eh and he tells
eh his friend that he lies in a fetal position on the ground eh and that they
chop him eh and at the same time so is like tough and brave and should joke about
that he was chopped in the ham and that his attacker was so damn bad for
that they had such a bad knife eh that he is not getting more injured
eh but also that eh only reason for the other
The abuse is interrupted in the fact that eh aina nearby so that there is one one
Police car that happens to be there and then eh becomes his
ehm and the friend asking again this way what happens to the tab
eh and eh sebastian save a little avoidance but but that he has not with
themselves something eh and so they talk about who can
eh come and help and give reach Skjuss away from eh if they are to order
a taxi or how to do and it is eh very clear that Sebastian not
know where he is somewhere eh so the friend suggests he should share
its position in this chat eh and just to have heard this is after all
Pretty dumb for me but but also knows that there are armed
people nearby who might be looking for
him and eh that may have taken over his eh gun and eh we stand
very exposed it is a clearly illuminated place next to a road and I
think we are very vulnerable where we stand
eh so i say eh i have to go home eh i feel i can't be left
in that place eh and I offer him to accompany eh because I feel that
he is eh really is in danger and that he has had incredible turn as eh has
survived this situation he has been in
eh and eh i also ask if it feels okay
that we take this shortcut up through the forest
eh considering that he has just been beaten in a forest so feel it feels
ok to go here it's a little dark eh but it's okay
and ehm during that walk so he tells
a little more for me because he understands that I have heard so he fills in eh and
tells me that eh this gun they talked about that it is a soft ergan it
is not a real gun ehm and that he
EH would receive 15,000 for eh this assignment to light electricity on the stairwell
and i say it was terribly dt
done and eh eh also comment on something that
It was quite a bit of money for such a mission
ehm we we go up for this rather steep hill and
eh and there eh ehm so he sits in an armchair
eh and eh i live in a pretty small apartment
eh with like a single room only with kitchenette in the room so I stand
and dishes eh for having something to do and
standing with his back to him eh while eh he continues to
Talk to his buddy and eh buddy seems pretty lethargic does not give
so much response or do not know
really what he is going to do eh and
eh Sebastian becomes more and more frustrated over
eh that he does not get any help and that it is like not answering
eh he says this is all spaming everyone in the group eh and even then eh spamma
any person called eh kill all the spamma spamma spamma spamma kill all
so spammy eh and they
eh reason about where he can go
and you can find somewhere eh eh where he can
go eh and after a while so eh can be interrupted by the call and Sebastian is allowed to borrow mine
first aid box eh go into the bathroom and eh flim about eh and
After a while he also asks for help and eh eh and I get to come in and
help and eh wash wounds and change them
eh and and it is then as I ask him what he eh if he wants to say what
His name is in the first name man eh say his name is Sebbe and I tell you what I
called
ehm and then as I remember it, there is a little shorter a little shorter
conversation with the friend after the eh but eh Sebastian is increasingly stated eh and
and that call ends eh and he says he is not feeling well
eh asks if you get allowed and lie down in my bed
and he gets that eh but he seems
have eh hard and be able to lie down without hurting
eh a lot and also gets very stressed by that he eh it bleed through
this eh band he has put on eh so there will be blood in bed and blood on
the sheets eh and eh he got in the armchair
again and is quite white and shakes throughout the body
and eh says he freezes very much so i eh take my my quilt
and put about him eh and talk to him eh
eh pick up alvedon
eh and so I ask again if we should not call an ambulance
ehm and that it is enough that
that he would need help with with these knife the injuries he has
that eh it is not only ambulance personnel coming but there will also police
ehm and in eh after eh the first call
with t two has finished eh so we just sit and wait and eh
We talk to each other eh and I notice that Sebastian has a lot of anxiety
eh and i feel
Ehm i feel very much empathy for him eh
eh
and trying to calm and eh
eh tell him that eh i have also made shit stupid things in life eh
and my life was pretty tangled too when i was 16
ehm but i wish so sincerely he won't let this event
Good
because so eh yes and then eh actually rings 112
up again because they have a hard time finding my apartment eh so I get to guide
the police to traites but then they have just found l I open and let in
them mm about what time was it like you
bumped on him you said that the last commuter tag had gone so you were allowed
to ride the bus you have any idea what time it was yes
Eh i have looked up that eh eh 10 in one so the bus went from
Civic site and eh it was a bit late then so i think it was 20 over
an approximate mm and then it was like relatively in
the near -time to you stepped off this bus that you met on him where I know after all
not really like this where it stops you described any shortcut you went and so on
Yes but just ehm it stays on the other side of the trail over here
Eh so then you have to go in a subway underneath and then past the commuter train eh and
away on the back of the eh that block with eh ica maxi and lidel and so eh but it
Don't be many minutes afterwards you tr on a maximum of five minutes
Mm eh and where somewhere in an approximately
was what you met on him you remember that yes
Eh it is eh i think it's named ebb boat square eh so it this street outside
the house and so exactly eh it is between a deserted plot eh with building fence around
around eh and eh a newly built house with red plaster so we
right at the crossing point there mm and how would you describe his
state of mind when you hit him eh up in turns
Quite focused
ehm and so eh somehow confident that he he
thought he would get help from me and very open to telling you what
that had happened etc. and you described there several different calls as here from your
All the time mm and one of the conversations I perceived as was except there
Still yes eh and you said that you you heard him
say something about some mistake that it is the friend ask about it yes and how
do you perceive it when it came to talk between you and Sebastian when you were talking
about what I actually did not attach so much to it without me eh I got it
here the explanation that it was a soft airgun gun etc.
Eh and and
eh yes, probably didn't know if it was or was anything else but
Eh i was in that situation just focused on we needed to get in
indoors that it was dangerous for us to stay out
mm he said something more about these then the people who had encountered him
So what their agenda was was to rob him on this phone or
Eh I rather think they were wondering what he was doing there okay he said something about
that eh i asked
not eh i was going to read one piece then
around it eh you have been heard twice eh but the first hearing was held with you it
6 October then there at night at 0 335 mm eh and then you ask this about this
If said what he has said to you and then you get a question quite high up on the page
204 he said something more then it says that yes he was afraid he
finished too much they tried to squeeze him
mm and I think that is eh under the second abuse eh it
Second abuse etc. When he was drawn in in the forest mm eh and eh as I
perceived torture him for him to reveal who is his
client eh and he he tells his friend at
telephone that he has revealed that the name of the client begins at J MM and
He ask his friend if the friend thinks that is enough
information for the client to want to murder him
okay and can you describe you say that as two different abuses yes it was so
he told me yes that eh he was on his way to this stairwell
eh gets discovered eh and eh they ask him what he does there
mm eh but that he should threaten them with eh it
Here Saf Ergan Pistol and been left in peace then so he could continue with
his assignment etc. and what did he do then then he described eh so crushed
he box eh to the stairwell and got in
Okay and then I perceived that you said it had been nothing
mailbox in this door it so then he didn't know he would do and
interrupted it all I understood it right then yes prime was something he said to
you or was it something that you heard he told this friend I
Think he told the friend yes okay he said something to you about it
When you talked to get closer or ask any questions about it
ehm in general so I ask very little questions m
Eh I also have a little trouble holding in this way what he told me right away
and v he told me the friend etc. eh but
[Music] eh no I I don't know anymore about it
Mm then i have no more questions for you thank you so much julia k would you like
Asking questions eh I have a question he could describe
These people who had attacked him or who had pulled him into
the forest yes eh it was
eh when he was in my apartment and eh talked to his friend there so
eh they speculated on who it could be and eh he told friends
that there were two people that eh deta was a Swedish guy who was eh
eh large and powerful ehm and a second would be a one